Chapter 1983 – Riddle of the Purple Card

The words of the two old men dispelled Lin Ming’s last traces of doubt.

He needed to find some way to deal with Famine’s soul as soon as possible.

However, even though Famine’s soul had been suppressed for 3.6 billion years, it absolutely wasn’t something that would be easy to contend with. Lin Ming estimated that his current boundary was far from enough.

He needed to increase his cultivation.

He had no idea how much longer the artifact spirit of the Ancient Elysium Seal was able to live on for. The main body of a transcendent spirit treasure might be able to last for 10 billion years, but its artifact spirit wouldn’t be able to survive such a long span of time. In terms of lifespan, it was similar to a living being.

For instance, the artifact spirit that once inhabited Lin Ming’s Black Dragon Spear and Black Dragon Armor had long since died.

“Do you have any more questions?” The two old men smiled at Lin Ming.

Lin Ming pondered for a moment. He said, “Junior has two more questions. The first is about the Holy Scripture. Seniors, do you happen to know about this inheritance?”

“Holy Scripture…” Clear and Ink seemed to fall into a deep state of recollection. “The creator of the Holy Scripture was Immortal Sovereign of the past. He was the High Lord’s rival, and then he lost to the High Lord by a small difference. Afterwards they even became friends…”

The two old men spoke about the history that occurred 10 billion years ago. Their description was brief, but Lin Ming knew that their words involved innumerable secrets.

“Is Immortal Sovereign still alive?” Lin Ming asked.

The two old men shook their heads. “We are only guardians of the High Lord; we have no understanding of Immortal Sovereign…”

“Then, do seniors know if there was a peerless woman that was closely connected to Immortal Sovereign? Someone who possessed an extremely high degree of talent and was also familiar with the Laws of Life and Death?”

What Lin Ming most wanted to know was who the mysterious woman he had seen in the Asura forbidden land’s Ice Cold Mirror was. She was a peerless woman that resembled Sheng Mei and also Lin Ming’s final opponent there.

He wanted to know just how she was related to Sheng Mei.

However, the two old men shook their heads at this question. It was clear they didn’t know much about Immortal Sovereign’s affairs from 10 billion years back.

Lin Ming was slightly disappointed. But, his intuition told him that this secret shared a profound link to Sheng Mei’s own secret.

Lin Ming then asked, “My final question is, I wonder if seniors know about the three divine tools: the Stone of Eternal Life, Grandmist Spirit Bead, as well as a Purple Card?

These three divine tools had always been an enigma in Lin Ming’s heart. In particular, he wanted to know the whereabouts of the last divine tool, the Purple Card.

“Three divine tools…”

Hearing Lin Ming mention the three divine tools, the vision of the two old men turned deep and thoughtful.

“The three divine tools are the most mysterious items in existence. They have existed since time immemorial, and even before the High Lord was born, there were already legends concerning the three divine tools. From different times, from different people, they had different names. For those things names have no meaning at all…

“The High Lord believed that these three divine tools were things left behind by a previous universal era. They might be great worlds that weren’t able to grow, or they might even be formed from the collapse of the previous universe…”

“Universal era?” Lin Ming asked, stunned. This was the first time he had heard something like this before.

“The High Lord believed that even the universes of the 33 Heavens existed in a state of birth and death, creation and annihilation. The 33 Heavens that we currently live in grew out of nothing, having formed from a giant explosion… but before the eruption of the universe, there should have been another super universe before it. Perhaps it also possessed 33 Heavens, perhaps it was 36 Heavens, or perhaps only a single Heaven. No one can say for sure what the Heavenly Dao Laws that governed that universe were like.

“The High Lord called the birth, development, and destruction of a universe a universal era.

“The three divine tools respectively represent the condensed forms of ‘essence’, ‘energy’, and ‘divine’. They correspond to the matter, energy, and Heavenly Dao Laws of a universe. The High Lord speculated that these three divine tools were condensed from the matter, energy, and Heavenly Dao Laws of the previous super universe when it was destroyed. Their existence is filled with infinite mysteries, and the High Lord once obtained one in the past – that is the Purple Card which you speak of…”

Hearing the words of these two old men, Lin Ming was shaken. The Asura Road Master had obtained the Purple Card!

In truth, he guessed that something like this had occurred. He even suspected that the entire Asura Road was created by the Asura Road Master using the Purple Card as its foundation.

“Is the Purple Card still in the hands of Senior Asura?”

“It once was…” Ink lightly shook his head, “But not afterwards.”

“This…” Lin Ming was surprised. “Could there have been someone who stole away the Purple Card from Senior Asura’s hands? Or, did Senior Asura pass down the Purple Card to someone else?”

To give away such a precious divine tool was a bit too unbelievable.

“I am not sure as to specifically what happened. In the codex left behind by the High Lord, the Purple Card is mentioned. In the era before the High Lord was born there was once a peerless powerhouse who wanted to gather all three divine tools. This peerless existence believed that by collecting the three divine tools, he would be able to reign supreme over all of creation and become an immortal being. It was even because of this that a great stormy war of blood and death was whipped up through the entire 33 Heavens. But in the end, the peerless powerhouse who tried to vainly gather the three divine tools was slain and the countless remaining powerhouses scrambled and struggled to obtain the divine tools. But even so, the three divine tools disappeared and no one knew just where they went.

“After hundreds of millions of years, the divine tools appeared. With their appearance, a great storm rose up yet again. Then they disappeared once more. They were like a curse of the world, their appearance frequently followed by a great calamity of the universe!

“These three divine tools once created peerless powerhouses, but they caused even more overlords to perish and sects to be destroyed. Even entire races were exterminated.

“But to these three divine tools, all those ups and downs were nothing more than passing history. No matter how the world changed, those divine tools never changed… as if they would continue spreading for all time, existing until the day that the universe is destroyed…

“The High Lord even thought that once the universe was destroyed, a new universe would appear, evolving from the three divine tools and using them as the foundation… to be born… if things occur like this, then those three divine tools are nothing more than travelers and witnesses passing through this universe. They were originally existences that stood above all, and what martial artists can utilize is only a tiny, almost trivial, part of what they truly are. In the end, how far one can walk down the road of martial arts depends on one’s self…

“They disregard the world. Even though countless chaotic tribulations and disasters are brought about by them, to these three divine tools, they are nothing more than insignificantly small events, as unworthy of mentioning as dust that falls on their surface…

“Because of this, the High Lord’s desire to pursue and obtain all three divine tools faded away. He concluded that everything came down to ‘fate’. The three divine tools could create a peerless being, but they could also summon a great disaster. Everything depended on ‘fate’.

“In the High Lord’s writings, he didn’t mention the Purple Card too much. He only wrote that, if possible, it would bring about inconceivable events and changes to the world and it might give the one who possessed it the chance to turn the world for the better. But, he also warned his descendants to not obsess over this, because one cannot force the hand of ‘fate’.”

As the two old men finished speaking, Lin Ming was lost in thought.

Everything depended on ‘fate’…

Lin Ming himself had once wanted to chase after the Purple Card. The Grandmist Spirit Bead was in the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s hands so it was impossible for him to obtain it. Thus, he wondered whether it was possible that the Purple Card was hidden in the Asura Road.

But now, after listening to the two old men, Lin Ming’s desire to chase after the Purple Card dimmed by a great deal.

As the Asura Road Master said, the three divine tools were objects that surpassed the limits of this world. But in truth they were only witnesses to this world. While they could create powerhouses, they actually destroyed even more.

The true road of martial arts was a path one could only walk down with their own two feet…

“Thank you seniors, this junior understands…”

Lin Ming respectfully bowed towards the two old men. To resist the saints, that was a battle he would have to rely on himself to fight…

The two old men smiled. “There is nothing you need to thank us for. We only told you what you need to know. The demon relic you obtained is a treasure refined from an extreme True Divinity abyssal demon that the High Lord slayed in the past. If you can refine it then your mortal body, blood vitality, and even cultivation will greatly increase. When combined with the third volume of the Asura Sutra, you will obtain an unbelievable advantage…”

Lin Ming nodded. During this return trip to the final trial his harvests were far too great.

Lin Ming didn’t know, but as he finished speaking with the two old men and started to read through the third volume of the Asura Sutra, the day of the final trial’s opening had arrived.

At this time, many influences of the Asura Road had gathered above the Asura Sea. Even the forces of Good Fortune Saint Palace and Soaring Feather God Mountain had come, tensely waiting for the return of their disciples…

Chapter 1985 – Deep Trouble

“I wonder how those boys of our clan have done…”

“The final trial’s competition is too intense and our background is too shallow. If they can at least complete the Gate of Laws test without any problems then I will be happy…”

A sect Elder spoke with a sound transmission. In truth, many of these sects didn’t have the ability to obtain a qualification token for the final trial. But, because of certain factors coinciding and with destiny on their side, they sometimes managed to occasionally obtain one. With the disciples they carefully raised and such a precious final trial qualification token, the future hopes of their sect were pinned on their success. If these disciples perished within, then the losses would be too great.

“He came out, the disciple of my White Snow Sect! Hahaha!”

An old man laughed. Everyone looked to the right and saw a youth slowly flying towards them. He had been transmitted several miles away from the sea viewing platform and had immediately discovered people from his sect.

His sect quickly welcomed him and checked to see if he was injured or not.

At this time, another sect found their disciple. These disciples didn’t enter the fourth level, but they still passed the Gate of Laws and obtained satisfying rewards.

Their rewards were some cultivation methods, Laws, and even heavenly materials that were bred within the energy of the final trial.

Lin Ming naturally held no desire for things like this, but to the martial artists of small sects, these treasures were enough to change their destiny.

“Haha, it looks like the Asura Road disciples obtained some good harvests!”

“I wonder how the several largest influences of the Asura Road have done.”

Some people whispered. Many of them looked at the people from Divine Void Divine Kingdom.

Dragonsweep stroked his beard, his lips turned up in a confident smile. But, his smiled belied the worry in his heart, the worry that something had occurred.

“Look over there, those are the disciples of Divine Void Divine Kingdom! They came out!”

“That’s their leader Whiteflower! Haha, they’re safe!”

Whiteflower was one of the core disciples of Divine Void Divine Kingdom as well as the focus of cultivation for this generation of disciples. As long as he was safe then everything was okay.

Dragonsweep let out a long breath of relief.

“Elder Senior-apprentice Brother, how was it?”

A disciple from Divine Void Divine Kingdom asked as he welcomed Whiteflower. But, to his surprise, he discovered that the disciples of Divine Void Divine Kingdom seemed to shrink away, looking distressed, as if they had encountered something terrifying.

“Whiteflower, what is it?”

Seeing Whiteflower’s appearance, Dragonsweep was puzzled. They didn’t have many disciples that died, so why was everyone looking so troubled?

As Whiteflower and his troop was welcomed back, Dragonsweep discovered that the disciples from other influences were glaring at their Divine Void Divine Kingdom. Then, those disciples used sound transmissions to say something to their Elders.

After they finished speaking, everyone would turn to stare at the disciples of Divine Void Divine Kingdom and even the look in their eyes would change.

“Elder… we…” Whiteflower hesitated.

The Good Fortune Saint Son watched all of this occur from the corners of his eyes. He contemptuously sneered. In his opinion, these people were mostly talking about some inane matters that weren’t worthy of his attention at all. Compared to the demon relic, anything they did was a joke.

“What an idiotic Divine Void Divine Kingdom!”

The Good Fortune Saint Son looked down at Divine Void Divine Kingdom was disdain. Although Divine Void Divine Kingdom was also a True Divinity influence, in the eyes of their Good Fortune Saint Palace, the Soul Emperor Divine Void was one of the weaker True Divinities and was far worse than Soaring Feather God Mountain.

But still, how come the disciples of the Good Fortune Saint Palace didn’t completely kill off the disciples from Divine Void Divine Kingdom?

As these dark thoughts swirled in the Good Fortune Saint Son’s heart, he waited expectantly for the Good Fortune Saint Palace to come out. At least two thirds of their disciples should still be alive.

However, at this moment, the Good Fortune Saint Son’s smile froze on his face.

He could hear some people speaking about Divine Void Divine Kingdom, “…It’s true, absolutely true! The disciples of Divine Void Divine Kingdom obtained a black bone that shined like crystal; its value cannot be estimated!”

Black bone? Inestimable value?

The Good Fortune Saint Son’s heart skipped a beat. Could it possibly be that…

He immediately shot down this thought. There were many lucky chances in the final trial and it wasn’t surprising for there to be some similar object.

But at this time, the disciples of Soaring Feather God Mountain also came out.

They only had two disciples remaining, and they had obvious wounds marring their bodies.

“Who injured you? Where is your elder senior sister?” Fairy Blue Lotus reached out a hand to investigate the situation of these two Soaring Feather God Mountain disciples. Her face immediately darkened.

“A wound left behind by a divine soul attack…”

In these past years, the saint race had sent many disciples to the Asura Road. Fairy Blue Lotus travelled to the Asura Road many times and had a good understanding of the cultivation methods of some large influences of the Asura Road. The injuries of their two Soaring Feather God Mountain disciples seemed to have come from the cultivation methods of Divine Void Divine Kingdom…

“Elder Senior Sister… died…”

The two disciples muttered with hate thick in their voices. As Fairy Blue Lotus heard this, her face turned into a mask of frost.

And at this time, the vortex leading to the final trial began to slowly shrink. This meant that the final trial was soon about to close. The disciples that should have come out would have come out by now. Otherwise, they had died inside.

It was only now that many Elders discovered that the number of disciples who died was far more than they had expected!

And it was also at this time, that in the middle of all these people, the originally confident Good Fortune Saint Son froze like a statue.

“Where are the disciples of my Good Fortune Saint Palace? How come they haven’t come out?”

The Good Fortune Saint Son was utterly stunned. He stared helplessly as the vortex continued to shrink away until it fully vanished.

Yet, the 20 some disciples of the Good Fortune Saint Palace, the Legion of Famine that the Good Fortune Saint Son had raised so carefully, still hadn’t emerged. Had they died inside? Was that even possible?

“The disciples of my Good Fortune Saint Palace, how come they haven’t come out!?” Blue veins stuck out on the Good Fortune Saint Son’s face. Gold light shot out from his entire body, even causing the skies to shake. Wild waves stirred up in the Asura Sea as the Good Fortune Saint Son’s anger reached the peak. The surging waves rolled up like giant tsunamis.

Clearly, from what the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had said to him before, two thirds of the disciples were still alive!

The Good Fortune Saint Son was like a maddened lion. He stepped in front of a small influence and grabbed one of the disciples who had just come out of the final trial.

“Tell me what happened in the final trial!”

The Good Fortune Saint Son’s eyes were blood red, like a rabid animal.

This mission was far too critical to him; he could not accept failure!

“I… I…” The disciple was frightened so badly that his face turned ash gray. Although the Good Fortune Saint Son was only a peak Great World King, in terms of strength, he was actually a master more powerful than an ordinary Empyrean. This disciple’s Great World King level influence wasn’t able to stop him.

“Your… your Good Fortune Saint Palace disciples were… cut down by the Asura Laws… judgment… dead, killed them…”

This disciple stuttered as he spoke, his voice trembling all the while. The Good Fortune Saint Son was so enraged that his eyes nearly popped out of his head.

The Asura Laws had sentenced them to death!?

How could this be!?

For a time, the Good Fortune Saint Son felt his mind go blurry and a ringing sound echo in his ears. How was he going to explain this to the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign? And the demon relic? Where was the demon relic?

That’s right… some people had just said that the disciples of Divine Void Divine Kingdom had obtained a black bone. Was that the demon relic?

Just as this thought popped into the Good Fortune Saint Son’s mind, he discovered that the disciples of many other influences had started to move and surround the disciples of Divine Void Divine Kingdom.

The disciples of Divine Void Divine Kingdom paled. The several Elders from Divine Void Divine Kingdom also had extremely ugly complexions.

As Dragonsweep saw these people surround his Divine Void Divine Kingdom, he coldly said, “Everyone, what is the meaning of this?”

“What do you mean ‘what is the meaning’? Sage Dragonsweep, there is no need to pretend to be clueless at this time. Didn’t your disciples tell you what happened in the fourth level?”

With such a precious treasure, no one could feel relaxed. In particular, the Good Fortune Saint Son’s face was completely distorted.

The situation had developed in the worst direction possible!

Originally, in the mission that the Good Fortune Saint Son led, everyone was to remain as low-key as possible. After his disciples exited the final trial and before the other influences could respond, he would take the demon relic into the body of Famine and then directly leave the Asura Road.

But now, with the existence of the demon relic exposed, all the influences of the Asura Road would force their way into the situation. After all, there were still two True Divinities here and this was not the stage of their saint race. If a battle were to start up here, they would surely suffer a loss!

“Do you plan on attacking us? I’ve already sent a sound transmission to Soul Emperor Divine Void… in another 20 breaths of time or so, he should arrive here…”

Dragonsweep’s face was grim. This situation was far beyond what he could handle. He had no choice but to contact the guardian god of their Divine Void Divine Kingdom – Soul Emperor Divine Void!

Chapter 1989 – Great World King

As the remnant will of the abyssal demon completely disintegrated, the demon power within Lin Ming’s body became utterly masterless and then erupted from within him!

This vast, sea-like strength smashed into Lin Ming’s spiritual sea and mortal body, constantly attacking his inner world.

As this wild demon power rushed through him like a crazed tide, it violently reacted with the power of divinity in Lin Ming’s inner world!

Rumble rumble rumble!

Lin Ming’s body emitted thunderous explosive peals. But at this time, his eyes were no longer blood red, but instead gradually returned to their pure brightness.

Lin Ming’s eyes couldn’t be described just with adjectives like bright or profound anymore. There seemed to be countless lives being born and then perishing within them, planets rapidly revolving.

If an ordinary person were to look at Lin Ming they wouldn’t see anything exceptional. But, if a martial artist with a profound understanding of the Laws and a deep cultivation were to look at Lin Ming, they would see the infinite mysteries contained in his eyes. If Lin Ming were to die, his eyes would become supreme treasures fought over by countless sects.

“Lin Ming, he, he really managed to suppress the demon’s will!”

From nearby the Galaxy Void Furnace, Clear was shocked as he saw Lin Ming’s changes. In his eyes, It was like a true universe was contained within Lin Ming’s body. Endless Laws, energy, matter, all of it was contained within this universe, all-encompassing!

“But that demon will become a hidden danger in his body. If Lin Ming’s spiritual sea were to receive damage in the future, then perhaps…” Ink said with some worry.

However, Clear shook his head, “That’s not necessarily true. In the final moments I felt Lin Ming completely destroy that demonic will when a horrifying soul storm erupted in his spiritual sea. That is not a strength that Lin Ming should be able to use…”

When Lin Ming activated the Magic Cube, it was targeted against the abyssal demon and not Clear or Ink. Although the Magic Cube’s aura was terrifying, it didn’t dissipate outwards. As an ultimate divine tool which surpassed the existence of this cosmos, Clear wasn’t able to feel the Magic Cube. But, he was able to faintly speculate that Lin Ming’s body contained some secret he didn’t know of.

“This child has a great destiny upon him… perhaps he really can achieve the High Lord’s deepest wish…”

“I hope so… in any case, you and I must assist him well. Starting today, he is our Young Lord, regardless of whether he succeeds or not…”

The two old men spoke with sound transmissions. At this time, within the Galaxy Void Furnace, the bone spikes over Lin Ming began to draw back into his body. The demon bone armor and scales also disappeared.

Lin Ming returned to his perfect form. His naked body was bathed in endless starlight, and his inner world constantly evolved with the two different strengths continuously surging through it.

Lin Ming’s consciousness also arrived in his inner world.

He stood at the center of a vast galaxy, looking at the surrounding universe.

He could see innumerable planets in this universe. Some planets were bleak and dark, but some had infinite lives living on them.

These lives, from as small as a blade of grass or a single ant, or as large as a towering tree, or even as majestic as a leviathan or great roc, all of it was clearly sensed by Lin Ming. In this moment he could feel everything within himself. With just a single thought, he could grant these lives a great strength, or maybe instantly destroy them.

In this moment, Lin Ming had become the king of a true universe!

This was truly the feeling of grasping a great universe in his hands. This feeling left Lin Ming intoxicated.

However, although he was intoxicated, he didn’t lose his mind. He controlled the energy within himself to constantly expand this space.

More planets were bred and developed. Some of these planets had humanoid life forms, prosperous countries, and sects that grew stronger with each passing day.

In lofty divine palaces, great rulers prowled. Dragons and Kirins roared and the beat of the Great Dao cycled in rhythm. Lin Ming could feel this world become increasingly full and plentiful, nearly impossible to distinguish between illusion and reality.

When the boundaries of this universe were expanded to their limit, he finally stopped. For a time, all the strength of this universe was poured into Lin Ming’s body.

He had become as one with this universe, becoming the ruler of a true world. In other words – a Great World King!

Bang!

A terrifying energy gushed out from this universe, flushing out and shattering the Galaxy Void Furnace. It was like a divine rainbow shooting straight into the horizon!

Lin Ming’s entire body was bathed in this divine rainbow. His black hair rose up and his body was soaked in this terrifying sea of energy, as if he were wandering in a sea of Laws.

In that instant, Lin Ming had truly broken into the Great World King realm!

Lin Ming’s eyes flashed open and brilliance blossomed within them.

Light shot out from his left eye, like colorful rainbow-hued clouds, filling the world with auspicious lights.

But from his right eye, a gloomy darkness emitted, as if a blood pond hell was contained within, as if sandy Asura plains stretched out in them. Just by looking at this eye, one would feel their soul being sucked into the bottom of an abyss and their spiritual sea falling into illusion.

“Natal Life Dao Palace, Great World King! With the demon power contained in this demon relic, my strength has risen to a new peak. There is no comparison to how I was before!”

Lin Ming gripped his fists together. He fervently hoped he could find a powerful opponent and fight them in a heaven-shaking battle so that he could test out the limits of his strength!

From a Holy Lord to a World King and finally to a Great World King, Lin Ming had used several thousand years to accomplish this during his fourth reincarnation!

Now he was like a phoenix that had undergone nirvana. His strength soared into the heavens!

With a wave of his hand, heaven and earth origin energy condensed into a robe that wrapped around him.

This robe was extremely strange. Lin Ming had casually made it, and he hadn’t designated anything special about it, but had allowed the world Laws to create it.

The robe was half black and half white. It was covered with stars, and the way these stars were arranged revealed infinite mysteries, so deep that one could perceive them forever.

If a World King level master were to summon all their mental strength to look at this robe, they would see phantoms of demons and god kings within it. These demons and god kings were all different, each one containing different principles of the Great Dao.

Just this robe alone, if it were refined and condensed into material essence and then given to any random World King powerhouse, would be a treasure. They could perceive it for hundreds and thousands of years, obtaining great harvests.

At Lin Ming’s boundary, any things he casually discarded would be precious treasures. This was because he was amongst the top characters of the universe!

Of course, to resist the saints and to resist the great calamity, his strength was still lacking.

“Thank you, seniors.”

Lin Ming bowed in the air. Dressed in this black and white robe, it gave Lin Ming an inexplicable feeling, as if where he stood was the center of the universe, the source of light and dark.

“Young Lord, there is no need to bow to us two. The ones bowing should be us. The High Lord showed deep graciousness to our race in the past, and the ancestors of my people have taught us to forever serve the lineage of the High Lord. 10 billion years have passed, and Young Lord should be able to complete the long-cherished wish of the High Lord in the past.”

Clear and Ink changed the way in which they referred to Lin Ming, and as they spoke, they even deeply bowed to him. This flustered Lin Ming and caused him to hurry forwards to help them up. “Seniors, please don’t do this. The reason this junior was able to absorb the demon relic was all thanks to two seniors helping me. As for Senior Asura, junior has inherited a great graciousness from him. If Senior Asura has a wish that he hopes to fulfill, then this junior will try his best to accomplish it; even if I have to pass through fire or water, I will do anything in my power.”

“The High Lord’s wish isn’t something that Young Lord needs to worry about at present. Now, Young Lord should focus on improving your strength. One day when Young Lord becomes a True Divinity, perhaps you truly can change the flow of this world.”

The two old men still weren’t willing to reveal secrets of the Asura Road. Lin Ming didn’t press them further.

“Young Lord, we two had a conversation just now and have some suggestions. The space of the final trial is the central point of the Asura Road’s origin energy and Laws. There are all sorts of pure energies and Laws gathered here, and for the last 10 billion years, innumerous world treasures have been bred and nourished here. Some weren’t taken away by trial challengers and have been collected by my race. Young Lord can use these resources to continue cultivating in the final trial’s seventh level for the next several hundred years in order to consolidate your Great World King foundation. What does Young Master think about this?”

“Mm, then I will have to trouble two seniors.” Lin Ming agreed after considering for a moment.

His Grand Reincarnation Art needed to be done in the outside world in order to bring his state of mind to perfection. But in terms of just consolidating his boundary, this final trial space would give him twice the results with half the effort.

After cultivating for several hundred years here, he could go out to practice the Grand Reincarnation Art to the seventh level. Then, Lin Ming believed he would have enough strength to stir up trouble for the saints!

Chapter 1992B - Lin Huang

...

...

...

“Hurry and run! I will distract it, and the rest of you flee!”

The blue-clothed scholar sent out the most sensible order that he could in this dire situation. The disciples behind him felt their hearts drop into their stomachs. The dangers of recklessly fleeing into the wild forests could be imagined. In particular, the fate of the blue-clothed scholar that was staying behind to delay for time would likely be hopeless!

“High Master!”

The young female disciple that had been chased by the desolate primal giant couldn’t help but cry out in sorrow.

“Hurry and run!”

The blue-clothed scholar bellowed from the depths of his lungs, his 36 flying swords spinning around him.

But at this time, there was a thunderous peal of roars from the forest. The sound was so loud and bass that the earth shook. From the far off forests, seven or eight hill-sized desolate primal giants leapt out!

These desolate primal giants had thick muscles that gripped their bodies like a dragon’s claws. Their skin was gray-blue. It would be impossible for ordinary weapons to even leave behind a scar on that terrifyingly hard skin.

“What!?”

Seeing these new enemies appear, the blue-clothed scholar felt his heart sink. A chill crawled up his back and his entire body turned cold.

Amongst these seven or eight approaching desolate primal giants, there were three royals!

Four royal desolate primal giants had actually appeared from this forest!

Fathomless abyss shrouded his mind and heart. With so many desolate primal giants, scattering and fleeing was no longer possible.

Could it be that they were all destined to die here today?

The blue-clothed scholar bit his lips, a decisive light flashing in his eyes. He was ready to burn his blood essence and go all out in a deathmatch against these desolate primal giants, and carve out a road of blood for his disciples. But at this time, he froze. He discovered that these seven or eight approaching desolate primal giants weren’t coming here to attack them, but were instead fleeing, as if they were being hunted down by something else.

One of the desolate primal giants was running away in panic and chose to rush towards the blue-clothed scholar.

This desolate primal giant came from the royal family and was a top master of its rank; it was even stronger than the desolate primal giant that the blue-clothed scholar had just fought. Its speed was extremely fast and wherever it ran, the earth would cave in and great trees would be broken apart like weeds.

The several young disciples following the blue-clothed scholar hadn’t noticed that these desolate primal giants were trying to escape. They thought that this giant was coming here to kill them.

With opponents from the front and the back, they were sure to die here without a burial.

As they had lost all hope of survival in their hearts, on the verge of waiting for death, the desolate primal giant’s body shook and froze, and it lost all forwards momentum.

In that moment, a gray light had pierced through its body.

Compared to that titanic desolate primal giant, this gray light seemed like a small gray needle, simply unworthy of mentioning. But as it sliced through the giant’s body, it produced a black vortex.

This black vortex grew within the desolate primal giant’s body, becoming larger and larger as it recklessly sucked in the desolate primal giant’s flesh and blood.

It cried out in pain and misery. It used its two hands to cover its chest but it couldn’t stop its life force from passing away. Like this, it crashed into the ground, and the powerful inertia of its weight and size shattered innumerable trees!

As this desolate primal giant toppled down, a young man’s figure appeared like ghosts and gods in the air. His body burned with black flames and he grasped a pale blue spear. His black hair scattered in the wind.

The desolate primal giant beneath it had yet to completely die. It reached out a hand, wanting to crush this youth. But, the youth simply waved his spear and a divine red light fell down from the clouds, thrusting through the desolate primal giant’s head!

Peng!

Horrifying black flames exploded within the desolate primal giant’s brain. Its spiritual sea was instantly destroyed and its life ended there, impossible to die any further.

“That… that person is…”

Seeing this black-haired youth suddenly appear, the young disciples were shocked. Wasn’t this too strong? He had instantly struck down a royal desolate primal giant who was at the peak of his level.

Even the blue-clothed scholar was bewildered. He looked at the blue spear in the youth’s hand, a thoughtful look on his face.

But at this time, a roar echoed out from behind him. The desolate primal giant that he had injured was enraged due to the death of its companion, and it angrily punched out at the blue-clothed scholar!

The blue-clothed scholar’s pupils shrank. Before he could even counterattack, all he saw was a blue light flash in front of him. The head of the desolate primal giant flew up into the air, and the terrifying blood pressure formed a fountain of blood that erupted hundreds of feet into the blue skies.

A top royal desolate primal giant had its head instantly severed!

“This… this strong!?”

The woman who was chased by the desolate primal giant was dumbfounded as she saw the flashing figure of the youth. This youth began hunting down the other desolate primal giants!

And with his horrifying speed, he could easily chase after these desolate primal giants like a lion chasing sheep!

As expected, in several breaths of time, another desolate primal giant had its heart pierced through and it toppled to the ground. This desolate primal giant wasn’t a royal and its body wasn’t too formidable. It directly blew apart beneath the power of the mysterious youth’s attack, nearly split in half!

The young disciples couldn’t help but fly into the skies to watch this battle. They flew to the blue-clothed scholar’s side, and saw that the blue-clothed scholar was watching the youth with a thoughtful look his eyes.

“High Master, who is that man?”

The blue-clothed scholar hesitated for a moment. Then he said, “If I’m not wrong, that youth is called Lin Huang. He comes from Divine Dream City.”

Divine Dream City was the first living zone that the human race had opened up in the wild universe.

It was called a city, but this so-called ‘city’ was merely a name. In truth, Divine Dream City included dozens of planets, including a massive super continent. It was the largest living zone of humans.

And the City Lord of Divine Dream City was the leader of all humanity – Empyrean Divine Dream.

By now, Empyrean Divine Dream had broken into the realm of True Divinity. Whether it was in status or strength, she was the pillar of humanity.

“Divine Dream City? He came from there?” The young disciples looked at each other. Communicating and travelling between the various living zones of humanity wasn’t easy at all. This was because in order to travel through the wild universe one needed a powerful strength as a foundation; otherwise one wouldn’t even have their bones left.

Let alone them, even the blue-clothed scholar wasn’t able to travel between the human living zones.

“Lin Huang… no wonder!”

Amongst the young disciples, some people had heard of Lin Huang and some people hadn’t. A young girl couldn’t help but ask, “Who is he? Is he famous?”

“Of course he’s famous! In Divine Dream City, there is no junior that doesn’t know about him. His talent is too terrifying!” The disciple spoke with awe in his voice. “Well, perhaps you might not know of him, but you should know who his father is. His father is Lin Ming, the man once known as humanity’s number one genius…”

Lin Ming?

Hearing this name, the other disciples sucked in a breath of cold air. This youth was actually Lin Ming’s son!

Chapter 1994 – Dark Clouds

This was a continent that was hundreds of millions of miles wide. On this continent, the origin energy was rich in the air and one could find opulent floating jade palaces everywhere. Rare spirit flowers bloomed throughout, making this land a living paradise.

This continent was called the New Era Continent. 6000 years ago, Empyrean Divine Dream joined together with several other Empyreans to open up this land, allowing it to be developed. Currently it was the largest of the human-inhabited continents.

Within the wild universe that was filled with perils and endless slaughtering, this was a rare blissful land of peace.

The name of New Era signified the hopes of humanity to overcome this tribulation and return to the Divine Realm.

At the center of this continent was an incomparably large divine tree. The crown of this divine tree towered into the clouds and the boughs shaded a radius of thousands of miles.

A quiet immortal palace quietly floated above the crown of this divine tree. This divine tree had numerous rainbow-hued clouds swirling about it. There were grand structures layered high and low, with winding waterside pavilions spread out everywhere. Many spirit beasts and spirit birds flew through the skies, the sight beautiful to the eyes.

In this immortal palace, there was an extremely ordinary-looking garden. The garden was planted with well-tended flowers and plants, all of it seeming delicate.

Dappled golden sunlight sprinkled down, shining down on a door. At some time, the door was pushed open by a jade-white hand and a woman stepped into the garden.

She was a beautiful and lithe young woman. Her looks were elegant and her skin was flawless, as if she were a dream painted by an artist. She wore a black dress that fell to her knees, revealing straight and slender thighs and creamy white ankles.

This woman was Lin Ming’s wife – the half phoenix body Xiao Moxian.

At this time, Xiao Moxian had taken out a pair of gardening scissors and was gently trimming the flowers and plants.

Her movements were patient as she pruned them. A rainbow-hued flower was cut down by her and a flower petal fell into her hands. She placed it in her mouth, slowly chewing it.

The sweet and fragrant scent dissipated through her senses…

These flowers and plants were treasures of the heaven and earth. They could be used for medicine and also to refine high quality pills.

Xiao Moxian plucked another flower petal. She placed it in her mouth, slowly eating it.

With every flower that she cut down, the spirit energy they dissipated began to slowly gather, finally forming a dense and hazy mist in the garden.

Xiao Moxian looked at this swirling mist, lost in thought. She used a finger to gently point at this mist. The energy in the mist began to rapidly move in the air. In just several breaths of time, it gathered into the phantom of a man.

This man had a forehead as sharp as a sword and eyes as bright as stars. His face was edged and angular and he held a long spear in his hands. He gave off a sharp feeling, as if he were some treasure sword hidden in a sheath.

Xiao Moxian looked at this image and gently sighed. Then, she waved her right hand and this phantom dissipated, vanishing into nothing.

She looked towards the skies, disappointed.

For 5000 years, Xiao Moxian’s cultivation had been at a bottleneck. Towards this, Empyrean Divine Dream had guided her, saying that if she couldn’t break past the shackles of self and heart, then it would be even more difficult to break through this cultivation barrier and would cause her cultivation to be delayed for a long time.

During these years, Xiao Moxian had spent a great deal of her time gardening, living life and eating flowers and drinking morning dew.

She used this to reminisce on the cherished memories in her heart.

And also to temper her own state of mind.

She had never been able to accept news of Lin Ming’s death. In truth, even though the saints had long since confirmed Lin Ming’s demise, even though she knew that Lin Ming had departed from her because he was being chased down by Soaring Feather God King, even though she knew he had chosen a path of certain death, she continued to stubbornly believe that Lin Ming was still living…

This might be an obsession or perhaps a kind of reluctance. It might even be because of her blind trust in Lin Ming, her faith that he would survive and once again create miracles…

However, even though she ardently waited for Lin Ming for 5000 years, he still hadn’t returned.

She touched her chest, pulling out a strange necklace.

This necklace was simple and crude. The chain was thick and the design was primitive. As Xiao Moxian wore it, it contrasted sharply against her pale neck, seeming completely incompatible. But for so many years, Xiao Moxian had always had this necklace with her.

This was the first gift that Lin Ming had given her. Its name was – the Thousand Mile Heartlink.

It could remember a person’s soul aura. As long as that person existed in the same world then regardless of how far they were, this necklace’s master could use its ability to communicate with this other person.

This necklace held a special significance to Xiao Moxian.

In the past when Xiao Moxian returned to Demondawn Heavenly Palace from the Asura Road, she had been placed under house arrest by Empyrean Demondawn because she had been with child. Empyrean Demondawn coerced Xiao Moxian to agree to marrying the Good Fortune Saint Son, using the life of her child as a threat. And as Xiao Moxian was in her most desperate time without any way out, she suddenly remembered the Thousand Mile Heartlink. Using it, she was able to contact Lin Ming and discuss countermeasures. Afterwards Lin Ming fought the Good Fortune Saint Son at the Monster Emperor’s Grand Longevity Feast.

Now over 5000 years had passed, and Xiao Moxian always kept the Thousand Mile Heartlink in good condition.

Besides recalling her most beloved memories, she also had a wild hope that one day, when she touched the Thousand Mile Heartlink, she would feel a familiar pull on her soul, a soul that haunted her dreams.

As she held the simple necklace in her hands, she hesitated. Then, she closed her eyes, sinking her thoughts into it…

Within her sea of consciousness, the boundaries were without limit.

However, after Xiao Moxian wandered this sea for a long time she still wasn’t able to find a wisp of that incomparably familiar aura…

Finally, she opened her eyes without having gained anything at all.

She discovered that the array formation runes on the Thousand Mile Heartlink were becoming increasingly weak. The Thousand Mile Heartlink came from the Asura Road, and the core of the array formation was in truth a divine runic symbol. There was a limit to the number of times it could be used, and now after so many years with Xiao Moxian constantly using it to sense Lin Ming’s existence, the array formation had slowly decayed over time and was now nearing collapse.

Once the array formation collapsed the memory of Lin Ming’s soul mark would disappear with it. Then, it would no longer be able to communicate with Lin Ming.

Gently tracing the Thousand Mile Heartlink and feeling the increasingly weak soul mark, Xiao Moxian dismally sighed. Then, she carefully put away the necklace…

“Little Sister Xian’er…”

As Xiao Moxian put away the necklace, two women entered the garden.

Of these two women, one wore a long red dress. She was elegant and mature, her stature tall and proud.

The other women wore a light yellow dress. She was beautiful and charming to the eyes, like the young treasured princess of a family.

These two women were Mu Qianyu and Qin Xingxuan. Now their cultivations had reached the peak Divine Lord realm.

A Divine Lord powerhouse could live for over 100,000 years. If one didn’t factor in foundation and actual combat strength, then with the support of many resources, it wouldn’t be hard for these two women to break into the Holy Lord realm.

In the past, when the human race hastily evacuated the Divine Realm and fled to the wild universe, Mu Qianyu and Qin Xingxuan had been considered non-combatants. Under the arrangements of Empyrean Divine Dream they had left with the first batch of people.

Mu Qianyu noticed the Thousand Mile Heartlink that Xiao Moxian had just put away. She also knew what use this necklace had, and also knew that Xiao Moxian hadn’t found anything just now.

“My two big sisters have arrived.” Xiao Moxian put away her wistful thoughts and revealed a charming smile.

In truth, before Lin Ming had been chased down by Soaring Feather God King and then disappeared without even a message, Xiao Moxian hadn’t actually had much contact with Qin Xingxuan and Mu Qianyu.

They didn’t know each other to begin with, and there was a large disparity between them in multiple aspects. This made it so that they didn’t have many chances to socialize and their relationship was somewhat estranged.

It was only when Lin Ming had disappeared for many years that the three women became much more familiar with each other as they all were in the same situation.

If one ignored the years that Xiao Moxian passed within Tragic Death Valley, then she would be considered the youngest of the three women. Thus, she called Mu Qianyu and Qin Xingxuan her big sisters.

“Huang’er just sent a message. He has arrived at Skyrend World and entered Skyrend God Palace…” Qin Xingxuan said.

Lin Huang was the only bloodline left in the world by Lin Ming. In the past, Lin Ming lived the life of a wanderer and often adventured alone in dangerous realms and situations to temper himself. He had gained many enemies and was often being hunted down by others. Thus, due to all these worries, Lin Ming had made the choice to not leave behind his bloodline with Qin Xingxuan and Mu Qianyu. At the time, the two women hadn’t thought much about it, but now that Lin Ming had been gone for so many years and none of them knew whether or not he was still alive, the two women felt a great deal of regret.

Thus, Xiao Moxian’s son Lin Huang had become their common child.

………….

At this time, at Skyrend World, Lin Huang was standing in a grand hall. He politely bowed, saying, “Junior Lin Huang greets Senior Skyrend.”

In front of Lin Huang, a tall old man strode down from a divine altar. He had fiery red hair and his hands were as large as fans. A kind and gentle smile hung on his face.

“Lin Huang, it’s been over 4000 years. You’ve grown up…”

The breeding of a God Beast was an extremely slow process, and this was even more so for Lin Huang who possessed a heaven-defying bloodline. He had been born only after spending several hundred years in his mother’s womb, and even after he was born, he still didn’t open his eyes but continued sleeping for a hundred years. It was only when his bloodline had finished its growth that he started to grow like other children.

By the time Lin Huang was a year old, almost a thousand years had passed since the war between humanity and the saints erupted.

Empyrean Divine Dream held a grand birthday feast on the day of Lin Huang’s first year. Many human Empyreans had attended and Skyrend Godlord was no exception to this. He also saw Lin Huang at this birthday feast, and now after 4000 years, Lin Huang was considered one of the masters of the human race.

“Senior, this is a letter that Empyrean Divine Dream wrote for you. Junior has brought it.”

Skyrend Godlord was one of the top ranked Empyreans of humanity. And in terms of age and background, he was almost the greatest of humanity. He had a high level of prestige among the human race and Empyrean Divine Dream would frequently consult with him concerning important matters.

However, in most situations, Empyrean Divine Dream would directly communicate with Skyrend Godlord. She rarely sent someone to deliver him a letter.

As Skyrend Godlord received the letter that Empyrean Divine Dream sent him, he probed it with his divine sense.

Slowly, his eyebrows furrowed deeply.

Within this letter there were many images. And, these images left him beyond shocked!

This was a giant red monster. It smashed at the void, again and again, causing cracks to appear in the void. But, these cracks slowly regenerated…

Skyrend Godlord knew just what this red monster was – it was Famine!

And the void that it smashed was the God Lamenting Wall that separated the Divine Realm and the wild universe!

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had gained enough strength that he could forcefully open a connection through the God Lamenting Wall without sacrificing too much strength?

Chapter 1998 – Setting Off On A Journey

Facing Lin Ming’s question, Yan Ke’er was stunned.

If she were to be captured by the saints because of her breakthroughs in strength and then made into a living furnace, that would be a life worse than death.

But as she thought of living a life of mediocrity, never being able to display her talent and wasting her days until her end game, Yan Ke’er felt a heaviness on her heart that she couldn’t explain.

She could not accept such a destiny.

Sometimes, the most painful thing in life wasn’t being defeated in struggling against destiny, but never being given a meaningful chance to struggle against destiny to begin with.

This was what left others wallowing in despair.

Thinking of this, Yan Ke’er clenched her teeth and said, “Even if I know that such a fate might await me, I will still continue to cultivate and grow stronger!”

“Mm… I understand.” Lin Ming sighed. “Since that is the choice you have made, I have nothing left to say. At midnight, come to the ninth room of Ancient Phoenix Hall…”

Lin Ming spoke these words and left.

A stunned Yan Ke’er was left behind. Ancient Phoenix Hall…

This was a training chamber established by the remnant bloodlines of the Ancient Phoenix Clan. Only martial artists of the Ancient Phoenix Clan were allowed to use it, and as a genius of the Ancient Phoenix Clan, she was naturally granted a chamber to use. This was room number nine.

But Lin Ming shouldn’t have the qualifications to enter this training chamber, and he shouldn’t know that hers was the ninth room.

Although she was puzzled, she still went to the ninth room in Ancient Phoenix Hall at midnight.

However, she didn’t see Lin Ming. All she saw was a farewell letter, and in addition to that was a spatial ring.

Seeing this spatial ring, Yan Ke’er was startled. This seemed to be an extremely high quality spatial ring, far surpassing the ones she normally saw.

If she was only startled when seeing the spatial ring, then after probing its contents with her divine sense she was thoroughly shaken.

Within the spatial ring were jade slips of all shapes and colors, over a hundred in total. Just from looking at their luster, one could feel the heart shaking. This was the aura left behind by the vast river of time or from the fluctuations of powerhouses’ energy. One could instantly see that these were extraordinary treasures.

These were inheritances!

Yan Ke’er sucked in a deep breath and continued investigating. Although she only had a Life Destruction realm cultivation, she could still distinguish the approximate rank of these inheritances. In particular, some of these inheritances still had messages carved into them, indicating the realm and life experiences of their maker. They shouldn’t be wrong.

In a time when the saints strictly controlled or eliminated most of humanity’s inheritances, she had suddenly obtained over a hundred sets.

A small number of these inheritances could even be cultivated from the Life Destruction realm to almost the Empyrean realm. It was as if they were custom made for her.

Such a massive and rich wealth of inheritances was something that not even the grand library of the Ancient Phoenix Clan Headquarters in the past would have!

But now, all of this had fallen into her hands, left behind by that mysterious High Master. Yan Ke’er felt this all unbelievable.

After these inheritance jade slips, there was even a massive number of pills and also some spirit artifacts!

These pills alone had such a potent medicinal fragrance that Yan Ke’er was left speechless.

When Lin Ming was in the final trial’s seventh level where he had to swallow the demon relic’s power, he had consumed almost all the high quality pills he had. As for these low level pills, he kept them, occasionally giving away a portion of them. Even so, to the martial artists of the Heaven and Earth Alliance these were priceless treasures.

“High Master, just who is he…”

Yan Ke’er was flustered. Then, she suddenly recalled the letter than Lin Ming left behind for her. She dazedly opened it and saw that the letter was completely blank, without a single letter. But as she touched this letter with her hand, a vast soul force broke into her spiritual sea, transmitting information through her spirit mark.

It was only at this time that she realized Lin Ming had left, and he hadn’t said whether or not he would return. But, Yan Ke’er felt that the High Master had permanently left this small world and wouldn’t return.

Yan Ke’er was a little disappointed.

Before he left, he had left behind these jade slips and told Yan Ke’er that she could do with these cultivation method jade slips as she pleased. She could quietly hoard the treasure and cultivate on her own, or she could share them with others.

But with every additional person that she shared them with, the potential dangers in her future would be that much greater.

If news of the jade slips were to be revealed, the entire Heaven and Earth Alliance would face the threat of imminent destruction.

Before this, Lin Ming hadn’t truly supported the Heaven and Earth Alliance. This was because he knew that too much support would only draw the attention of the saints. If so, the consequences could be imagined. And in the Divine Realm, it was impossible for Lin Ming to personally defend the Heaven and Earth Alliance, otherwise he would be in danger if the saints were to discover his continued existence.

Before he truly left, he had left behind a rich and varied number of cultivation method jade slips with Yan Ke’er. She could keep them to herself, share with the entire Heaven and Earth Alliance, or only share with a select number of people…

But no matter what her choice was, once made, they would have to bear the consequences of their decision…

Every person was responsible for their own choices, regardless of whether that meant glory or destruction…

This was the price of struggling against destiny.

Looking at these jade slips, Yan Ke’er couldn’t find the words to say for a long time. That mysterious High Master had left just like this. In the end, who was he and what was his identity?

And these jade slips… what should she do with them?

Yan Ke’er grit her teeth. She turned around and walked away, going to the room where the Patriarch of the Ancient Phoenix Clan remnant bloodlines was…

……

At this time, Lin Ming had already left the small world where the East Blue Planet was located. He entered Crimson Light World, and with incredible speed he flew towards the border zone of the Divine Realm and the Saint Convocation Heavens!

Lin Ming planned on entering the saint race’s Saint Convocation Heaven.

Ever since the Divine Realm was annexed by the saints, the saints opened many channels between the Divine Realm and the Saint Convocation Heavens. Each channel was wide enough to fit several planets; this was in order to facilitate easier transportation of plundered goods.

These channels were tightly controlled by saint race martial artists. They forbade any human from passing through.

However, no matter how strict the saint race was in defending these channels, they couldn’t send a True Divinity to guard them. With Lin Ming having undergone his multiple rebirths and in addition to his horrifying soul force and Bodily Rebirth Technique, even if a True Divinity personally came here they still might not be able to find anything. Looking at the boundless saint race armies that continued to pass in and out, it would be incredibly difficult to find Lin Ming.

Moreover, the ones currently responsible for guarding the channels were only saint race World Kings.

Thus the innumerable checkpoints within these channels existed only in name to Lin Ming. He easily took on the appearance of a saint martial artist and passed through.

In the saint race’s territory, Lin Ming was even more relaxed. He used the great void shift and rapidly passed through Saint Convocation Heaven.

His goal was – the Soul World!

Soul World, Akashic Dream Battlefield, ancient galactic battlefield!

This was a place where Lin Ming had to go.

His goal was to find Ruby and convince her to help him.

In the past, Empyrean Divine Seal had the help of Fishy. If Lin Ming could obtain Ruby’s help, this his ability to control the Magic Cube would rise to a whole new level.

Moreover, Ruby’s comprehensions of the Laws left Lin Ming dumbfounded. When he was grasping the principles atop the shrine platforms at Fallen God Mountain, Ruby didn’t need to use any energy or effort to see the Law markings left behind by Immortal Sovereign. To her, it was all as easy as a fish swimming through water.

This wasn’t something that Lin Ming could compare with. In the end, Lin Ming cultivated and perceived the Laws, but Ruby herself was condensed from the Laws.

She was a manifestation of the Laws.

Before returning to the wild universe, Lin Ming had to do something.

That was to go to Immemorial Imperial City and undo the bindings of the Ancient Elysium Seal and deal with Famine’s soul.

However, 3.6 billion years ago, Famine had been an extreme True Divinity. It was even possible that before it was injured and forced to cooperate with the saints, it might have been an existence approaching the Asura Road Master and Immortal Sovereign.

Even if Famine was defeated and its soul sealed and suppressed for 3.6 billion years, it was still an extremely terrifying existence.

Lin Ming didn’t have full confidence he could deal with Famine’s soul. But if he had Ruby’s help, his chance of success would be much higher.

The junction point between the saints and spiritas was even more tightly controlled. But, they still couldn’t stop Lin Ming’s steps. He used his same trick and easily passed through.

Then Lin Ming changed his appearance into that of a spiritas genius. He infiltrated his way into a small sect and obtained a token to enter the Akashic Dream Battlefield, staying with the sect until the Akashic Dream Battlefield opened.

The slaughter within the Akashic Dream Battlefield would continue for three years. When Lin Ming arrived at this spiritual universe and saw the Emperor God Wall, his heart was filled with emotion.

He swept his eyes over the Emperor God Wall and saw the name he had once left behind – Polar Ice Lin. He also saw Sheng Mei’s name that was beside his own.

For over 6000 years, no one had been able to surpass them…

Chapter 2000A – Half-step Empyrean

Hearing Ruby’s answer, Lin Ming smiled. This smile contained warmth and affection, as well as hope and desire for the future.

“If you come with me, there may be terrifying things you will have to face. Ruby, are you not afraid?”

“I’m not!”

Ruby gripped her small fists and firmly shook her head.

“Good! Then let’s go!”

As Lin Ming spoke, he raised his right hand. In his palm, a gray cube slowly condensed from his flesh and blood, revolving in the air.

And as soon as Ruby saw this gray cube, her eyes could no longer move from it.

She could feel that this cube was the same as her life.

“I call this the Magic Cube. There are some things that you will slowly know of. This thing is originally the same body as you.”

As Lin Ming spoke, Ruby indeed felt that this thing called the Magic Cube shared her bloodline. It seemed to call to her with some strength she couldn’t explain. She turned into a flow of energy and submerged into the Magic Cube.

In that moment, Lin Ming could feel that his spiritual connection with the Magic Cube had deepened. The originally blurry Laws became increasingly clear. He knew that if he were to use the Magic Cube again, he would be able to display an even greater strength from it.

Lin Ming clenched his fist and the Magic Cube returned to his body. He stamped his feet and flew upwards, sinking into the void and directly vanishing.

After leaving the Soul Cave, Lin Ming’s destination was the ancient galactic battlefield within the Akashic Dream Universe.

He had to stay in the Akashic Dream Battlefield for the full three years before the exit would open. This was something that Lin Ming couldn’t change no matter how strong he was right now; it was one of the Laws of the Akashic Dream Universe.

So during this period of time, he would break into the half-step Empyrean realm.

He returned to the ancient galactic battlefield once more. As he looked at this lonely and desolate galaxy, he closed his eyes.

The last time he was here his boundary had been insufficient; he had only been able to vaguely feel the aura of the Asura Road Master and the Holy Scripture creator.

But now, from this ravaged galaxy, from the innumerable eternal space cracks that littered the starry space, he was able to make out more details of the battle between the Asura Road Master and the Holy Scripture creator.

All of this was thanks to Lin Ming’s higher understanding of the two great Laws.

Lin Ming wandered about in the void. The great echo of the ancient era seemed to flow into his ears across the vast river of time.

His deep understanding of the world’s Great Dao had never been so clear before.

Behind him, Ruby followed closely.

After arriving at a planet that had yet to be fully destroyed, Lin Ming sat down in the void.

“Ruby, in a moment I will use a supernatural technique to refine a great treasure. You’ll be fine if you watch from afar.”

“Mm!” Ruby nodded. Her form faded as she flew off to a distant end of the galaxy.

The heavens and earth fell silent.

Lin Ming sat in this silence. The strength within his body began to swiftly and wildly rise. He became a furnace, rapidly arousing the potential within his body.

Every pore and hole on his body began to emit a blinding light.

At this moment, Lin Ming had become a great burning star. He shone through eternity, burning away the dark, searing away the night, brimming full of vitality.

Suddenly, he formed tens of thousands of seals with his hand. Countless runes swelled out in all directions of the galaxy like ripples, instantly spreading for tens of millions of miles.

The originally dying and ebbing stars seemed to come back alive, shining with overwhelmingly bright starlight.

Starlight shined down from the core of these stars, turning into silver pythons in the air.

They wove together in the air, slowly wrapping Lin Ming within and forming the Galaxy Void Furnace.

Not just that, but behind the Galaxy Void Furnace, the giant phantom of an Asura appeared. It grasped a long spear, its bloody killing intent soaring into the stars. It stood behind Lin Ming like a guardian god.

Lin Ming’s mind was as steady as a rock, disallowing any outside interference. Within his palm, the demon relic appeared, shining like pitch black jade and exuding a bloodthirsty and ominous aura.

This relic only had 70% of its strength remaining. He had to take this remaining strength and refine and swallow it in one attempt!

This was a crazy decision.

He chose to borrow the power of stars within this ancient galactic battlefield. By arranging the Galaxy Void Furnace and then drawing support from the remnant marks of the fierce battle that occurred between the Asura Road Master and Holy Scripture creator, he would use this power to suppress the demonic power of the demon relic.

The potential in his body erupted without end. Within Lin Ming’s pupils, stars were born and destroyed, suns and moons rising and falling.

His aura rose to an extreme, and the roar of a True Dragon echoed out from his body. At this time, Lin Ming took the demon relic in his hands and tossed it into the Galaxy Void Furnace, refining it with starlight. Then, he leapt in with it.

Within the final trial’s seventh level, Lin Ming had already mastered the secret skill behind the Galaxy Void Furnace.

The demon relic tumbled about in the phantasmal starlight. It became hungry and wild, filled with eager desire to devour Lin Ming’s body.

After all, this demon relic was refined from the essence of an abyssal. Although the demon’s soul had been erased, the demon relic itself still retained its swallowing instinct.

It longed for a powerful body, longed for a strong blood vitality. Thus, Lin Ming’s body possessed an infinite temptation for it.

As soon as the demon relic’s power entered Lin Ming’s body, the strength within him erupted like a volcano.

Streams of blood threaded with endless power of Laws stubbornly tied up the demon relic like shackles.

Lin Ming’s blood vitality was monstrous. It soared to the heavens, directly rushing over the demon relic.

Every time his blood vitality washed over the demon relic, it would take away a portion of that cruel and evil power.

This power turned into fiery demons that floated up and down in the sea of blood. The demons roared out at the top of their lungs, but soon, a mystical power of thunder crashed down from up high, killing off these demons!

Rumble rumble rumble!

Divine thunder crashed down without end. The demon relic’s tyrannical aura was cleansed away, turned into the purest form of strength that then fused with Lin Ming.

Compared to the last time he refined the demon relic, Lin Ming was much more calm and composed.

He had already swallowed a massive amount of demon power and had formed a seed of demon power in his body. This time, what he needed was pure strength. Then he could use this pure strength to break into the half-step Empyrean realm.

Time passed. Of the remaining 70% of the demon relic’s power, another 30% was absorbed by Lin Ming. All that was left over was the core section that pulsated like a heart.

No matter how much Lin Ming washed the demon relic with his blood vitality, he still couldn’t wash out the core.

This was the most essential part of the demon relic and also the most difficult to refine. As Lin Ming was slowly digesting this strength, a wisp of black light exploded from the demon relic. Finally, the wisp of black light condensed into an abyssal demon phantom within Lin Ming’s spiritual sea.

As this abyssal’s massive figure became fully visible, one could see the two dark metallic horns on its head. Its entire body glittered with arcs of lightning and it was covered with pitch black scales that exuded a metallic sheen. It stood in a pool of blood and it held a towering demon palace within its hand. It rampaged straight through Lin Ming’s spiritual sea.

Roar!

That demon palace carried with it a momentum that seemed as if it could crush apart anything in its way. It savagely flew through the air, and wherever it went, great tracts of Lin Ming’s soul force would be destroyed – the abyssal wanted to completely raze Lin Ming’s spiritual sea.

Lin Ming’s pupils shrank. The final moments of refining the demon relic had arrived.

Facing the core strength of the demon relic, he was far more prepared than the first time he swallowed its strength. He had more experience and his strength had risen considerably.

Within the Galaxy Void Furnace, the Laws of the Holy Scripture and Heavenly Sutra were drawn into his spiritual sea through his soul force.

As the remnant marks of two great supreme powerhouses met the rampaging abyssal, they suddenly became active.

After all, whether it was Immortal Sovereign of the Asura Road Master, they were both intelligent life forms of the 33 Heavens. And all intelligent life forms shared a mortal hatred with all abyssal demons. This was something branded into their very beings, a part of their instinct that would never change.

The marks of these two highest Laws worked to suppress the abyssal together!

Chapter 2000B – Half-step Empyrean

The marks of these two highest Laws worked to suppress the abyssal together!

Although this abyssal was powerful, it had already been slain by the Asura Road Master and had an inherent fear of him. As it felt the aura of the Asura Road Master, its cruel and barbaric killing intent suddenly faded away by a great deal.

In these circumstances, the two Laws continuously barraged the abyssal phantom, causing it to cry out in pain and misery again and again. Then, with a loud explosion, the abyssal completely exploded beneath the onslaught of Laws!

Lin Ming knew that at this moment, he had already completely refined the final wisp of demonic will within the demon relic and was now in full control of this strength!

Within the Galaxy Void Furnace, the endless starlight pierced into Lin Ming’s body. Endless star runes emitted an ancient intent as they wrapped around Lin Ming.

At this time, the final dregs of the demon relic’s core exploded, turning into the purest essence of power and spreading into Lin Ming’s body.

His appearance changing technique had already vanished. His appearance had reverted to that of a formidable and handsome youth.

“Little Black, come out!”

At this time, Lin Ming called for the little black dragon to emerge. The little black dragon happily cheered as it dived into the sea of energy.

A God Beast’s body possessed an incredible carrying capacity. At this time, Little Black was like a withered sponge thrown in water, greedily absorbing all the surrounding strength!

Energy flowed into its open jaws, flowing into its organs and starting to transform its body.

Over a thousand years had passed since Little Black had gone to the final trial. Its body was already as large as a young dragon of the dragon race, and its ability to absorb this pure demonic energy was even greater.

Ka ka ka!

Little Black’s horn became longer and thicker, and fierce spikes like those on an abyssal demon appeared on its tail. If this tail were to swipe across someone, the damage it would cause could be imagined.

Slowly, Little Black’s spine, wings, claws, everything was affected by this demon power and became increasingly fierce.

After absorbing this demon power, its body had become different from ordinary royal Black Dragons.

But at this time, Lin Ming couldn’t bother with these things. Great noises rang out from within his body, like the beatings of a great drum.

Bits of demon relic essence burned like stars as they blazed through Lin Ming’s body.

As Lin Ming and Little Black swallowed the remaining 70% of the demon relic’s strength, over 50% of that had been swallowed by Lin Ming. Even though he was strong, the pain was so intense that veins stuck out on his forehead. It felt like his flesh and blood and even his divine soul was being burned cleanly away by the demon relic’s essence.

But Lin Ming’s body had been tempered to an abnormal state. He forcefully withstood this immense demonic strength and even drew it to attach to different places all over his body.

Bang!

When the energy was condensed to the peak, a great door seemed to be pushed open within Lin Ming. Endless and boundless essence energy became a giant hammer that crashed into Lin Ming’s inner world!

Within Lin Ming’s inner world, a vast and limitless strength started to crazily gather, condensing in the center of his universe. It slowly evolved into the giant phantom of a person!

This human phantom was terrifyingly large. By stretching out a palm it could grasp a planet!

The phantom’s face was majestic and dignified, as if it stood above all living beings, so high and lofty that nothing could face it.

It was like a god king who rose up, its aura frightening the vastness of space, its divine light illuminating the galaxy!

And looking at this giant’s appearance, it was actually somewhat similar to Lin Ming.

This was an Empyrean that belonged to Lin Ming!

The so-called Empyrean was the Supreme of the heavens and earth. Once a martial artist reached this realm, they could form a true Supreme within their inner world.

A half-step Empyrean was only a virtual phantom.

As for a true Empyrean, they would produce a true material Supreme, able to shock and awe their own world.

From a Great World King to a half-step Empyrean, this was an incredibly difficult step. Many powerhouses were stuck at this checkpoint for their entire lives.

But once one became a half-step Empyrean and formed their own Supreme phantom, then transitioning to their own true material Supreme wasn’t difficult at all.

In other words, for most half-step Empyreans, as long as they didn’t perish they would eventually be able to become Empyreans.

Even between a half-step Empyrean and Great World King, there was an essential difference. Once a half-step Empyrean condensed their own Supreme phantom, killing a similarly talented Great World King became simple.

As the Supreme phantom formed, Lin Ming’s self-created inner world began to experience heaven-shaking changes as it was nourished by the essence of the demon relic.

Although he had formed his inner world, that inner world had been filled with endless fog and blurriness. It was vast, but the strength within was disorderly and too varied.

But with so much demon relic essence pouring in, carrying with it an aura of cold and death, it actually began a chain of miraculous changes.

From Lin Ming’s strength, whether it was the power of divinity from the Laws of the 33 Heavens, or the power of life from the Holy Scripture, it was inevitably biased towards the power of light.

But the power of the demon relic that Lin Ming absorbed was actually the power of pure darkness.

These two strengths represented extreme polar opposites.

And yin and yang were the greatest source foundation of the world, where all of existence derived from.

As the two strengths mixed together and collided, thunderous sounds echoed out. The disorderly strength turned chaotic, and soon, traces of vitality appeared.

This part of the world was also sliced open by the yin and yang energies. A dim brown strength vaguely evolved from between them. It became like a mystical turtle, carrying the earth on its back. A sacred and holy energy wafted out, roaming through the deep blue skies…

The world continued to expand. Beneath the aura of the yin and yang, the chaotic world Laws began to be brought to order.

The truth was that when Lin Ming became a World King, his inner world had already been completely different from the inner world of a normal martial artist.

And now this difference increased even further!

The power of divinity, the power of demons, these two strengths tangled within his inner world, causing more things to appear within it.

In addition to the two highest Laws of the Holy Scripture and Heavenly Sutra, Lin Ming’s inner world had become a miracle that no one had been able to accomplish in the vast and endless river of the years.

Even heroes like the Asura Road Master, even talented geniuses like the Holy Scripture creator, although the two of them had travelled to the extremes of their roads, one had travelled to the extremes of the world universe and one had travelled to the extreme of the body universe.

And Lin Ming evolved a world in his body; this was the same as combining the world of the universe and the world of the body together.

Then, by gathering the power of divinity and the power of demons, he had slowly stepped onto a path that no one had ventured on before.

If he could truly refine his inner world to completion, then Lin Ming would undoubtedly become someone who surpassed any genius who existed or who had existed.

As the Supreme phantom within Lin Ming’s inner world stabilized itself, he tossed his head back and roared into the heavens, his body hurtling up and impacting into space!

Bang!

The Galaxy Void Furnace was blasted open!

Lin Ming’s blood vitality surged like wild waves, like a peerless god king. At this time, his entire body blazed with blinding brilliance, dazzling like a sun.

He could feel that his body had never been as powerful as it was today, as if he could reverse rivers of stars and slaughter gods and buddhas!

Weng!

The Black Dragon Spear leapt into Lin Ming’s hand. It violently wobbled and a resounding echo spread through the world.

Then, with a dragon’s horrifying roar, a massive black dragon rushed out from the shattered starlight, its two wings shaking the void behind Lin Ming!

Lin Ming stood atop the black dragon’s head. He grasped the Black Dragon Spear, his eyes as sharp as electricity. He gazed at the endless starry skies above him.

His goal had never been the saints, but had been this vast and endless galaxy, the cosmos of the 33 Heavens, the eternal world.

As for humanity’s great calamity, perhaps… it was his smelting trial!

Chapter 2002 – One Last Pure Land

“It’s really you…” After confirming Lin Ming’s status, the Ancient Elysium Seal seemed filled with emotion. “You’ve returned…”

“Yes, Senior, junior has returned…”

Lin Ming respectfully bowed. In the past, he didn’t know just what was sealed beneath the Ancient Elysium Seal. He only knew that the artifact spirit of the Ancient Elysium Seal had guarded this land for 3.6 billion years, and that was far too shocking a time.

But now he knew that the soul of Famine was being sealed and suppressed beneath the Ancient Elysium Seal, the soul of an extreme True Divinity level demon. Now, besides shock, Lin Ming also felt a reverent respect.

In the past, Empyrean Divine Seal as well as the Ancient Elysium Seal artifact spirit had paid far too great a price in order to obtain victory in the great calamity.

“Mm… you are already…”

The Ancient Elysium Seal artifact spirit looked at Lin Ming with some surprise. It had just noticed Lin Ming’s cultivation boundary – a half-step Empyrean.

To become a half-step Empyrean after 6500-6600 years, although this was an extremely fast cultivation rate, it didn’t shock the artifact spirit too much. After all, it knew that Lin Ming had the Magic Cube.

But when it tried to probe Lin Ming’s inner world just now, it discovered something amazing. The artifact spirit was completely unable to understand his inner world, as if everything was encompassed within, possessing a complete set of advanced Laws and an extremely terrifying and mysterious power.

This youth was not just any ordinary half-step Empyrean. As for his true strength, it was hard for the Ancient Elysium Seal artifact spirit to estimate. It was like a Divine Dragon was slumbering deep within his body, and as long as he wanted to he could erupt with a strength that would destroy the heavens and sunder the earth.

“Junior has already learned about many things, and as for the great calamity that Senior mentions, it has already erupted…” Lin Ming explained.

Deep from the void, a quiet sigh reverberated outwards. “Everything is fated… what will come, will eventually come.”

The Ancient Elysium Seal artifact spirit said. Then, the void in front of Lin Ming twisted and pure black runes appeared, slowly gathering into the appearance of an old man’s face.

This face seemed carved from metal and it was filled with the ice-cold sobriety of reality. The eyes were deep and profound, as if this face had no pupils but black holes instead.

Lin Ming knew that this metallic face was the true form of the Ancient Elysium Seal artifact spirit.

At this time, Lin Ming could feel constant waves of weakness emanating from the Ancient Elysium Seal artifact spirit. Compared to 6000 some years ago, it didn’t seem to possess even half of its previous strength.

This left Lin Ming puzzled.

“What has Senior experienced in these years that has used up so much energy?”

“This is all because of… Famine.”

The dark eyes of the artifact spirit flashed with a mystical light. “Famine has come. I felt it, but it also did. The faint connection that exists between its soul and body as well as its natural instinct caused it to begin stirring once more, almost approaching consciousness. I did everything in my power to suppress it once more, but I ended up using far too much origin energy… of course, it didn’t get off any better.”

The Ancient Elysium Seal’s artifact spirit sounded exhausted. The ‘it’ that it referred to was naturally Famine’s soul.

When the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign came to the Divine Realm, Famine’s soul desired to break out of the seal. The deeply slumbering Ancient Elysium Seal artifact spirit had awakened and they had engaged in a great battle where both parties had been grievously wounded.

But if this were to continue, the Ancient Elysium Seal artifact spirit felt that the first one to be unable to last any longer would be itself.

“I cannot seal it for much longer… at least 4000 years or at most 10,000 years. The day it breaks the seal is also the day that I perish in dust. At that time, Famine’s soul will return to its mortal body and the consequences of that will be inconceivable.”

Although the artifact spirit was what it was, it had still lived for 3.6 billion years. The Ancient Elysium Seal was far too old and didn’t have much strength remaining.

“I fear that Famine’s soul will not return.” Lin Ming suddenly said.

“Mm?” The Ancient Elysium Seal artifact spirit was startled.

“Senior likely doesn’t know, but Famine’s flesh and blood has already been subdued by the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign and made into an avatar. And, humanity’s great calamity was also all planned by the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign.”

“Subdued?”

The Ancient Elysium Seal artifact spirit was stunned. It hadn’t thought that the ever-powerful Famine would manage to be subdued by someone.

“That’s right. This is likely related to a divine tool that the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign obtained. The reason junior came to look for Senior is because of Famine’s soul!”

“Mm?” The Ancient Elysium Seal artifact spirit was dumbfounded. “What do you want to do?”

“Junior wants to undo the seal, and from Famine’s soul, find a method to turn the battle against the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign!”

Lin Ming’s words were stunning. For a time, the Ancient Elysium Seal artifact spirit was left speechless.

It looked at Lin Ming with amazement in its eyes. Undo the seal and find a method to turn the battle against the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign through Famine’s soul?

“Do you understand what you are saying?”

“I know. But, I still want to attempt it!”

Lin Ming firmly said. For this day, he had made far too many preparations.

“And you understand the consequences of this?” The Ancient Elysium Seal artifact spirit’s voice turned grim and serious.

“If I am defeated, then my soul will be swallowed by Famine. Then, Famine’s soul will also escape. It may choose to return to its body and fight with the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. Although I would like to see both of them harm each other, I have a feeling that the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign has already expected this might happen and is even prepared for it. At that time, Famine’s soul which has been weakened over 3.6 billion years will lose and be made into nothing but a gift for the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign…”

Listening to Lin Ming’s words, the Ancient Elysium Seal artifact spirit’s complexion turned solemn. It stared deep into Lin Ming’s eyes. It was clear that Lin Ming had already considered every aspect of this decision.

If one could cultivate to a half-step Empyrean in 6600-6700 years while possessing strength that far outstripped other half-step Empyreans’, the artifact spirit knew that it was impossible for this youth to randomly make such rash decisions. Otherwise, he would have long since died.

“Very well! Since that’s the case, I’ll join with you on this one final bet!”

The artifact spirit slowly said after an incense stick of time.

This seal contained far too much meaning. It was a seal that its master had laid down at the cost of his life, and protecting this seal was the reason for which the Ancient Elysium Seal artifact spirit existed.

Now it would personally undo the seal.

Of course, if it didn’t do so then once another expanse of years passed, the seal would eventually be shattered from within. If so, then the artifact spirit might as well take this bet!

The Ancient Elysium Seal artifact spirit’s face vanished. At the same time, the massive violet sun crystal mountain in front of Lin Ming began to melt away. Within the crystal mountain, a cave opening appeared, allowing Lin Ming to walk in.

Lin Ming didn’t immediately enter. He composed his breathing and entered an optimal fused martial intent state. Then, he stepped into the tunnel leading inside the crystal mountain.

Step after step, Lin Ming’s pace was slow and measured.

As he walked into the depths of the violet sun crystal mountain, he suddenly saw shimmering writings appear all around him on the crystal walls.

Each character was written with strokes as heavy as a mountain range. They emitted an ancient and boundless aura.

These were writings from Empyrean Divine Seal. They contained the mysteries of the Divine Seal Art as well as Concepts of the Asura Heavenly Dao.

Just this tunnel alone had tens of thousands of seal characters. If so, then in the massive violet sun crystal mountain, there would be trillions upon trillions of seal characters.

Lin Ming could feel that each seal character contained the condensed bravery and heroic spirit of Empyrean Divine Seal.

He couldn’t help but gently trace his fingers along these seal characters. People were like their words, and from these curved characters, Lin Ming could feel the gallant and epic bearing of Empyrean Divine Seal in the past.

After several hours, Lin Ming finally arrived at the center of the Divine Seal Array. This place was like a temple. The temple was lit up with brilliant lights, and at the central point of this temple was a great floating bronze seal!

This great bronze seal was engraved with numerous images. And on the top of this seal was a great yellow dragon that served as the handle of the seal.

This was the Ancient Elysium Seal’s true form.

However, what caught Lin Ming’s attention was not the Ancient Elysium Seal, but everything else in the temple.

There were skeletons here!

These skeletons were arranged around the great array and there were dozens in total. Their arrangement was like petals of a sunflower, and each skeleton glowed with rainbow-hued lights, opalescent and shining. Although billions of years had passed, they still emitted a dignified and holy aura.

Without a doubt, these were skeletons left behind by peerless powerhouses.

“This is… these remains are…”

Lin Ming could faintly guess what had occurred. His heart began to fill with awe.

The Ancient Elysium Seal artifact spirit’s face suddenly appeared in the air. Its icy cold metallic face revealed sorrow and a trace of disappointment.

“These are the remains of blood sacrifices that were used to stabilize the Divine Seal Array. Each one was a famed elder of the human race…”

Lin Ming’s mind shook; he was left speechless.

“The Divine Seal Array used to suppress Famine’s soul had to be arranged ahead of time. This array formation itself took ten years to create, and at the time, Famine was at least an extreme True Divinity. With Empyrean Divine Seal’s strength, it was impossible for him to create an array formation powerful enough to completely seal away an extreme True Divinity. He could only draw support from the blood sacrifices of human powerhouses. The runes at the core of the array formation were all written in the blood of these famed elders, and as for the array heart of the array formation… that is a sealing black hole, created from the collapsed inner worlds of numerous powerhouses…

“This is a great sealing array formation that was laid down using the blood and pain of innumerable peerless human powerhouses.”

The Ancient Elysium Seal’s voice was slow, but the words it spoke left Lin Ming bewildered.

He looked at the runes around this great array. And indeed, these runes were a mottled dark red, written using the blood of these human masters that weren’t willing to resign themselves to destruction.

Lin Ming silently walked to a skeleton. This skeleton was a bit bent; it was clearly left behind by an old man. Lin Ming didn’t know who this skeleton had been before either. Neither his name nor history had been recorded.

No one knew that this was a heroic soul who had sacrificed himself to resist the great calamity 3.6 billion years ago, and here he died in obscurity…

Lin Ming straightened his clothes and deeply bowed.

Then, he moved, walking to each skeleton and bowing to them, feeling the auras that these seniors of humanity left behind. His eyes began to turn wet and he remained silent throughout.

It could be imagined that in the past, humanity had run into a similar dead end. And they didn’t have the wild universe as an escape route; they could only risk their lives on a final bet.

In order to create this sealing array formation, these human powerhouses sacrificed themselves, all in order to capture a result that they would never see. This kind of tragedy left Lin Ming’s heart shaking.

Lin Ming continued until he bowed to the last skeleton. Then, he saw some words carved into the ground near that skeleton.

“I am willing to have my hundred million years of life be reincarnated into an enchantment. To suffer 10,000 lives of loneliness, to suffer 10,000 lives of tribulations, to suffer 10,000 lives of hardships, all I wish is to shelter my race and create this last pure land for them!”

Chapter 2004 – Fighting Famine

Lin Ming’s strength had aroused immense interest in Famine. With a roar, it began to burn its own source soul force!

Hu – !

Hu – !

Hu – !

Flames blazed. After Famine burned its source soul force, it erupted with dreadful black flames. They burnt through the void, their heat so devastating that the Ancient Elysium Seal artifact spirit couldn’t help but retreat.

“This crazy beast!”

The artifact spirit grimaced. Famine had been suppressed for 3.6 billion years and in the last several thousand years, it had engaged the artifact spirit in unending battle. It had already consumed an incalculable amount of its soul force, but now it actually continued to crazily burn away its source soul force.

This was undoubtedly creating a giant wound.

“Crazy? Hehe, I believe that as long as I can swallow you, everything I’ve lost can be restored.”

Famine diabolically leered at Lin Ming. Its 1000 eyes emitted a fierce demonic light. This sort of feeling was like a starving wolf staring at delicious prey.

Famine was an evil and cruel demon. It was merciless to other creatures and also merciless to itself. With the chance of escape so close, it was willing to risk everything!

At this time, Famine attacked. Its 1000 hands turned into 1000 pythons that surged towards Lin Ming!

“Be careful!”

The artifact spirit shouted out. The giant ancient bronze seal came crashing down like a mountain, smashing into Famine!

Bang!

With a horrifying strike, Famine shook. 300 pythons changed directions to collide with the Ancient Elysium Seal. It had split off a third of its strength to forcefully resist this strike!

When Famine was suppressed by the Divine Seal Array, it was restricted by the array formation and thus it couldn’t compete with the Ancient Elysium Seal. But now, with the seal broken, it was able to reverse the situation after burning its source soul force!

“I’ll kill you all!”

Famine roared into the air. Its demonic eyes blazed with a horrendous killing intent!

The demon domain expanded once more, covering both Lin Ming and the Ancient Elysium Seal!

700 pythons recklessly hurtled towards Lin Ming, surrounding his protective grandmist space.

Piki paka!

Grandmist energy was wildly swallowed up by the pythons. Lin Ming was besieged on all sides!

Famine cruelly smiled. As it was already sure that Lin Ming would be swallowed up by these 700 pythons and have his spiritual sea torn to pieces, a sudden change occurred!

In that moment, a mystical and terrifying black light, one that seemed to carry with it the will of the Heavenly Dao, came slashing out like the sword of a divine god!

It cut out, splitting apart the heavens and earth. The pythons formed from demon energy became like snow that had molten metal poured onto them, instantly melting away.

Puff! Puff!

Hundreds of pythons were sheared off by this divine light. Black blood gushed out!

This black blood was Famine’s soul force. Lin Ming’s attack caused Famine to cry out in pain again and again.

“Ahhh!”

Famine screeched like a cat that had boiling water poured on it. Its sharp and ear-splitting cries shook the air. It dragged its half-remaining body away and tumbled through the air, surging with demonic energy as it protected itself.

Its pitch black eyes stared hatefully at Lin Ming.

Or, it was more accurate to say at Lin Ming’s hand!

At this time, endless black starlight had gathered within Lin Ming’s right hand. The space here had twisted, and within this space distortion, a dark gray cube slowly revolved.

The cube was simple and plain, covered with strange patterns and wrapped in a shroud of riddles.

As Famine saw this cube, it instantly froze. Its pupils flashed with pure disbelief.

Suddenly, in its heart that feared neither the heavens nor earth, a chill crept in.

 “The Stone of Eternal Life… that is the Stone of Eternal Life! Why is it in your hands!?”

He could clearly feel the terrifying soul force emitting from the Magic Cube!

The Magic Cube was the ultimate nemesis of all souls and spiritual strengths! And at this time, Famine was nothing but an amalgamation of soul force. Thus, it naturally feared the Magic Cube!

“What a pity. I thought I could twist you to pieces with that strike…”

Lin Ming held the Magic Cube and slowly approached Famine.

The Magic Cube was Lin Ming’s final trump card. From the start, he didn’t use it all in order so that Famine would approach him without raising its guard. Then, he would land a fatal strike on Famine. But Lin Ming never thought that Famine would be so powerful. It had actually managed to survive the attack and only suffer heavy wounds.

A normal soul would have been instantly sliced to nothing by the Magic Cube’s divine light the moment Lin Ming revealed it.

“It really was at least an extreme True Divinity in the past, or perhaps even an existence approaching the Asura Road Master. Even though it was suppressed for 3.6 billion years, it can remain so powerful… if I can control it, then what would it be like when I face the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign?”

As Lin Ming thought this, his eyes turned cold and resolute.

At this time, Famine’s body began to surge and billow outwards. Traces of pain etched themselves on its face. The wounds that the Magic Cube cut on its body began to emit a dense demonic fog, and the arms that were severed started to regrow.

But at the same time, Famine also became paler in color.

It was regenerating its body!

Seeing this, Lin Ming didn’t delay any further. Without speaking he used the strength he obtained after burning his blood essence and threw out the Magic Cube!

He couldn’t give Famine any respite to restore itself!

The Magic Cube shared a connection with Lin Ming. Now, with his current strength, he was able to command it as he pleased!

In that moment, a horrifying soul storm of death swept up around the Magic Cube. The power of this attack was countless times greater than the Ancient Elysium Seal’s attack.

The attack left Famine crazily grasping for breath!

It hadn’t yet repaired its body but now it had to face a life or death crisis!

However, billions of years ago, Famine had traveled through the universe and ravaged wherever it went. Countless supreme powerhouses had died to its hands, and their supreme blood had cast an indefatigable faith in its soul, one that would never concede.

Ho - !

Famine lit up with black flames once more. It was burning all of its source soul force!

Normal martial artists, even spiritas martial artists that were renowned for their potent soul force, would instantly die as soon as they burned their complete source soul force. But Famine was actually able to resist it. This was simply unbelievable.

Even Lin Ming was shocked; did it want to commit suicide?

“Be careful, Famine has swallowed the souls of countless powerhouses and refined them into soul essence that was sealed in its body. Now, what it is burning isn’t its own source soul force but all the soul essence that it has saved. It wants to go all-out against you!”

The Ancient Elysium Seal artifact spirit rapidly explained.

Lin Ming suddenly realized what was occurring. No wonder it was so difficult for Famine to die and it still had such strength after being suppressed for 3.6 billion years. So it had actually swallowed the souls of countless Empyreans, and even True Divinities, and had slowly consumed their soul force over the years. In this case, of course it was able to survive. Even within the Divine Seal Array it was able to endure the passing of time until the Ancient Elysium Seal artifact died of old age, whereupon it could break out of the seal.

Suddenly, an eye split open on Famine’s head. This eye was formed from flesh and blood, and was similar to the eyes on its palms. But, this eye was completely blood red.

This was Famine’s 1001th demon eye. The surface of the eye, the billions of black lines that covered it, everything flashed non-stop with a mystical black light.

The black light contained runes that seethed up and down like grains of sand in a storm.

Although this eye didn’t reveal any abnormality, Lin Ming only looked at it once to feel a strong power. Something strange began to emerge in his heart.

Beams of black light shot out from that strange eye, containing the condensed rhythm of a mystical Dao.

Shua –

The black light was faster than lightning. As the demonic attack tore through the void, although it seemed simple, this actually contained the condensed power of a True Divinity’s soul that Famine had swallowed billions of years ago!

With a rumbling explosion, the black light collided with the Magic Cube and caused a massive energy shockwave to sweep outwards!

The spiritual strength released by the Magic Cube was reversed backwards and it was sent flying away by the soul force condensed from a True Divinity!

But Famine was no better off. Its body shook and it paled even further.

And at this time, Famine simply didn’t care about its wounds. Its 1001st demon eye had turned completely blood red.

Woosh! Woosh! Woosh!

Hundreds and thousands of beams of black light blazed out from Famine’s body. These were the soul forces of the Empyreans that Famine had swallowed billions of years ago. Compared to the soul force of a True Divinity, the soul force of an Empyrean wasn’t much at all. But with hundreds and thousands of these Empyrean soul forces rushing out, it was still an incomparably terrifying force.

These soul forces wrapped the Magic Cube in layers. Famine had desperately used every card in its hands, even taking heavy wounds all in order to wrest away the Magic Cube.

Although it was impossible for Famine to refine the Magic Cube, it could actually use the force field created from the souls of Empyreans to surround it, making it so that Lin Ming wouldn’t be able to control the Magic Cube for some time. With this, it would win.

“You’re over! You can die, and this Stone of Eternal Life is also mine!”

Famine roared. The strange eye on its forehead projected a giant shield that blocked out the skies and covered its body.

In this final moment, it wouldn’t give Lin Ming the chance to use any sneak attacks to turn the tide.

Famine’s body violently shivered. Fierce dragon tentacles rose up around it, whistling in the air. Hundreds and thousands of crimson spears shot out. Burning hot flames blazed, freezing cold ice crackled, yin and yang distorted the air…

The supreme Dao arts of the 33 Heavens began to appear in droves.

“This is the power of the Great Dao that it swallowed!” The pupils of the Ancient Elysium Seal’s artifact spirit shrank as it warned Lin Ming once more.

Famine’s most powerful ability was to swallow. And, the Dao arts it used now came from the supreme powerhouses it defeated in the past. When it swallowed the blood essence and divine souls of those powerhouses, it also swallowed the Laws they grasped. Now, it used everything at its disposal in an attempt to kill off Lin Ming.

This was a terrifying ability, the ability to swallow the strength of others and use it for oneself.

Without hesitation, Lin Ming flew backwards.

The Ancient Elysium Seal came crashing down once more. As for the desperate Famine, it only used a fifth of its Dao arts to send the Ancient Elysium Seal flying away!

The Ancient Elysium Seal violently shook; it had clearly reached its limits.

But at this time, Famine no longer cared about the Ancient Elysium Seal; its target was Lin Ming!

Lin Ming was the one controlling the Magic Cube. It would absolutely not kill the Ancient Elysium Seal and give Lin Ming the chance to recapture the Magic Cube during that time!

Chapter 2005 – Defeating Famine

Ka ka ka!

The Great Dao of the 33 Heavens controlled by Famine shattered the void into pieces!

Lin Ming drew back again and again. Facing the onslaught of the 33 Heavens’ Great Dao, he had been forced back to the edge of the array formation!

However, as Famine planned on killing Lin Ming in a single breath, it suddenly heard a ringing sound from behind.

The Magic Cube’s spiritual connection with Lin Ming had been temporarily severed after being surrounded by the souls of Empyreans. But now, it suddenly erupted with a vast and boundless soul storm!

The power of this soul storm even surpassed the soul storm released by the Magic Cube when Lin Ming controlled it!

Piki paka!

All around the Magic Cube, the force field created by the Empyrean souls began to be twisted apart by the soul storm. It was like countless knives chopping down on a painting, slicing it to pieces!

“What!?”

Famine didn’t turn around to look, but still had absolute clarity of what was occurring behind it.

The Magic Cube that should have been temporarily cut off from Lin Ming had suddenly started to go berserk, and was actually attacking Famine!

How was this possible?

Before Famine could figure out what was occurring, a red fluctuation of energy appeared around the Magic Cube.

This energy fluctuation condensed into the phantom of a cute, red-clothed little girl. Her cheeks were ruddy and her eyes were bright, the definition of childish innocence.

This little girl was Ruby. In terms of strength, she couldn’t compare with Lin Ming at all. But it was more accurate to say that she was a condensed form of the Laws; it was simply impossible for her to manipulate the energy that existed in the universe.

But in the Magic Cube, Ruby had become a fish in water. This was because she was a being evolved from the Magic Cube. Although she was not a true artifact spirit, she could be considered a quasi-artifact spirit.

She could manipulate the Magic Cube to a great extent. In terms of control, she was far more skilled than Lin Ming!

As Ruby looked towards the fierce and dreadful Famine, her large black eyes shined with decisiveness.

Without hesitation, Ruby struck out. A vast sea of source soul force burst out from her. Bright red light shined and wrapped around the Magic Cube.

The Magic Cube shot out like a bolt of lightning. As it flew, divine light rose, becoming brighter. The originally gray light fused with a blood red, becoming blindingly dazzling like a star shining in the skies.

“Damnit!”

Famine was incensed. If it continued to attack Lin Ming then it would be struck from behind by the Magic Cube. In a situation where it had already shot out all the True Divinity and Empyrean soul force within its body, if it were to take such an attack it would definitely die!

Famine didn’t want to die. All it could do was reverse its strength just before it struck Lin Ming, and transfer 60% of the 33 Heavens Dao arts to roar towards Ruby instead.

But at the same time, the rest of the 33 Heavens Dao arts continued to attack Lin Ming!

It didn’t give up on attacking Lin Ming. This was because it was well aware that if it freely allowed Lin Ming to do what he wanted, then he would join together with that mysterious little girl and it would die even more miserably.

It instantly made a decision to split its attacks. In a situation with both parties wounded, this was the best method it could think of to obtain victory.

However, at this time, a corner of Lin Ming’s lips pulled in a taunting sneer. A sound transmission immediately passed to Famine’s mind –

“A smart decision, but it’s only you who thinks it is smart!”

Whorl whorl whorl –

Lin Ming’s swirled his hands. Behind him, a primal chaos diagram appeared. But this primal chaos diagram wasn’t composed of the power of yin and yang, but of the power of divinity and the power of demons.

As the diagram appeared, the will of a horrifying Heavenly Dao recklessly blazed out, welcoming the attacks of Famine’s 33 Heavens Dao arts.

Bang!

A fierce explosion rang out. Lin Ming was sent flying backwards. As for Famine, it was also affected by this energy explosion. Its body violently trembled and blurred!

The power of demons!? How was this possible!?

Panic and horror began to dawn in Famine’s eyes. It simply couldn’t imagine how a human like Lin Ming was able to control the power of demons!

Moreover, Lin Ming’s strength was far too terrifying. A mere half-step Empyrean was able to withstand its attacks with nothing more than minor wounds.

But at this time, an even more horrifying attack arrived.

This attack came from behind Famine; it was Ruby’s strike!

Ruby sat cross-legged behind the Magic Cube. Her two small hands were pressed together and an endless black hole appeared between her palms. Within this black hole, the Magic Cube revolved, as if it were capable of swallowing all strengths in the world.

Hum –

Hum –

Hum –

Waves of condensed soul storm essence blasted out in circles, colliding with Famine’s demon force field.

The demon force field was only able to resist for a blink of an eye before it shattered to pieces!

The soul storm swept out. Wherever it went, blood spears would break, glaciers would melt, flames would extinguish, shields would erode… everything that Famine displayed, all the supreme arts of the 33 heavens, all of it was crushed like bugs beneath the suppression of the Magic Cube.

“Ahh!”

Famine cried out in pain. It had underestimated Lin Ming’s strength. Lin Ming’s resistance had caused it to suffer a backlash, and now it was unable to face the Magic Cube’s attack!

The result had been decided!

Kacha!

The Magic Cube’s soul storm started to grind away the final force field defense summoned by Famine. The blood dragons behind famine as well as its thousand arms were all annihilated in the terrifying storm, and even the force field started to disintegrate.

Famine emitted another heart-wrenching scream. It had already used up all the True Divinity and Empyrean soul force it had held in its body. Now, it had to rely on its soul force alone to resist this attack. The Magic Cube controlled by Ruby was like a butcher’s knife cutting down on its body. Each time the soul storm revolved, it recklessly swallowed up Famine’s life!

If this continued then it would be utterly obliterated in just several breaths of time!

“Ruby, slow down!”

Within that dreadful soul storm, Lin Ming suddenly shouted out.

Ruby had always listened to Lin Ming. She immediately reduced the strength she used. In that moment, Famine gained a brief moment of respite to avoid the fate of being turned to ashes.

It didn’t know why Lin Ming had told Ruby to stay her hand at this moment, but to it, this was undoubtedly a glorious celebration. It could seize this chance to survive.

“Don’t kill me! I am willing to surrender to you!”

Famine shouted out loud. It had decided that Lin Ming had some plan to use it. If it could make use of Lin Ming’s greed, then there would be a chance to swallow Lin Ming and obtain the Magic Cube!

Famine’s heart was filled with hope. But, Lin Ming didn’t answer it at all. He flew up and caught the Magic Cube.

“Ruby, help me.”

Ruby nodded. She placed her two hands atop the Magic Cube and combined as one with Lin Ming’s soul force.

Famine looked at Lin Ming with a hint of trepidation. But at the same time, its words were filled with beguiling temptation.

“Young man, from of any race in the 33 Heavens, you are the most terrifying genius I have ever seen. In the future you will absolutely become the ruler of the universe! You have already proven your strength. As long as you let me live then I am willng to help you. I can be your servant, and if you don’t believe me then you can leave a slave seal within me. I can even sign a contract with you! My strength and experience will bring you unimaginable benefits! With me by your side, no one will be your match. I can even gather a massive number of abyssals to support you. The entire 33 Heavens can be yours!”

Famine passionately spoke. It was confident in its ability to mislead and tempt the hearts of men. It knew how these intelligent life forms were greedy and it also knew that anyone with ambition would be lured by its words. As for peerless geniuses, which one didn’t have ambitions? Otherwise they would have never reached this step.

Famine believed it had found the turning point it needed to survive.

But, it never thought that Lin Ming would completely ignore its words, as if he never heard them. In fact, Lin Ming never even glanced towards its passionate and fervent performance.

Lin Ming only helped Ruby position her hands, then he placed his own hands atop hers, wrapping the Magic Cube with two layers.

Then he casually said, “Ruby, you and I will join forces to erase Famine’s spirit mark. But, don’t injure the main form of its soul. I still have a use for it!”

These words were a blow to the head. They immediately cracked open Famine’s courage!

“Mm!” Ruby nodded. Above her red and round cheeks, her large and watery eyes closely stared at Famine as she aimed the Magic Cube. She was already ready to strike Famine. As for what Lin Ming wanted to do, she didn’t ask nor did she care.

In short, as long as Lin Ming wanted to erase this ugly monster’s spirit mark, she would be more than glad to help.

“You! You want to erase my spirit mark!?”

Famine crazily roared. The only remaining demon eye on its forehead nearly cracked open and bled. It finally realized why Lin Ming had released its seal and why he didn’t turn it to ash in the final moment. This was because from the very start, this cruel and abnormal human had planned to erase his spirit mark and swallow its soul for his own use!

To die only meant turning to ash and fading away. But to have its spirit mark erased meant that it would lose itself; this was a fate worse than death. And after its spirit mark was erased, it would then be swallowed and used as a gift to its enemies to enhance their strength. This was definitely ten times worse than simply being killed off!

Then, Famine suddenly thought of the Stone of Eternal Life! If Lin Ming used the Stone of Eternal Life, there really was a chance he could accomplish all this!

“You will die like a dog!”

Famine cursed. But then, Lin Ming finally looked at Famine. His eyes were filled with disgust and disdain.

“What a pity. If you really did your best and attacked me with all of your 33 Heavens Dao arts, then even if I didn’t die you would still have been able to heavily wound me, and even injure my source soul force, making it so that I wouldn’t be able to recover for at least several hundred years. As for you, although you wouldn’t have been able to escape, you would have exploded into nothingness and have saved yourself from a destiny of being enslaved forever, so that I would never have obtained any advantages. But instead, you are now paying a deep price for your actions.

“You are far too greedy. In a severely wounded state, you still wished to kill me and obtain the Magic Cube. Your natural character is to swallow so you are doomed to be greedy, but, your greed has doomed you to be made a gift to me!”

As Lin Ming spoke, the Magic Cube emitted rays of black light that wrapped around all of Famine’s severed arms.

And after that, with a thought, Lin Ming caused a beam of black light to puncture Famine’s central eye, causing it to lose all sight.

By this time, Famine no longer had any ability to resist.

Chapter 2006 – Imprison

Ruby was focused. With her two small hands together, she held the Magic Cube floating in the void. Lin Ming’s hands covered hers as he poured his soul force into the Magic Cube.

Before having Ruby’s help, he had never felt his own spiritual sea so closely connected to the Magic Cube. This sort of feeling was like the Magic Cube was a part of his body and he could control it as he wished.

Woosh!

A ray of black light thrust into Famine, drilling through its forehead and hitting its spiritual sea!

“Ahh!”

Famine cried out in pain and sorrow. The sound was like a person screaming with a throat full of glass, harsh to the extreme.

Its body started to rattle and pop, as if something were cracking apart!

Lin Ming was cold and resolute. In the final moments he absolutely could not allow Famine any chance to self-implode, otherwise he would lose everything.

With a thought, the array lines that wrapped around Famine like burning magma suddenly drilled into its soul form, burning it away, eroding its will.

Famine wildly struggled. But, all of its strength was in utter chaos and it was unable to gather any. At the same time, its spirit mark was being grinded away and its consciousness became increasingly blurry.

It was a being that had existed for billions upon billions of years. It never imagined that it would experience such a scene one day!

Even when Empyrean Divine Seal locked away its soul, it had never been so afraid.

This was surely the most terrifying way to die!

It was no longer able to move its body nor could it speak any words with its mouth. Even its ability to think was frozen. These short several breaths of time seemed as long as a hundred million years, and the pain it experienced during this time seemed far greater than the sum total of pain it had gone through in the last 3.6 billion years!

“It’s over.”

Lin Ming’s tone held no emotion. The Magic Cube emitted another black ray of light that penetrated into Famine’s spiritual sea like an earth-breaking drill.

Peng!

Famine’s spirit mark blew apart at this moment, dissipating to nothingness…

In the next moment, the Magic Cube whipped up a black soul vortex that swallowed Famine’s now masterless soul.

“Done!”

Lin Ming let out a long breath of air. He had used up a considerable amount of energy in this battle, and it wasn’t just from using his source soul force or burning the Asura blood essence, but because the pressure he shouldered from starting this battle.

At this time behind Lin Ming, the Ancient Elysium Seal artifact spirit that had watched the battle unfold was already left at a loss for words. The artifact spirit had basically played little to no role in the battle. Lin Ming, along with the Magic Cube and the mysterious little girl, the three of them had joined together to subdue Famine’s soul.

Moreover, Lin Ming’s crazy plan had left the artifact spirit gasping in awe and shock. This junior actually planned on erasing Famine’s spirit mark and then absorbing its soul.

“Junior, you want to absorb Famine’s soul? You should know that even if Famine’s spirit mark is erased, it will still be immeasurably dangerous for you to swallow it. This is because even if that soul no longer has a master, it still retains its instinct to resist and swallow.”

What the artifact spirit said was correct. When Lin Ming obtained the Magic Cube in the past, just absorbing a soul fragment the size of a grain of rice had nearly caused his spiritual sea to fall to illusion. The dangers of swallowing a masterless soul was similarly high.

What lay before Lin Ming was the soul of an existence that had once been an extreme True Divinity. Although it was severely weakened, it was still the complete soul of Famine. Wanting to swallow it wouldn’t be easy at all.

Lin Ming said, “Junior has no plan to do so for now. Famine has likely lived for around 5 billion years, or even longer… the memories within its soul are too great, and for someone like me with only several thousand years of life to absorb it is the same as an ant wanting to swallow an elephant. For an ant to swallow an elephant, that isn’t realistic at all. With the capacity of my spiritual sea, it is impossible for me to absorb so many memories. I only need to imprison Famine’s soul and use it as I need.”

With a masterless soul that had its spirit mark erased, and in addition to the suppression of the Magic Cube, there shouldn’t be any problems with doing this.

“That… is also good!” The Ancient Elysium Seal artifact spirit let out a sigh of relief. There was a bit more insurance with this.

At this time, Lin Ming had already sat down in meditation. He ate some soul recovery pills and used two hours to adjust himself back to his peak state. Then, he took out the Magic Cube and drew out Famine’s soul.

At this time, Famine’s soul had already condensed into a pitch black sphere of light.

Without thinking, Lin Ming plunged this sphere of light between his eyebrows, submerging it in his spiritual sea.

Bang!

Within Lin Ming’s spiritual sea, roiling waves immediately rose up!

Famine’s soul was too strong. It was far more formidable than Lin Ming’s soul.

At this time, the scene of Lin Ming’s spiritual sea trying to accommodate Famine’s soul was like a small sea suddenly having a giant planet fall into it!

Tsunamis rose up, the entire sea began to tumble.

Lin Ming paled. He grabbed the Magic Cube and also pressed it in between his eyebrows.

Ka ka ka ka!

In that instant, the massive Magic Cube came pressing down in the skies above Lin Ming’s spiritual sea. Black energy shot out, and as this black energy shrouded down, the raging soul suddenly became a mouse that saw a cat; it immediately calmed down.

Famine’s soul was just far too formidable. Wanting to refine it would be an arduously difficult process.

Lin Ming used his will to form spiritual ropes.

Whoosh whoosh whoosh!

These spiritual ropes shot out from Lin Ming’s spiritual sea like water snakes. They flowed across the sea, wrapping the massive sphere of light in numerous layers.

The spiritual ropes crawled over Famine. Sharp steel needles dug into Famine’s soul like knives, penetrating deeper into it.

Rope after rope of spiritual strength appeared. More and more chains rose up in Lin Ming’s spiritual sea, imprisoning Famine’s soul in innumerable layers. As these iron chains tightened and pulled down, Famine’s soul finally sank into Lin Ming’s spiritual sea until it was fully submerged.

For a time, an indescribably powerful soul force surged up along the spiritual ropes and into Lin Ming’s spiritual sea. This feeling numbed Lin Ming’s entire body, paralyzing him like he had been struck by lightning.

Lin Ming’s spiritual sea was absorbing Famine’s soul force through these ropes. From afar, they looked like leeches sucking blood.

If this continued, then slowly, Famine’s soul would be completely absorbed into Lin Ming’s spiritual sea. The capacity and intensity of Lin Ming’s spiritual sea would also be enhanced by a terrifying degree.

This was just like a sea that suddenly had a planet-sized amount of water thrust into it. The depth and width of this sea would be incomparable to the past!

Moreover, doing things this way had another benefit; this was that Lin Ming could preserve Famine’s soul to the highest degree. With this, he would have an even greater advantage when he fought with Famine’s mortal body later.

After completely imprisoning Famine’s soul, Lin Ming’s eyes opened.

At this time, Ruby was also standing behind Lin Ming. Her two hands were placed along Lin Ming’s temples, helping him control the Magic Cube in his spiritual sea.

The reason Lin Ming was able to smoothly absorb Famine’s soul was all thanks to the suppression of the Magic Cube. And Ruby had played a great role in accomplishing this.

Lin Ming saw that Ruby’s forehead was already wet with sweat, and her bangs had also pasted themselves onto her face. A warm feeling surged in his heart.

“Thank you, Ruby.”

Lin Ming patted Ruby’s head. Ruby shyly smiled. She was happy that she could help Lin Ming in some manner.

When Lin Ming just absorbed Famine’s soul, not too much time had passed in his spiritual sea. But in reality, two days and two nights had passed. During this time, the Ancient Elysium Seal artifact spirit had been closely watching over Lin Ming.

As the old artifact spirit looked at Lin Ming, it finally understood what others meant when they said ‘the young will surpass the old’.

Famine’s soul had truly been subdued. Who would have imagined that when this youth returned to visit, not only would he help solve a great problem that had been weighing down on the artifact spirit’s mind for all this time, but he would also imprison and refine the soul of Famine to use for himself?

Lin Ming had used 6000 some years to grow to such a degree. If he were given another 6000 years, what would he be like then?

The artifact spirit sighed with emotion. Then, it seemed to recall something. Its eyes passed over Lin Ming and looked at Ruby.

Feeling the gaze of the Ancient Elysium Seal artifact spirit, the somewhat shy and timid Ruby couldn’t help but grab onto the hem of Lin Ming’s robe.

Such a timid Ruby, it made it hard for others to imagine that she had calmly and coldly controlled the Magic Cube to severely wound Famine.

“Is she… the Stone of Eternal Life’s artifact spirit?”

The Ancient Elysium Seal asked with incredulity. Existences on the level of the three divine tools already surpassed the universe, and it was difficult for them to form artifact spirits. If they did produce an artifact spirit then those artifact spirits would be destined to be incredibly powerful existences capable of destroying the heavens and earth. But, this little girl was clearly not such an example.

Lin Ming held onto Ruby’s cold and small hand, hinting for her not to be nervous. He smiled and said, “Senior might believe that, but to be more accurate, Ruby is a special life form condensed from the Laws of the Magic Cube and combined with the will, energy, and blood vitality of a peerless powerhouse, as well as mixed in with all sorts of other information. When junior first came here, I brought a little girl called Fishy with me, and she was also a similar existence. She could have been a life form condensed from the Purple Card and related to the Asura Road Master.”

“Fishy… Purple Card… Asura Road Master…”

The Ancient Elysium Seal artifact spirit lost itself in thought. “So it was that little girl… I remember her… when Empyrean Divine Seal laid down the Divine Seal Array, he seemed to have collected a set of something. So, he left the Divine Realm to go to the Asura Road in order to find his own unrivalled lucky chance… and when he returned, he truly did bring a little girl back with him. But by that time, I was already guarding the Divine Seal Array.

“Unfortunately, Empyrean Divine Seal didn’t have a chance to develop the inheritance he obtained. When he sealed away Famine’s soul he had to burn away his life. As for me, that was when my mission began. I have been suppressing this seal for 3.6 billion years since then…”

Hearing the Ancient Elysium Seal artifact spirit’s words, Lin Ming felt a deep awe and respect towards it. To guard this land alone for 3.6 billion years, just how much loneliness did it have to endure? How many tribulations did it have to cross?

It had likely fought with Famine’s soul countless times, using up its life as it marched forwards with its mission.

It was like a torch that had been lit in ages past, set in an unknown corner where it continued to illuminate the future of the human race.

Realizing this, Lin Ming respectfully bowed towards the artifact spirit.

The old artifact spirit smiled. “The one bowing should be me. If it weren’t for you, I would have been destined to waste away until Famine killed me. Now, I have been freed. Although my life is ruined, being able to live for another hundred million years or so shouldn’t be a problem. Of course, that’s on the premise that I don’t die somehow.”

The life of an artifact spirit was much longer than the life of a human. They were comparable to the temple spirit race.

Lin Ming cupped his fists together. “Senior… junior plans to return to the gathering place of humanity after a little more time – the wild universe. I want to ask… does Senior have any plans?”

“Wild universe?” The artifact spirit repeated, surprised.

Lin Ming retold the story of humanity’s evacuation from the Divine Realm. The more the artifact spirit heard, the more shocked it was. The last time Lin Ming was here, it had guessed that Lin Ming might be able to save the world because he was in possession of the Magic Cube. But, it had never imagined that over 6000 years ago when Lin Ming had only been at the Holy Lord realm, he had been able to have such a terrifying influence on the great war between humanity and the saints.

Escaping to the wild universe could be said to only have been possible because of Lin Ming. Lin Ming could truly be called the child of fate!

“I’m just an old bag of bones. If I still have any use left, then it’s time to show the world I can still burn!” As the artifact spirit spoke, Lin Ming smiled with understanding. He knew that the Ancient Elysium Seal had already decided to go to the wild universe with him and challenge the saints!

His journey would begin from here on out!

Chapter 2008 – Spear

Within the Divine Realm, Soul World, or universes that the saints resided in, one could often see giant mainlands floating in the vast nothingness of space. These mainlands weren’t like bare wooden planks, but were surrounded but layers upon layers of infinite nebulous space. From the outside, they often had the shape of ellipsoid domes, like unbelievably large eggs.

As for the nebulas surrounding these central mainlands, there were innumerable planets that dwelled within, most of them even larger than the Sky Spill Planet. From this, it could be seen just how vast the area of these mainlands was.

The Divine Realm’s 3000 great worlds each had at least one such central mainland. And, without a doubt, each one of these central mainlands was the liveliest place of the entire great world. For instance, Immemorial Imperial City was situated in the central mainland of the True Martial Great World.

But in the wild universe, one rarely saw such vast central mainlands. Instead, what replaced them were galaxies.

These galaxies were giant beyond compare. Their arms were rivers of stars that extended for quintillions of miles.

Within these galaxies, there were millions and billions and trillions of planets. The breadth of space they occupied was beyond description.

According to the information gathered by the saints, the galaxies in the wild universe were originally the ‘central mainlands’ of this universe. But, billions of years ago these central mainlands were destroyed by some exceedingly dreadful strength and had completely imploded. The fragments of these mainlands had drifted away, spreading out far and wide, but remained revolving and spinning around each other through the strange interaction of gravity and other mystical forces, thus forming these galaxies.

And at this time, the Blue Horn Galaxy that the saint martial artists headed towards was one such galaxy.

Within his inner world, Lin Ming had hypnotized the unlucky saint race martial artist to obtain all this information. Upon learning it, even he was shocked.

If the information gathered by the saints was true, then just who was it that destroyed the central mainlands of the wild universe?

Such a giant land that was countless trillions of times larger than Sky Spill Planet was actually destroyed like this…

This level of destruction surpassed Lin Ming’s imagination. Let alone an extreme True Divinity, would even the Asura Road Master have such capabilities?

Lin Ming couldn’t confirm whether or not the Asura Road Master could really achieve something like this. But, Lin Ming intuitively felt that the destruction of these mainlands involved the great calamity that occurred 10 billion years ago.

In the past, the intelligent races lived throughout the 33 universes, and each universe had its own brilliant and glorious martial arts civilization. However, after that one great war, the intelligent races only occupied 16 universes.

As for the other half of the universes, they had become wildernesses. Was the reason the population fell so drastically in the past related to the destruction of these central mainlands?

If so, if one had to compare the war between humanity and the saints to what occurred in the past, then it simply wasn’t anything at all.

After all, the saints would be unable to exterminate an entire race in such a short period of time.

“The great calamity of 10 billion years past…” Lin Ming mumbled. It was only after those events that humans, saints, and spiritas had been able to develop. Just who was it that was able to serve as opponents to the all-powerful god race of 10 billion years ago?

Could it have been the abyssal demons?

And just what sort of world was the Dark Abyss that the abyssals resided in? What secrets were held within?

Lin Ming didn’t know these matters and neither did the Ancient Elysium Seal artifact spirit. Perhaps only the two old men that guarded the final trial would know. But when Lin Ming asked them before, their reply was that he would find out the truth when he was able to control his own destiny and become a player instead of a chess piece. Otherwise, it was likely he would draw some disaster onto himself if he were to know these secrets.

By this time, Lin Ming had gone with the forces of the saints and long since departed the entrance to the wild universe. The ships leapt towards Blue Horn Galaxy, again and again.

According to gathered intelligence, humanity had an influence that was hidden within Blue Horn Galaxy.

When the wild universe’s central mainlands were destroyed, it had caused terrifying space storms and eruptions that swept out for quintillions of miles, forming a chaotic space where these dangers still existed. There were distortion force fields, black holes, wormholes, and all other confusing space environments. To hide in this galaxy would be far too easy.

It was exceedingly difficult for a martial artist’s sense to penetrate into these spaces. Even a True Divinity powerhouse would have to spend an inordinate amount of time and energy to search these galaxies.

And there were far, far too many galaxies within the wild universe. It was impossible for the True Divinities of the saint race to search all these galaxies one by one, thus humanity was given more time to breathe and recuperate.

When this fleet of ships reached the midpoint of the wild universe’s entrance and the Blue Horn Galaxy, Lin Ming stood up and walked outside the spirit ship.

Several days ago, Lin Ming had obtained information from the mouth of that unlucky saint race martial artist. But, this information was far from satisfactory. He needed more detailed intelligence so that he could better determine the location of Xiao Moxian, Divine Dream, and the others.

As for an exact position, Lin Ming didn’t have any hopes of finding out. If Xiao Moxian and Divine Dream were really discovered by the saints, then it was possible that the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign would personally arrive.

And to obtain this information, there was a shortcut – that was to grab hold of someone even stronger.

Outside, Lin Ming’s divine sense instantly spread outwards, covering the entire fleet.

……………

One day later, after another spatial great void shift, a skinny old man was sitting in a chair within a chamber in the fleet’s flagship, staring at a pile of scarlet flesh and blood, his eyes in a daze.

This chamber resembled the workshop of an alchemist. There was a large pill furnace, as well as tables that were covered with pill bottles and other precious medicinal herbs.

At a corner of one these tables, there was a medicinal cauldron that was still boiling and emitting green bubbles. The medicinal soup inside seemed as if it would boil over due to the heat.

But, the old man didn’t care about any of this at all. Rather, he stared at the pile of red flesh and blood in front of him. His appearance was wizened and decrepit and he was skinny like a monkey. He wore a dark green robe that fell flat all over his body, making him seem increasingly old and rickety.

“The flesh and blood of Famine; it is indeed marvelous.”

The old man spoke to himself. His filthy eyes were brilliant as they stared at the mass of flesh and blood. He couldn’t help but open a jade box, and then take out a fist-sized mass of red meat from it.

This mass of meat had been preserved using special methods in order to guarantee absolute freshness. After taking it out, it gently trembled, pulsating with blood.

This was a heart, a human heart.

The old man took out this heart that he had personally taken from a human World King and brought it towards that mass of Famine’s flesh and blood. In the blink of an eye, that unmoving mass of Famine’s flesh and blood suddenly wriggled and shot out like a shark, wrapping around this heart.

Hualala - !

Famine’s flesh and blood fiercely wriggled. A moment later, it had completely swallowed that heart, turning it into a part of itself!

The skinny old man calmly released his sense and pondered for a moment. Then, his filthy eyes flashed with a miraculous light. “To swallow the heart of a human World King and turn it all into its own nutrients, this has clearly strengthened Famine’s flesh and blood. If I were to fuse with it and then continue to swallow others, then even though my life is nearing its twilight, I would still be able to extend my lifespan for tens of millions more years, and maybe even break into the middle Empyrean realm in the future.

“Although if that happens, I will become a monster that relies on swallowing others to live. But, this isn’t important. The crucial point is that after fusing with Famine’s flesh and blood, I will become a servant absolutely loyal to the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. Such a price is far too heavy… The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign granted me Famine’s flesh and blood and he wouldn’t have done so for nothing. He will surely keep something hidden within me…”

All of these thoughts instantly flashed through the skinny old man’s mind. However, the temptation of living for several tens of millions of years was something he couldn’t erase from his mind. He hesitated for a moment and then shouted to the outside, “Come in!”

A moment later, the door opened and a meek and handsome youth entered the chamber.

“Go the human prison camp and bring out six pairs of men and women. They need to be 18 years of age or younger and have decent talents.”

The skinny old man wanted to verify just how much life essence the flesh and blood of Famine would give him after swallowing someone else. He wanted to know just how much he could delay his aging.

But at this time, he felt that something was off.

“What are you still dawdling about for, how come you haven’t left…”

The skinny old man suddenly looked up, his sharp eagle-like eyes looking towards this youth. But at the moment he looked up, the youth had moved.

His speed was like ghosts and gods. A black spear appeared in his hand, thrusting straight towards the old man’s throat!

This spear was far too fast, fast to the point that even the skinny old man found it difficult to follow!

However, he was still an Empyrean powerhouse. In this critical life or death moment, terrifying black flames erupted from within his body. These were vital life flames he had cultivated within himself through his years of being an alchemist, and it also served as his best trump card.

The moment these flames appeared, the entire chamber that was boosted by array formations instantly melted to molten metal. Everything within the chamber, besides the pill furnace and Famine’s flesh and blood, instantly disintegrated to ash!

The damage had been minimized in breadth because the flames were highly condensed. Otherwise, the entire spirit ship would have exploded.

But as these black flames swirled about and started to take the shape of a growling dragon, a black spear suddenly pierced through that flame dragon!

Peng!

Black flames burst apart. The skinny old man’s protective astral essence exploded like glass. With utter disbelief in his eyes, the spear had pierced his heart.

With a twist of the spear, the skinny old man’s body shook. All of his meridians were shattered by an overbearingly tyrannical strength!

“You…” The skinny old man vomited a mouthful of blood. But, the youth didn’t say a word. Instead, the youth formed seals with his fingers, shooting out mysterious Asura Law runes that bound the skinny old man in layers upon layers, sealing away all the energy in his body!

This youth was Lin Ming.

Lin Ming looked at the skinny old man with no trace of mercy in his eyes.

The skinny old man’s meridians had been wasted and his heart and been pierced. With the energy being locked within, the old man was now nothing more than a walking bag of ruined meat. But, because he was a saint Empyrean that had tempered his body, he would still be able to maintain a few years of life in this state.

Lin Ming didn’t kill him because he had other uses for the old man in mind.

The skinny old man could no longer speak. His eyes were blood red, so wide that they nearly popped out of his head. He looked at Lin Ming with hatred.

But at the same time, he was also dumbfounded. Who was this youth and just why was his strength so great!? Was he the human race’s Emperor Shakya?

Chapter 2010 – Blue Horn Galaxy

The 33 Heavenly Daos.

Within them, two of the Great Daos were suitable for humanity to train in.

First was the body transformation system’s Nine Stars of the Dao Palace.

Second was the essence gathering system’s Nine Divine Shifts.

3.6 billion years ago, Famine swallowed humanity’s Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, an event equal to severing one of humanity’s arms. And this time, Famine would swallow the Nine Divine Shifts, humanity’s essence gathering system.

This was the same as sentencing humanity to death!

If Famine were to swallow humanity’s essence gathering system, then would the human martial artists who controlled the power of it lose their strength?

Lin Ming recalled the time he broke into the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace. In Bai Qi’s tomb he had been blocked by a dao diagram of the Heavenly Dao. It was only after crushing through this Heavenly Dao dao diagram that he was able to step into the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace.

Moreover, he was able to freely use the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace up to the present.

This meant that the 33 Heavenly Daos could never truly vanish. Rather, for some unknown reason, they were sealed away.

If Famine swallowed humanity’s essence gathering system, then the likely result was that the human martial artists who had cultivated the essence gathering system wouldn’t have any change to their original strength.

But for martial artists that had yet to reach that point, they would suffer arduous difficulties one after another during their future cultivation. When they tried to make a breakthrough, they would likely encounter the same Heavenly Dao dao diagram that had hindered Lin Ming.

At the same time, if other masters wanted to take a step further, for instance if Emperor Shakya wished to break into the realm of True Divinity or if Lin Ming wanted to break into the Empyrean realm, it might be even more difficult!

This sort of feeling was as if Famine was swallowing the causal relationship, the karmic ties that bound humanity together with the 33 Heavenly Daos. This was the same as swallowing the great destiny of an entire race.

Then, humanity would be abandoned by the Heavenly Dao!

After realizing this, Lin Ming’s mind shook!

Since the beginning of time, there had been no race that could stand atop the river of history for eternity. They would decline for all sorts of reasons.

For instance, the primal god race or the celestial race, they were slowly declining due to their inability to reproduce.

Many primal god race powerhouses would have hundreds or even thousands of wives, yet, they never managed to leave behind a single descendant. Like this, they could only look helplessly on as the primal god race declined in number until they finally withered away to nothing.

If so, then was it possible that there was some abyssal similar to Famine that had swallowed or reversed the destinies of the primal god race and celestial race? So that these races which once stood at the peak of the era 10 billion years ago slowly lost their ability to reproduce until they finally perished?

Lin Ming felt more and more that this was a likely possibility.

This abyssal likely feared the primal god race and wished to erase the entire race from existence!

And humanity seemed to be stepping onto the same road that the primal god race traversed in the past. If the two roads of the essence gathering system’s Nine Divine Shifts and the body transformation system’s Nine Stars of the Dao Palace were to be suffocated and sealed away, then all that remained for humanity would be their prodigious ability to reproduce.

But if so, how would they be any different from common farm animals?

If the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign were to succeed then humanity would be frozen where they were, forever unable to raise their heads high. And the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign would also be able to rid himself of all future troubles.

Lin Ming felt increasingly pressed for time.

However, the only thing worth rejoicing for from this matter was that swallowing the 33 Heavenly Daos would require an immense amount of Famine’s strength as well as a considerable period of time. During this period of time, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign would need to go into seclusion.

This was also Lin Ming’s chance.

Without the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, the saints were like a tiger without its fangs.

As these thoughts flashed through Lin Ming’s mind he continued to sift through Timebright’s memories. Soon, he found a great deal of additional valuable information.

This was information concerning Famine.

During these past years, Famine had swallowed an uncountable amount of resources and had already grown itself its own giant avatar. This avatar was now under the control of the Good Fortune Saint Son.

Meanwhile, Famine had bred a great deal of flesh and blood essence similar to the demon relic. This flesh and blood essence was divvied off to some Holy Lords and World Kings. After swallowing it they would gain the ability to undergo a new body metamorphosis, thus establishing the Legion of Famine.

The Legion of Famine naturally followed the orders of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. But with the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign in seclusion, the Legion of Famine was now under the command of the five saint generals.

Lin Ming had once heard the names of the five saint generals during the second time he joined the Asura Road’s final trial. At the time, they were called the four saint marvels.

They were the Good Fortune Saint Son of the Good Fortune Saint Palace, Soaring Feather God King’s disciple Fairy Blue Lotus of Soaring Feather God Mountain, as well as Astral Vault God King’s two great direct disciples, Highsun and Darkmoon.

But in truth, Highsun and Darkmoon had ordinary level of talents. In the past they were able to rely on their superiority of age and rise into the Empyrean realm a step earlier, thus standing on par with the Good Fortune Saint Son and Fairy Blue Lotus.

Now, the Good Fortune Saint Son and Fairy Blue Lotus had both stepped into the Empyrean realm; Highsun and Darkmoon were placed in a precarious position.

However, before they could sit steady in their positions as third and fourth ranked amongst the five saint generals, their positions became shaky once more.

The youth that was originally ranked in fifth place was already starting to catch up; he was Imperial Prince Xishen who was in the limelight at the Good Fortune Saint Palace.

This Imperial Prince Xishen even seemed to have talent beyond that of the Good Fortune Saint Son.

His cultivation was at the half-step Empyrean realm, but in terms of combat strength, he could already defeat many saint Empyreans of the older generation.

Of the five saint generals, the Good Fortune Saint Son and Fairy Blue Lotus served as the leads, and as a group, they each neared the strongest force within the saint race. They were the great enemies of humanity, and through these years countless human martial artists had died beneath their hands.

While there was much bad news, there was also some good news worth being thankful for; that was that news concerning Xiao Moxian, Mu Qianyu, Qin Xingxuan, and the others was all completely unknown to Timebright. This also meant that they were alive but their hidden locations were still unknown.

In order to find the position of the human enclaves, the saints had already started to train their own spies.

These spies mainly came from the human captives.

Even when a race was nearing the point of extinction, not everyone would be willing to sacrifice their own life for their race. Beneath torture and the threat of death, there would always be some people willing to betray their race, signing a contract and becoming a spy.

In addition, there were also some humans that were forcefully controlled by the saints, confused with illusions, or even had slave seals planted in their bodies. These people were sent to the wild universe in droves where they were used to seek out the location of the humans.

Using this method, the saints had already completely annihilated several human bases.

This information all crossed through Lin Ming’s mind.

Lin Ming now had an extremely detailed grasp of the situation between the saints and humans.

At this time, the fleet arrived at the Blue Horn Galaxy.

Lin Ming looked outside the porthole and gazed upon the giant blue galaxy that swirled before him. The stars hidden in the ethereal nebula numbered in the billions and trillions.

The Blue Horn Galaxy seemed beautiful, but hidden within it were countless chaotic spaces, black holes, wormholes, space-time storms, and all sorts other dangers.

In truth, this was the skeleton of a great world’s central mainland, and Lin Ming also intended to fill this graveyard with some more skeletons.

He had already formulated a plan to fight the saints.

This plan was a bit crazy and was bound to set off a massive storm. Before the saints could react, he had to strike with all he had!

Chapter 2012 – The Burden of a Leader

Through over 6000 years, Xiao Moxian had already forgotten how many times she had touched the Thousand Mile Heartlink or had tried to use it to contact Lin Ming.

And now, the Thousand mile Heartlink’s sealed divine runic symbol was near the point of collapse and yet there still wasn’t any news of Lin Ming.

After gently stroking this necklace that had lost its luster, Xiao Moxian’s thoughts and mood began to waver up and down. If she were to use this necklace but a single time more, than after a short period of use the divine runic symbol sealed away in the necklace would shatter into nothing. As for this divine runic symbol, besides Lin Ming there likely wasn’t anyone in the 33 Heavens capable of drawing it up again…

After countless attempts failed, all she had was a single chance. With just a single chance, how could she possibly reach him…?

Xiao Moxian let out a deep sigh. At this time, she heard a sound come from outside the room, followed by fast and chaotic footsteps.

A group of people had arrived. Xiao Moxian put away her necklace and hid away the sorrow that etched her face.

A group of 7-8 people had come. Each one of them was the backbone of Demon Fairy Celestial Palace. The black-clothed man standing at their head was Xiao Moxian’s son – Lin Huang.

Ever since New Ming Planet stood at peak of the perilous storm, Lin Huang had ended his adventure to temper himself and had returned to Xiao Moxian’s side. This was the only thing that made Xiao Moxian feel a bit more at ease.

“Your child greets mother!” A war armored Lin Huang quickly strode into the room and bowed. The others following behind him, the core of Demon Fairy Celestial Palace, also bowed in tandem.

“What is the matter?” Xiao Moxian’s heart quickened as she saw the expressions on Lin Huang’s face and  the other officer’s faces. She knew that this was unlikely to be anything good.

In this war against the saints, the commanders of humanity each had to have nerves of steel.

Lin Huang stood up and said, “Our allies in the Hidden Dragon galaxy –  the forces of Empyrean Transience and Dragon Fang have been locked down by the Good Fortune Saint Son into a star territory that is less than a trillion miles in width. The saint legions have already begun their search. It won’t be long before our allies are discovered by the saints.”

Lin Huang’s voice was grim. Dragon Fang had yet to break into the Empyrean realm, and in truth, even if he did he still wouldn’t be a match for the Good Fortune Saint Son. As for Empyrean Transience, he was merely a middle human Empyrean, not a match for the Good Fortune Saint Son at all.

“What?”

Xiao Moxian directly stood up, her heart sinking into her stomach.

The fact was that Dragon Fang and Empyrean Transience had been dragged into this disaster by her. Originally, the Good Fortune Saint Son didn’t know that there were other human influences in the Hidden Dragon Galaxy besides Xiao Moxian’s. In order to coordinate and help shield Demon Fairy Celestial Palace, Dragon Fang and Empyrean Transience had been slowly discovered by the Good Fortune Saint Son.

Empyrean Transience’s influence was far larger than a single New Ming Planet. The Good Fortune Saint Son had yet to locate New Ming Planet but was now already beginning to hone in on Empyrean Transience’s location.

This was incredibly bad news, so bad that it couldn’t be any worse.

At this time, a core figure of Demon Fairy Celestial Palace stepped forwards. He asked Xiao Moxian, “Palace Master, Dragon Fang and Empyrean Transience’s forces cannot last much longer. Do we set out to save them? Or not save them?

This officer of Demon Fairy Celestial Palace asked. This was also the main reason why Lin Huang and the others had rapidly made their way here to ask Xiao Moxian for her decision.

To not save them was to violate the tenets of righteousness.

But, to save them meant that they would have to face an unbelievably terrifying enemy. This would be the same as jumping into the fiery pit. The most likely result was that they would all be annihilated!

This was a difficult choice!

And the only who could decide this was Xiao Moxian.

Without being a leader one could never understand or feel the pressure of a leader. It was only when Xiao Moxian became a leader did she profoundly realize just what it was like.

In the battlefield, any decision made by the leader concerned the lives of trillions and quadrillions of people!

And in these turbulent times, she was pillar of everyone’s courage, she was their hope. No matter how confused or shocked or overwhelmed or helpless she was, she had to stand tall and firm, calmly making her decision.

Perhaps, in the thousands and millions of roads that stretched out before her, there might be only a single road to survival. As for her, through her tense nervousness and desperation, she had to seek it out no matter what!

Whether or not she could do it, she had to do it!

………..

“Mojin greets Lord Timebright.”

In front of Lin Ming stood a saint race World King. This World King was the general of the third saint legion in the Blue Horn Galaxy.

“Have you brought the information?”

Lin Ming dragged out his words and simulated a hoarse and gravelly voice. Currently, he had the appearance of a skinny old man, one that was completely similar to the dead Empyrean Timebright. In addition, he had already read through Timebright’s memories and learned everything he needed for his disguise. Even if Timebright’s own son came here they still wouldn’t be able to tell the difference.

“I have brought the requested information. Lord Timebright, please take a look.”

The saint World King passed several jade slips to Lin Ming. Lin Ming swept through them with his divine sense. The information contained inside included the rough distribution of the saint race armies, the map of the wild universe and places which had been explored, as well as some galaxies which might hold human influences.

Lin Ming used a mere 10 breaths of time to read through these materials. He frowned. These materials were far from complete. For instance, the distribution map of the saint race armies only sketchily indicated star territories. Those star territories were far too vast; wanting to find any information there would be difficult.

Moreover, there was only a tiny amount of information regard the Legion of Famine.

Lin Ming believed that the saints had even more detailed information but they just didn’t give it to him.

“Is there nothing with more detail?”

Lin Ming tossed the jade slips at the saint World King. The saint World King awkwardly spoke, “Lord Timebright, without sufficient authority it is impossible to access more information. Moreover…Lord Timebright should only need information related to the Blue Horn Galaxy, so what is the reason for needing other information?

As the saint World King spoke, he looked at Lin Ming with some doubt in his eyes. If Lin Ming’s actions were done by anyone else, they would have long since aroused the wariness of other saint race officers. But because Lin Ming’s identity could not seem any more real and he also knew all the secret codes of the army and also had the status badge to prove his identity, he could not be doubted. No one dared to suspect that a saint Empyrean could be a traitor to the saint race.

“If Lord Timebright really requires this information, then some of the information you seek is in the hands of Empyrean Thundercloud. You may make a request to him. Lord Timebright will be spending some time in the Blue Horn Galaxy, so you can also pay a visit to Empyrean Thundercloud…”

The saint World King carefully said. Empyrean Thundercloud was an upper Empyrean as well as the high commander of the saint race forces in the Blue Horn Galaxy. The reason Empyrean Timebright came to the Blue Horn Galaxy was to coordinate with Empyrean Thundercloud. If so, then the first person Lin Ming visited after reaching the Blue Horn Galaxy should ben Empyrean Thundercloud. However, because the Timebright that he masqueraded as originally had a strange and eccentric personality, not paying a visit wasn’t anything out of the ordinary at all.

Hearing the saint World King say such words, Lin Ming’s lips lifted in a smile. “I understand.”

Lin Ming walked directly towards Empyrean Thundercloud’s Heavenly Palace.

…………….

In a purple grand hall, the high level figures of the Blue Horn Galaxy’s saint legions were currently carrying out a military conference.

“…We have already spent over 20 years in this damned place and used so many people, but all we found in the Blue Horn Galaxy so far has been three of the human planets. Moreover, they are nearly all commoners. This is no different from finding several trillion ants. Even using them as fertilizer isn’t enough to fill the gap between my teeth…”

A Great World King with vaguely blood red eyes and thick blue veins on his neck grimly said. He came from the Legion of Famine and was the commander of the Legion of Famine forces in the Blue Horn Galaxy.

“Don’t worry. This sort of comprehensive search might seem a little stupid but it’s the best method possible. As long as we stick to this plan then we’ll be able to find those mice hiding in their holes. At that time, I’ll make sure I entertain them well and have them all regret ever coming to this world.”

A pallid man that looked like a viper quietly said. As for Empyrean Thundercloud who sat in the head seat, he didn’t say a single word throughout but simply let the subordinates discuss amongst themselves.

At this time his thoughts stirred and he looked towards the entrance.

“Lord Timebright, a conference is underway right now. Would you like to wait?”

Just as a guard was speaking, the door to the hall was pushed open and an old man as skinny as firewood walked in.

Empyrean Thundercloud’s complexion darkened as he saw Timebright burst in; he never had any favorable impression towards this lower Empyrean that had been transferred over here.

Just as he was about to say something to establish his position, he suddenly saw Timebright’s lips curve up in a smile.

Then, Timebright thrust out a hand. In the center of his palm spun a black cube. This black cube seemed to contain some demonic charm, capable of drawing one’s soul into it.

Empyrean Thundercloud was immediately on guard. “What are doing?”

Shua!

A boundless and potent force field came shrouding down. Everything with a thousand feet was enveloped in this force field.

And this force field was a strength that Empyrean Thundercloud had never experienced before. But mixed among it was a Law that he recognized.

That is, the Grandmist Laws!

“You…you aren’t Timebright!”

Empyrean Thundercloud was enraged.

But at this moment, Lin Ming had already stepped forwards. He shot out the Magic Cube from his hand and a terrifying soul vortex swallowed all!

Empyrean Thundercloud’s eyes turned blood red. His body emitted loud crackling noises as he instantly activated the power of his bloodline.

And beside him, the two officers from the Legion of Famine also roared. Wriggling red tentacles dripping with blood rose up from their bodies; they had summoned the power of Famine within their bodies without any hesitation. As Great World Kings facing an Empyrean, their only chose was to undergo body metamorphosis and become an abyssal monster, otherwise they simply wouldn’t have any strength to resist!

However, they never imagined that just as they activated their body metamorphosis, their bodies would seem to be caught in a mire of chaos, completely unable to move. The blood red tentacles that stretched out behind were like snakes caught in the charm of a flute, completely escaping their control.

In a flash, those tentacles that should have plunged towards Lin Ming suddenly turned around and pieced towards their necks!

That change caused them to be scared out of their minds. They wanted to resist, but to their horror they discovered that their bodies were no longer under their control and they were rooted in place.

Puff! Puff!

The tentacles of Famine’s flesh pierced through the necks of those two Legion of Famine officers. Then, their heads flew off with everlasting regret in their eyes.

This ability to control the Legion of Famine had been tested by Lin Ming on Timebright before. Now, he could do so with skillful ease.

At the same time, Empyrean Thundercloud was also surrounded by the massive soul storm set off by the Magic Cube. No matter how much he struggled he couldn’t change his fate.

Peng!

Blood gushed out from Empyrean Thundercloud’s head and his body slumped to the floor…

Chapter 2014A – Fire God Galaxy

Lin Ming rapidly traveled through the starry skies. He had already obtained what he wanted from the dead Empyrean Thundercloud – extremely detailed information that involved the distribution of the saint race’s armies.

A great deal of this information wasn’t even recorded in jade slips; much of it was within Empyrean Thundercloud’s mind and it was all thanks to the Magic Cube that Lin Ming easily obtained this.

Currently, it could be said that Lin Ming had a comprehensive understanding of the war between the saints and the humans in the wild universe.

Now, he was headed towards a star territory called the Fire God Galaxy. There was another saint influence there that he planned to utterly exterminate.

He would strike at the rear of the saints and begin a horrifying storm of blood and slaughter. With a single breath he would overturn the heavens and earth and make it so that the five saint generals had no choice but to turn their attention towards him.

Lin Ming knew that because the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was controlling Famine to swallow the Heavenly Dao Laws, he simply wasn’t able to extricate himself from that process.

As for Soaring Feather God King and Astral Vault God King, they were battling against Empyrean Divine Dream in some far off place and similarly couldn’t withdraw.

In truth, Lin Ming even suspected that Empyrean Divine Dream might not be a match for these two God Kings. After all, those that could reach the heights of a True Divinity were all incredibly talented, at least at the level of Emperor Shakya. None of them were weak. And though Divine Dream dual cultivated essence and divine, perhaps giving her a tad more strength, she still couldn’t face two alone.

Lin Ming speculated that Soaring Feather God King and Astral Vault God King simply weren’t willing to work themselves to death for the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. Although they were meddling in the war of saints and humanity because of some unknown reasons, they still wouldn’t take this time to withdraw from their battle against Divine Dream and chase after some unknown enemy.

True Divinities were all proud and arrogant individuals. An enemy that suddenly emerged from nowhere wouldn’t be enough to arouse their interest.

Then, if one ignored these three True Divinities, the one most likely to strike at him would be the overly confident Good Fortune Saint Son.

Lin Ming understood the Good Fortune Saint Son. They had been opponents for many years and he had a good idea of the Good Fortune Saint Son’s strengths and weaknesses.

He could use the Good Fortune Saint Son’s own cocky confidence to draw him here. Once that occurred, he could display his plan and have his strength rise in a short period of time!

“Fire God Galaxy… hah!”

Lin Ming looked at a great dark vortex-shaped galaxy that was deep in the distance. A murderous light flashed in his eyes. In the next moment he tore through the void and disappeared.

Lin Ming quickly soared through the skies and teleported forwards. He remembered the detailed maps of the saint race influences and hurtled straight forwards like a speeding dragon!

Several days later, Lin Ming finally arrived at his destination. From far away, he could see a group of gathered planets. He knew that these planets were human living areas that had been captured by the saints. Over 10 quadrillion humans lived here.

In the words of the saints, this was nothing but a giant naturally formed jail. This was a human camp, the ‘slave concentration camps’.

After entering the wild universe, Lin Ming had heard again and again of the human captives and slaves. But, he had never seen the conditions in which they lived.

The saint race influences were stationed near these planets. Above every planet floated 12 saint race Holy Palaces. These Holy Palaces gathered together and formed a force field that wrapped around the entire planet.

Such a force field was not something that the human captives living on these planets could ever hope to break.

Rather, it was more accurate to say that these weren’t war captives at all, but commoners.

This galaxy was named Fire God Galaxy. The human Heavenly Palaces in this galaxy had already fallen in the war against the saints. Now, all that was left over were some non-combatants, none of which reached the Divine Transformation realm.

……….

The truth was that Fire God Galaxy had already been held by the saints for over 100 years.

To a martial arts master, this hundred plus years might merely be a bout of meditation or a period of seclusion. But to the average person, this was a whole lifetime…

The human commoners left behind in the Fire God Galaxy didn’t have high degrees of talent to begin with. And beneath the iron rule of the saints, they had no means to practice martial arts. This caused their overall strength to rapidly plummet.

And over 50 years ago, a group of saint race pioneers had arrived at Fire God Galaxy.

These people came from universes native to the saints. To be blunt, they were a ragged pack of people who didn’t manage to mix well in the saint race. Many of them were bandits, vagabonds, thieves, and other such types. Because it was difficult for them to survive in Saint Convocation Heaven, they voluntarily came to the human race’s wild universe to develop this ‘virgin land’.

If one was an individual who lived a good life of wealth and honor amongst the saints already, then who would want to come to such a seemingly barren and remote land?

And the so-called ‘developing the virgin soil’ that the saint pioneers did was actually to rob, kill, and plunder throughout the Fire God Galaxy. The resources that had already been established here, such as medicinal fields, mines, spiritual lands, all of these were taken for themselves.

The saint race armies tacitly consented to all of this. Their goals in invading the wild universe were already obvious.

First was to further expand the territory of the saints, develop more resources, and if possible, seize the Asura Decree that could pierce through the barriers of the God Lamenting Wall so that they could help supply the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign with what he needed to restore Famine to its past peak state.

Second was to cut off the inheritance of humanity to sever all troubles by the roots, thoroughly crushing all future hopes and chances that the humans had to counterattack in the future!

Chapter 2014B – Black Dragon Roars to the Moon

Song Yan was an average human of the Fire God Galaxy. He was already 200 years old and had just barely broken through to the Xiantian realm. Amongst the masses, he was considered standard for commoners.

When he was born, the war between the saints and humans within the wild universe had already begun.

And when he came of age, the flames of war had reached his home and the Fire God Galaxy fell to its enemies. Thus, from that day forth, he along with his 10 quadrillion plus human compatriots were all reduced to slaves.

When Song Yan was a child, he had read through a history book and learned about the history of his fellow humans from 6500 years past. Because the Divine Realm was conquered, humanity was in dire circumstances.

But this time of over 6000 years ago was simply too distant a period for Song Yan. As for him, he never thought that the destiny and life of slavery would arrive so quickly and descend upon him.

This was a horrifying nightmare!

Song Yan had always held his own dreams and desires. He wanted to become a warrior that fought for the human race. He never hoped to become the most dazzling talent in the world that was respected by all, but rather, becoming the most ordinary and common warrior in Fire God Heavenly Palace would have been more than enough.

However, the most basic qualification to become a warrior of Fire God Heavenly Palace was to step into the Divine Transformation realm before a thousand years of age.

To Song Yan, this was far too difficult.

He wasn’t born with much talent and destiny had never given him many lucky chances.

In the end, these dreams could only remain dreams.

He forced himself awake and soberly accepted the reality set in front of him. When he was at the peak Houtian realm, he married a woman. She was a homely woman with ordinary talent, but he loved her deeply with all his heart. In return, she gave him three cute little children, one son and two daughters.

However, these three children were born into a never-ending nightmare, one filled with cruel and avaricious demons that would swallow a person whole and even eat the bones.

Murder, robbery, rape, young women were captured and used as living furnaces and sold as slaves, and young boys were turned into blood sacrifices…

Song Yan didn’t know when these dreadful days would end. The war between humans and saints would continue for several thousand years, but, could he live on for several thousand years?

His children, grandchildren, and even his great grandchildren, would they even be able to live through those thousands of years?

The premise of all this was that… he could have grandchildren.

He was an ant, one that faced an ice age that would continue for an unknown period of years. He quietly stood in an empty field of ice, waiting for his inevitable death to take him.

“Wah – !”

A loud cry spread through the air.

His daughter was crying.

Song Yan’s heart ached. He turned to see his 12 year old son cradling his three year old daughter.

His daughter, she was hungry.

Song Yan had just entered the Xiantian realm. In this wild universe that was filled with chaotic origin energy, although he hadn’t managed to completely sever hunger and thirst, he still only required a minimal amount of rations every month. He only needed to drink water and absorb heaven and earth origin energy to sate his hunger pangs.

But his son, his daughters, his wife, they were different.

They needed to eat. They needed meals.

In the past, in a world of martial artists, starving due to a lack of food was simply unimaginable because they were strong and they grasped the ability to conquer the land and nature around them.

This type of thing would only occur in purely mortal societies.

But now, the Fire God Galaxy was actually in such a state. Of the 10 quadrillion citizens, over 9 quadrillion weren’t able to achieve the state of completely severing their appetite; they needed to consume a massive amount of grain and other rations.

After the chaos of war, a massive number of common citizens lost the protection of the warriors. And without their protection they had no way of facing the vicious beasts that rampaged through the open country. They had no choice but to rush into the city and let their fertile farmlands turn into wasted fields…

As for the remaining food sources, this was all controlled by the saint race bandits. 50 violet sun stones couldn’t even buy a bag of grain, and this was already a price over a million times higher than it had been in the Divine Realm. If one wished to live they had no choice but to go to the tunnels and mine. But in the open country that was filled with vicious beasts, recklessly going out was the same as gambling with one’s own life. It was rare for anyone to survive past three years outside.

Because she had been starving for a long time, Song Yan’s originally chubby daughter had turned sickly thin.

Song Yang’s wife, Zhou Hui, was nursing an even younger daughter. As she heard her other child’s pained cries, she felt as if someone was twisting a knife in her heart.

She no longer had any breast milk. In truth, allowing her child to suckle upon her withered breast was only to psychologically comfort her.

Song Yang grit his teeth. He pulled out a small pack of food from his sleeves. After thinking for some time, he broke off a piece and placed it in his wife’s hand to feed their second daughter.

The leftover piece was given to his son.

As the young boy looked at the food his father handed to him, he continued to cradle his little sister. Although he was 12 years old and his face was a bit pale and gray, his eyes maintained a stubborn light.

“Why won’t you take it?” Song Yan asked.

“Father, I am not hungry.”

The young boy stubbornly said, a strength and defiance in his eyes that no 12 year old should have.

Song Yan suddenly felt his eyes swell with tears.

He directly placed the black pack of food in his son’s arms. Then, he rose and said, “I will go and find something for us to eat.”

After speaking, Song Yan began walking towards the city gates.

“A’Yan, where are you going?”

Looking at her husband head outside the city, Zhou Hui was suddenly panicked. “Do you plan to go hunting? Are you tired of living?”

Outside the city, in the distant wild forests, there were plenty of beasts and prey. But the danger there was over a hundred times that of the mines!

Song Yan was but a Xiantian realm martial artist. If he entered the wild forests then even a variation mouse could eat him up!

Zhou Hui was anxious to the point of crying. The pillar of their family was her husband. Once her husband died, the fate of her and her three children would be unimaginable!

However, Song Yan seemed to have already made up his mind. “I will be fine. If I’m lucky then we won’t have to worry about food this month.”

Then, he continued to say, “If I don’t go then our children will only last for another ten days…”

These second words were said to Zhou Hui with a true essence sound transmission. The hand that reached out to stop him suddenly froze.

She knew that in these past years, because of a myriad of reasons, the population of Fire God Galaxy had already sharply fallen by two-thirds…

Death was something always waiting just outside their door…

Zhou Hui was at a loss for words. But at this time, Song Yang had pushed away her hand. Just as he was about to walk and leave the city, his complexion suddenly changed.

A blood red moon hung high in the dark night. He could hear faint humming sounds from all around, as if they came from afar and also from nearby.

Then, the ground beneath his feet began to gently shake.

This shaking was extremely weak but Song Yan wouldn’t have sensed it wrongly. He looked at a puddle of water on the ground. In the cold and calm night, small ripples began to appear on this puddle of water.

The humming became louder.

Song Yan’s complexion paled.

Could it be…?

As if he needed to confirm something, Song Yan lifted his head and looked into the skies. There, the bright red moon seemed as if it were dyed in blood…

“The blood moon rises… it’s all over…”

Song Yan trembled as he spoke, unable to stand steady.

“What is it?” Zhou Hui asked as she saw Song Yan’s expression.

“Beast tide…”

Song Yan humorlessly smiled. This was a beast tide, a gathering of 10 million or even a hundred million vicious beasts that would attack their city together.

This wild universe never lacked vicious beasts.

In the past, with human masters present, such a beast tide hadn’t occurred for a long, long time.

But now there were no human masters to deter and scare away these vicious beasts. Now, in the Fire God Galaxy, beneath the blood moon which aroused the bloodthirst of these vicious beasts the most and allowed them to easily gather, a beast tide had suddenly erupted!

This city likely wouldn’t be the first to be overrun by this beast tide.

It wouldn’t be the last one either.

“The heavens have abandoned us…”

Zhou Hui grasped her child. She knew that today, on this night, they would all perish here!

The city they lived in had its own guards, but these guards were only Divine Transformation realm martial artists. Because these Divine Transformation realm martial artists weren’t able to reach the Divine Transformation realm before a thousand years of age they weren’t able to enter the Heavenly Palace. With their combat strength, how could they hope to resist such a beast tide?

But at this moment, from the middle of the city, several spirit ships suddenly soared up into the skies, rapidly flying towards the Holy Palaces in space.

Song Yan could see that these were the spirit ships of the saint race pioneers.

Those saint race pioneers were originally thieves and bandits whose only desire was to plunder wealth and resources. Now, with danger approaching, they naturally had no duty or intention to guard the humans.

“That trash!”

Song Yan’s eyes turned blood red. He had never hated another race to such a degree!

And at this time, a loud horn bellowed from within the city!

The armed forces of the city were beginning to gather.

Compared to a true army, this was nothing but a motley gathering of individuals. Most were at the Divine Transformation realm, Divine Sea realm, and even the Life Destruction realm. Moreover, they were all relatively weak amongst their own ranks.

They lifted weapons of varying length and inferior quality. They stood on the city walls, facing the dark army of vicious beasts in the distance!

In the city, Song Yan could only see their backs. Even in the dark pall of night he could see that many of them had backs bent with age and heads of scraggly white hair.

These warriors were all people who had been eliminated from entering the Heavenly Palace. Even so, they still silently and dutifully continued protecting the human citizens.

Song Yang’s eyes had already turned red.

In his eyes, these people were like a wall of steel that stood there tall and proud, bound by their faith and duty…

They were true warriors!

When the saints arrived, they didn’t have the qualifications to fight them. This was because in front of a boulder, an egg was nothing. Trying to rush it would mean nothing but dust and death.

Yet now, facing this annihilating beast tide, the time for them to battle had approached…

This… would likely be the last battle of their lives…

In the face of imminent death, these warriors were incredibly calm, as if at this moment what they faced wasn’t a beast tide that destroyed all life, but peaceful days where they were reunited with their families, where they were able to sit together and gaze upon the setting sun…

“Today, we fight!”

At the top of the city walls, the old commander of the guard grasped a long sword and shouted out his declaration of battle.

Although his declaration was only a mere three words, it was more than enough.

Yes, as a warrior, even a warrior that had been eliminated, they still had their own life mission and their own glory.

That was – to fight!

In the perilous moments when their race faced annihilation, the fate of a warrior should not be to die miserably beneath the suppression of their enemies, but to heroically die upon the sandy battlefield!

Behind them, the common citizens of Fire God Galaxy had already started walking towards the city walls. Some hugged their children and some people knelt down to kiss the earth.

This wilderness was a land they had nourished with their sweat, where they had planted the seeds of hope.

If they had to die here, then let their blood serve to water these lands!

Roar! Roar! Roar!

The demonic beasts that blotted out the skies had already rushed to the city walls. To these strong vicious beasts, the 200 feet high city walls were nothing more than a single leap away. In addition, the sky was filled with a massive number of killer beasts. Their speed was several times faster than the human masters present.

A slaughter was soon to begin.

Song Yang’s blood began to boil over with heat. He picked up his own crude and humble weapon and was about to fly upwards.

But at this time, his wife suddenly pulled him back.

“Hui’er, what are you doing?”

He thought that his wife wanted to stop him, but he saw her stretch out a hand and point into the skies.

“A’Yan… you… what do you think that is?”

In the deep night skies, the blood moon hung high in the air. And in front of that blood moon, a massive black shadow appeared. The shadow unfurled its wings, looking like a demon god of the night.

That… was a Black Dragon!

“Dr-dragon!?”

Song Yan was utterly shocked.

ROAR –

The Black Dragon raised its head, its single horn jutting out into the heavens. Then, it emitted a roar!

This majestic roar echoed through the world, carrying with it a horrifying pressure that impacted into the highest heavens and broke into the starry skies!

Within the city, everyone was dazed. Many of them looked up into the skies. This was the pressure of a Sovereign Beast. Every person could clearly feel that because of this Black Dragon’s roar, the originally manic beast tide just outside the city gates had suddenly frozen in its tracks.

Countless beasts tumbled to the grounds due to their momentum, and some of them crashed into the city walls.

Then, regardless of what injuries they suffered in the chaos and confusion, each beast pulled themselves up and then fell to the ground, prostrate. Beneath this pressure, they all trembled.

A Black Dragon roars to the moon, all beasts bow and submit!

The guards on the city walls were at a loss for what to do. What was this Black Dragon?

Then, they were all shocked to discover that the beast tide began to retreat.

Those blood red eyes of those vicious beasts seemed to be clouded now with fear and awe. Crawling on their bellies, they gradually and carefully returned to the forests, disappearing into the dark…

Everything returned to serenity. There was nothing left but wild winds of the wilderness whipping up the dirt, reminding everyone of what had just happened…

Chapter 2015 – The Smile of Destiny

“What happened?”

“Bastard…”

“Prepare for combat!”

High in the skies, the saint race Heavenly Palaces had already descended into chaos.

To them, a beast tide erupting outside some nameless human city was just a minor matter not worthy of caring for. But, that terrifying Black Dragon roar brought with it a dreadful pressure that struck their fortress. They could sense just how formidable it was!

The Heavenly Palace shivered. As the spirit ships of these saint race ‘pioneers’ were about to reach the Heavenly Palace, they were all blown away and sent tumbling by a brutal storm.

“Motherfucker, what is going on!?”

A giant one-eyed leader of the saint pioneers shouted, incensed. Because of the shaking and tumbling ot the spirit ship just now, a number of high quality stones containing energy of the wild universe had tumbled to the floor. He thought one of his subordinates had operated the spirit ship incorrectly and had struck a meteor of some sort.

However, before he could continue cursing, he suddenly shut up. His eyes widened as he saw that in front of the bow of their spirit ship, several miles away, a giant Black Dragon head was poking out form the thick clouds.

“This… this…”

The pioneer leader was completely dazed. But at this time, he could vaguely see that standing just beside the horn of the Black Dragon was a black-clothed man.

Behind this black-clothed man were three other men in similar clothes. It was as if they were taking this man as their leader.

Woosh!

Those three men hurtled up from the dragon’s head and impacted towards the saint race’s Heavenly Palace.

The speed of these three men quickly reached the limit as they shot into the saint race Heavenly Palace like arrows. Compared to the giant saint race Heavenly Palace, their figures seemed as small as insects. However, just as they vanished into the Heavenly Palace’s protective barriers, a giant explosion rang through the skies a short moment later!

The energy flows surging out from the explosion were not flames, but sweeping currents of chaotic black energy.

No matter what this terrifying chaotic energy struck, it would instantly evaporate into ashes!

Seeing this occur with their eyes, several saint martial artists rushed forwards, wanting to kill these three mysterious people. But they were swept up into that black energy whereupon they immediately vanished.

From head to toe, there was not a single drop of blood left over. Their bodies didn’t shatter but melted away like snowflakes falling into boiling water.

This scene left the saint pioneers falling over each other in a jumble. They wanted to escape, but they saw that many other saint spirit ships also wanted to flee.

Within the armies of the saints there was a strict hierarchy. The size and color of a spirit ship represented its rank and who was riding within it. These saint pioneers helplessly watched as even a World King spirit ship started flying away, so why would they wait around?

However, just as they wanted to flee, they saw that the spirit ships rushing away from the Heavenly Palace suddenly struck an invisible force field that was several hundred miles away.

Bang!

The force field trembled and countless runes shimmered out of existence. Then, something horrifying occurred that left everyone dripping with sweat. The spirit ships that rammed into the force field all broke apart before directly exploding!

The three mysterious men blocked off the skies. A mystical energy swept out, evaporating everything!

All those riding the spirit ships, whether they were Holy Lords, World Kings, or Great World Kings, all of them were instantly killed off.

Seeing this, the saint pioneers were panic-stricken. To them, World Kings and Great World Kings were lofty characters that they would normally never see. But now they were all being killed off in droves, as if they were nothing but ants being stepped on!

It was at this time that everyone realized this planet had already been surrounded by a force field which shrouded over everyone!

No one would be able to escape…

At this time, a giant blood red centipede phantom shot up into the air from the saint race Heavenly Palace!

This blood red centipede was a thousand miles long and had two rows of brutally sharp and thick claws. As this blood centipede appeared, a dreadful pressure gushed out in waves, exciting all the saint martial artists present!

“The blood centipede astral essence totem, that is the symbol of Empyrean Blood Centipede after he undergoes his metamorphosis!”

A saint martial artist shouted out, his morale suddenly rising. The blood centipede was a rare variation bloodline amongst the saints, and Empyrean Blood Centipede who guarded the Fire God Galaxy was someone who possessed this bloodline.

But before the saint martial artists could cheer, that Black Dragon that was over a thousand miles long suddenly roared out loud and then threw itself towards that giant blood centipede phantom. Like a hawk catching a snake, it gripped its claws around that blood centipede!

And at this time, standing on the Black Dragon’s back, the black-clothed man who had yet to move finally did so. His figure flashed and faded like gods and ghosts. In the next moment, a blinding spear light passed through space and pierced through the blood centipede phantom, immediately causing it to shatter and explode, its thick red blood sprinkling through space!

Empyrean Blood Centipede’s pressure plummeted and the world returned to serenity once more…

Empyrean Blood Centipede had died. Even after undergoing his bloodline body metamorphosis, Lin Ming had taken less than 10 seconds to kill him off. He had been utterly rolled over!

All the saint martial artists started to tremble with fear. An Empyrean had been instantly killed like that?

Who was this person?

A demon?

From the ruins of the saint race Heavenly Palace, Lin Ming received the corpse of Empyrean Blood Centipede.

In this war against the saints, he would give no quarter, show no mercy. If he let even a single saint martial artist survive, who knew just how many humans they would go on to kill in the future?

For all those that entered the war, if they wished to obtain military exploits for benefits later, or if they desired to plunder wealth and gain fame by killing others, then they should have understood that they too could be killed off by others.

In this battle, from the point when Empyrean Blood Centipede was slain, the end result was already plain to all.

The disparity in strength was too great.

However, Lin Ming himself didn’t really need to do anything. Just his three avatars was more than enough.

Now all that remained was cleaning up the battlefield.

As his avatars continued fighting, Lin Ming swept his eyes across the planet below him. His thoughts stirred and fell down from the skies.

……….

In the human city, some people looked at the brilliant fluctuations of energy in the night skies. These energy fluctuations looked like beautiful aurora borealises, but the people knew that they were actually phenomena produced from terrifying explosions.

“The saint race Heavenly Palace… has been destroyed!”

A Divine Sea martial artist could already vaguely make out the battle occurring in the high skies. The saint race Heavenly Palace had been blown apart!

A single stone had aroused a thousand waves. All the commoners in the human city were shocked speechless. That saint race Heavenly Palace had floated in the skies for the last hundred years and they were already used to its presence. They subconsciously believed that it would continue floating up there even after their death, but it had actually been blown up?

First was the eruption of the beast tide, then the Black Dragon roaring to the moon, then the retreat of the beast tide, and finally the explosion of the Heavenly Palace. Everything had occurred in a short period of time and had subverted all of their understandings. They didn’t even have time to think about what this meant.

“The saints are finished!” Someone suddenly cried out.

“Our warriors have returned!”

Someone else joyously bellowed. And, these words stunned everyone.

Humanity… had returned?

This war that had such a massive difference in strength, a reversal had occurred?

Bang!!

As if to answer the questions of all mortals in the Fire God Galaxy, in the deep dark sky an even more blinding fluctuation of energy spread out once more. The saint race Heavenly Palace had been thoroughly destroyed. Faintly, one could hear the roar of a dragon echo through the world.

All of Fire God Galaxy began to bubble over with excitement.

“Our warriors have returned!!”

More and more people shouted out. This grief and dread that had existed for over a hundred years was all unleashed at this moment!

People started to sob in their happiness. Some people flew into the skies, some kissed the ground, and strangers turned to hug each other. All of them took deep breaths to calm themselves but they still couldn’t contain the vivid excitement boiling up in their blood.

At this moment, their hearts seemed to beat as one!

Without undergoing hardship it was impossible to understand how precious the feeling of victory was at this moment.

In order to be free, in order to continue being free, at this time even the most cowardly individual wouldn’t hesitate to rush onto the battlefield and shed their blood!

As Lin Ming walked into the streets he saw the crazy crowds all around him. He saw a young man running through the streets, waving his arms. He saw a mother with red eyes unable to stop her tears from falling. Finally, she knelt to the ground and held onto her child, breaking down in heaving sobs.

At this moment, Lin Ming finally understood that his life was already tightly connected to his own race, a connection that could never be separated… he would always belong to his people. Step by step, he had walked towards this day. He was proud to be able to fight for the continued survival of his race…

In the frenzied crowd, Lin Ming’s calm behavior stood out from the rest. He quietly walked through the manic crowds and slowly headed towards a family home.

This was a family of five. In this age where the flames and chaos of war raged through the land, it was already extraordinary that they could guarantee the lives of their entire family to this point.

Song Yan and his wife hugged their children, hot tears streaming down their faces. Then, they saw a black-clothed youth step in front of their tent.

This youth clearly walked down the streets but it seemed as if he were utterly isolated from the world, as if he had walked down from the deepest end of the river of time. Song Yan was startled.

“You are...?”

Song Yan had a faint guess in his heart, but he couldn’t be sure.

There were countless people like Song Yan in the Fire God Galaxy and many of them lived lives far more miserable than he did.

But, when Lin Ming used his divine sense to cover the entire Fire God Galaxy, had actually paid particular attention to Song Yan.

This was because of Song Yang’s 12 year old son.

Lin Ming accidently discovered that this child had an extremely high talent in cultivating the martial path. When combined with his decisive stubbornness and firm moral character, he was simply someone born to live and breathe martial arts.

It would be a pity for such a good seedling to be wasted here.

Zhou Hui pulled Song Yan close. The sudden appearance of this black-clothed youth left her feeling restless. Although her cultivation was only at the Houtian realm, she could intuitively feel how terrifying this youth was.

“You’re all good.” Lin Ming turned towards Song Yan and his wife and faintly smiled. Then, he leaned over and asked Song Yang’s son, “What is your name?”

The 12 year old boy looked at his father and then met Lin Ming’s gaze. He replied, “Song Mo.”

“Song Mo, very good. Are you willing to come with me? To see the outside world?”

Lin Ming smiled.

As this smile fell into Song Yan and Song Mo’s eyes, at this moment they wouldn’t understand just what it meant.

Many years later when Song Mo followed Dragon Fang and became Dragon Fang’s direct disciple, it was only then that he would learn just what sort of existence this youth with the bright smile was.

This was probably a smile from the god of destiny…

Chapter 2018 – Mysterious Ancient Book

Fairy Blue Lotus had no good impression of Imperial Prince Xishen. The Good Fortune Saint Palace’s two peak disciples, the Good Fortune Saint Son and Imperial Prince Xishen, were both incredibly ambitious individuals.

Both of them were extremely dangerous.

Although the Good Fortune Saint Son was domineering, wildly reckless, and murderous, he had always gone straight to the point and never engaged in little schemes and intrigues.

Of course, in Fairy Blue Lotus’s eyes, this was entirely because the Good Fortune Saint Son’s combat strength was ridiculously high, thus making it so that his intelligence in certain areas was only average.

Yet Imperial Prince Xishen was not only cruel but acutely sinister. He was like a viper always hiding in a bush, leaving Fairy Blue Lotus no choice but to dread him.

If Imperial Prince Xishen suddenly appeared here it was naturally in order to struggle for military merits. He wanted to accumulate more military service merits to become more valuable to the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign in the future.

Fairy Blue Lotus coldly eyed Xishen and honestly said, “If you want to join us then show us what value you have! I don’t believe that your strength can pose any threat to this mysterious person.”

“Haha! Senior-apprentice Sister Blue Lotus doesn’t beat around the bush, wonderful.” Imperial Prince Xishen chuckled. “My strength is naturally far from Senior-apprentice Sister Blue Lotus’s, and of course the disparity to that mysterious person is even greater. But…”

As Imperial Xishen spoke he pulled out a thick black book from his spatial ring and placed it before Fairy Blue Lotus. It was a strange ancient book and the cover had the pattern of a blood red eye. This eye seemed as if it were alive. No matter what angle it was viewed from, Fairy Blue Lotus felt as if this blood red eye was staring at her.

There were all sorts of mystical patterns surrounding the eye as well as worm-like seals. These seals seemed to be some form of writing, but Fairy Blue Lotus had never seen such writing before.

Within the entire 33 Heavens, the most ancient writing was likely the common language used by the primal god race and celestial race. But, the writings on this black book seemed completely different from that.

This was an ancient book filled with mysteries and evil. As Fairy Blue Lotus looked at it, she felt an inexplicable sense of fear and dread, as if there were some contagious and ominous curse lurking within it.

“This is an ancient book obtained from the Primeval Realm Ruins?” Fairy Blue Lotus asked.

“Yes!” Imperial Prince Xishen frankly acknowledged. This mysterious ancient book clearly didn’t belong to this era, but it contained a disturbing and terrible power. If so, then it could only originate from the Primeval Realm Ruins. Imperial Prince Xishen wasn’t surprised by Fairy Blue Lotus’s guess at all.

“This book… is evil.” Highsun frowned. This ancient book seemed to possess some kind of demonic charm, calling out for him to open it and peer through its pages. This subconscious feeling of being drawn in and misled by a book left Highsun restless.

“Hehehe… this book that Junior-apprentice Brother Xishen took out really tickles my interest. How about opening it so that we can all take a look?”

Darkmoon tittered atop Highsun’s shoulder. Xishen scratched his chin and then shook his head, saying, “It’s a shame, but I cannot open this book…”

These words left everyone startled. Their eyes fell on this ancient book. This book couldn’t be opened? Just what was in it?

Everyone became increasingly curious.

“You can join us!” Fairy Blue Lotus made her decision. When Xishen took out this ancient book and also poured his astral essence into it, she had already felt the changes in the surrounding energy fluctuations; she clearly sensed the power of this ancient book.

Although she didn’t want to divide any merits to Xishen, all her plans were based upon the premise that they could kill this mysterious person. If Xishen were here then their chances of success would rise by another 10%. She naturally wouldn’t reject such a condition.

In this way, a tight and aggressive deployment of troops began throughout Blood Cloud Galaxy.

The Legion of Famine and various array formations were arranged in approximately ten days. For this mission alone, the saints had used a total of 108 Empyrean spirit treasure level array flags!

In order to lay down a 108 Empyrean spirit flag God Locking Array and prevent the mysterious person from escaping, Fairy Blue Lotus also used an unimaginable amount of violet sun crystals, blood demon crystals, and other such energy stones that had been plundered from the wild universe.

And just two days ago, the mysterious person’s sixth strike had begun. As expected, the neighboring Red Yang Galaxy had been attacked. The mysterious person’s methods were clean and tidy and the entire saint race army stationed within Red Yang Galaxy had been wiped away!

This also confirmed Fairy Blue Lotus’s suspicions. If there wasn’t an accident, then in several more days the mysterious person would arrive at this next destination – Blood Cloud Galaxy.

The trap had already been laid. Now, the mysterious person simply needed to walk into their own doom.

“Hahaha! Senior-apprentice Sister’s strategies are truly divine!”

Highsun laughed. They great formations they arranged could be called an inescapable net through the heavens or earth. He couldn’t think of a single scenario in which the mysterious person could escape.

“I’m really anticipating this battle. With the diversion of the array formations and the coordination of the Legion of Famine, perhaps I can even fight one on one against that mysterious person!”

As Highsun spoke he slammed his heavy swords together. The clear sound of striking metal rang through the air. As he thought about battling such a master he felt his blood seething with vivid excitement.

On his shoulder, Darkmoon giggled, as if she were also impatient.

“The battlefield is constantly evolving; no one can accurately predict what will happen. I can only assure that we have the highest possibility of victory.”

As Fairy Blue Lotus spoke, a faint restlessness stirred up in her heart. She had no idea just where this restlessness came from. It was something that was purely a sixth sense, a feeling against dangers that one felt when the destiny upon their bodies was great enough.

However, she had considered her plans repeatedly and couldn’t find any flaws in them. She shouldn’t be mistaken in her speculations of this mysterious person’s strength also.

If so, then just where was the problem?

Was it related to that ancient book?

Fairy Blue Lotus shook her head, not thinking about it any further. After all, she had paid a great price for all these preparations and it was all in order for this single battle. If she were to give everything up based upon a faint illusory feeling then that would be far too ridiculous.

She could only wait.

However, this wait continued for an entire month. That mysterious person still hadn’t appeared in the Blood Cloud Galaxy…

According to the calculations of previous times, this other party should have come after 10-20 days, but they still hadn’t arrived…

Those within Blood Cloud Galaxy could only impatiently wait.

Highsun lifted his two great swords every day and patrolled back and forth across the square of the Heavenly Palace. Once in a while he would look up into the starry skies and even his lips would turn dry with waiting. After spending so much effort and even sacrificing an Empyrean level influence to create this trap, if nothing were to come of it then they would all be made jokes of.

He didn’t want to be mocked by the Good Fortune Saint Son.

“Junior-apprentice Sister Blue Lotus…” Highsun frequently ran over to Fairy Blue Lotus’s seclusion area, but, she would only have a single word to reply to him with. That was – wait!

Regarding this, Imperial Prince Xishen simply sat in the commander’s hall and stroked the black book in his hands. He didn’t ridicule Fairy Blue Lotus over her plans and whether she had misjudged the situation because he knew that no matter how smart a commander was, it was impossible to perfectly factor in every situation and predict what would occur. At the very least, if he had sat in Fairy Blue Lotus’s spot then he wouldn’t have done anything better.

However, slowly, after Fairy Blue Lotus left Potala Galaxy, the troop-concealing arrays that she had left behind started to arouse the suspicions of Emperor Shakya.

The monks of Mount Potala often prayed to buddha and lived simple lives; they did not excel in war matters. The information that their scouts sent back had many problems that caused Emperor Shakya and Great Limitless Buddha to have difficulties in their analyses of the battlefield.

Although many monks believed that the fortresses had been emptied, they were also worried that the truth was that the saints had set up a trap so they would walk into it.

At this time, no one dared to recklessly push forwards. Otherwise, if a single error in judgment were to be made then total annihilation was possible.

It was only one day that Emperor Shakya single-handedly rushed into the area controlled by the saints!

This could be called the actions of a man with courage and who also trusted in his own skills. Only by himself would he have the freedom to come and go as he pleased. Even if he were to walk into some elaborate trap formed by the saints he believed that he could retreat.

As a result, he discovered that the Legion of Famine, as well as the saint race commanders such as Fairy Blue Lotus, Highsun, and Darkmoon, had long since vanished from their positions!

Emperor Shakya stirred up a great war in the saint encampment and even called in the armies of Mount Potala and the primal god race to come help him. But at this time, the remnants of the defeated saint armies passed through a transmission array that had been prepared beforehand and escaped. Although humanity was successful in this battle, they didn’t actually manage to kill many people.

Seeing such a scene, Emperor Shakya felt his heart drop to his stomach.

“This saint race scum, how could they have emptied out from this area?”

Battle Sovereign To Bagui cursed. The god race and celestial race had coordinated with Mount Potala ahead of time and had prepared to arrive with help. After being suppressed by the saints for so many years and being left without a chance to catch their breaths, they had finally managed to counterattack after a great deal of trouble. But, to find that their fists were hitting nothing but air, this left To Bagui feeling unwell.

Great Limitless Buddha frowned. He thought for a moment and then slowly said, “Amitaba. If this old monk isn’t wrong then Fairy Blue Lotus, Highsun, Darkmoon, and the others have already left with the saint armies ahead of time and have relocated somewhere else to fight. If there is something they would take so seriously, then that is likely our mysterious benefactor who has appeared in their backlines…”

Great Limitless Buddha’s words left them all feeling chilled. Towards this ally that had appeared from nowhere, they were both curious and grateful. Thanks to this mysterious ally diverting the attention of the saints, humanity had been granted a moment of respite.

But if the Legion of Famine were to turn around, then how could this ally, whether it was one person or several people, possibly hope to resist the saints?

This was the Legion of Famine!

Let alone a single person, even if the entirety of Mount Potala and all its disciples were to be encircled by the Legion of Famine, total annihilation was a possibility!

“We have to inform him!” But just as To Bagui spoke these words he realized how ridiculous they were. They didn’t know who this mysterious person was and he was also thousands of quintillions of miles away; how could they possibly hope to contact him?

For a time, the human powerhouses were at a loss of what to do. All their previous happiness had faded away.

Now, they could only stare helplessly on as this mysterious person collided with the Legion of Famine.

“Fairy Blue Lotus is not some common person of her generation. The Legion of Famine’s array formations are an inescapable net. With the Legion of Famine being commanded by Fairy Blue Lotus, the war strength they can display is incredibly terrifying. Perhaps…” Diwuhen nervously said.

“Pray, pray…” Great Limitless Buddha began reciting buddhist scriptures. “May buddha bless him, that it is a blessing and not a curse, and if it is a curse then he can avoid it. But, everything is already in the hands of fate…”

Chapter 2023 – God King Phantom

After more than 6000 years passed, Lin Ming once again encountered the person who had hunted him down in the past. At this time, the Soaring Feather God King in front of Lin Ming wore a layer of light gauzy clothes, a veil over her face. As she raised her hands and stepped upon the air she seemed like a celestial maiden riding upon the surging waves.

Amongst the saint race’s three True Divinities, she was the most low-key and mysterious one.

No matter which True Divinity it was, they were all characters that stood high in the clouds above the highest heavens, overlooking the common world.

Not to mention the giant disparity that existed between True Divinities and Empyreans, just the talent of a True Divinity belonged to the class of unrivalled geniuses in the 33 Heavens. At the very least they would be at the level of Emperor Shakya.

With such a talent combined with the superiority of cultivation, this made it so that there were no Empyreans capable of fighting a True Divinity.

In their hands, a grain of sand could shatter the vault of heaven and a single feather could sunder the galaxy.

And now, such a feather was floating before Lin Ming, and it had also transformed into the phantom of Soaring Feather God King.

“Soaring Feather’s incarnation?”

Lin Ming’s pupils shrank. This was an incarnation left behind by a True Divinity.

Moreover, Fairy Blue Lotus was a lower Empyrean. In addition to her talent, her strength was amongst the top echelons of Empyreans. If Soaring Feather God King left behind an incarnation then its strength would definitely surpass the realm of a peak Empyrean, otherwise it wouldn’t be of much use.

In other words, if Soaring Feather God King wanted to create an incarnation that could protect the life of someone on the level of Fairy Blue Lotus then she would need to use a great deal of her cultivation and blood vitality.

Without a doubt, this feather contained Soaring Feather God King’s blood essence; it was extremely precious.

Lin Ming never thought that Soaring Feather God King would place such importance on this disciple of hers.

At this time, Soaring Feather God King was already holding a blade of energy and slashed down at Lin Ming!

Soaring Feather God King’s incarnation only contained a minor part of her consciousness. At this time, her expression was calm and a strange charm flashed in her eyes.

The sword pressed down like a divine mountain, seeming as if it could crush the world apart. Lin Ming felt the surrounding space immediately lock down, preventing him from avoiding.

But, Lin Ming never planned to defend to begin with. He wanted to see just how strong Soaring Feather God King’s incarnation was.

Lin Ming instantly summoned the power of the Asura blood within him. Black scales covered his body as the Black Dragon Spear emitted a keening cry, thrusting outwards!

At this moment, a Heretical God Tree phantom appeared behind Lin Ming. Thunder and flames howled into the air, twining around the spear shaft in a vast sea of red and purple. Even if a God Beast were to fall into this horrifying sea of energy it would be reduced to ashes!

However, Soaring Feather God King’s expression was still indifferent. She stepped upon the sea of thunder and flames. No matter how much the thunder and flames tumbled and roiled, all it did was gently pass over Soaring Feather God King’s body, unable to harm her or affect her at all, as if she were located in a completely different time and space. At this time, she truly seemed like an eternal celestial maiden that stood above the surging waves, as ethereal and elegant as flowing dust.

But, this scene contained a brutal killing intent, one that filled the body with unease.

Soaring Feather God King’s sword separated the sea of thunder and fire.

The sword energy slashed straight down at Lin Ming!

As Fairy Blue Lotus watched this her heart had long since tightened. Before, she had attached the feather atop the sword in a sneak attack because only the incarnation of her master would be able to directly fight against Lin Ming. She was afraid that even her master’s incarnation wouldn’t be able to strike him down, but as she saw Soaring Feather God King sunder the sea of thunder and fire that Lin Ming used, hope began to light up in her heart.

As Lin Ming watched this whistling sword energy, he rapidly drew backwards. His eyes shimmered with seals of the Asura Laws. At the same time, the Daevic Eye Dao Palace opened from between his eyebrows.

He was well aware that the power of thunder and fire wouldn’t be able to damage Soaring Feather God King. It wasn’t because it lacked in power, but because his opponent had reached the level of a True Divinity and their attainments in the Laws were incredibly high.

This incomplete Heretical God Force was simply unable to touch Soaring Feather God King.

After his testing strike failed, Lin Ming no longer held back. His pupils contracted. As he opened the Daevic Eye Dao Palace, he also opened the Three Lives Pupils’ All Existence to Void!

Within the vision field of the daevic eye and the Three Lives Pupils, the energy flows in Soaring Feather God King’s incarnation become utterly clear. Lin Ming drew a yin yang chart with his hands, causing a flow of black and gold energy to twist together.

The black energy was thick with dark demonic intent, and the golden energy was like a shining sun.

The two flows of energy connected. In that instant, all the Laws and origin energy in the surrounding space began sweeping up towards him, as if Lin Ming’s hands were the center of all Laws in the universe.

A massive yin yang vortex slowly formed, like a primal chaos yin yang diagram. But, the heights of these Laws had actually far surpassed the Yin Yang Laws.

This vortex violently collided with the sword light of Soaring Feather God King’s incarnation!

Chi chi chi!

Sword light shattered. On the face of Soaring Feather God King’s incarnation, a hint of shock flashed over her features!

Although this was but a wisp of one’s self used to form an incarnation and was only an incomplete body of consciousness, it still possessed intelligence and thoughts, similar to a person.

The vortex of divinity and demons continued forwards with unstoppable momentum, rolling over all. Soaring Feather God King’s incarnation protected her body with sword light but in the end she was nothing but an incarnation, unable to summon measures capable of resisting Lin Ming.

Peng!

The final layer of sword light was smashed apart. The incarnation’s protective astral essence shook like a ship’s sail in a raging storm even as it was slowly torn apart.

Lin Ming roared out loud. Behind him, the phantom of nine stars appeared. Starlight began gathering onto his body. As he erupted with strength no weaker than the Black Dragon, he brutally thrust his spear through Soaring Feather God King’s protective astral essence.

Kacha!

The spear penetrated the protective astral essence and then pierced through Soaring Feather God King’s chest!

The white clothes were stained red with blood, like vivid red plums falling onto a plain of white snow. Soaring Feather God King’s lips overflowed with blood and the sword in her hand had long since fallen away, turning into energy light before vanishing into nothing. Soaring Feather God King gripped the shaft of the Black Dragon Spear with her hands, her ghostly blue eyes looking at Lin Ming with disbelief.

At this time, she was only a mere foot away from Lin Ming. Her eyes began to slowly lose their brilliance. As she gazed upon Lin Ming’s face that seemed carved by a saber, his eyebrows that were as sharp as swords, and his deep and profound eyes, confusion appeared on her face. This youth seemed familiar, but in the end he was only a stranger…

Peng!

Soaring Feather God King’s body exploded into countless motes of light. These motes of light were like 20 million fireflies that flew off into the void, all of them vanishing from the world.

And from the center of these motes of light, a feather floated down.

Lin Ming reached out and took this feather in his hand.

The strange feather was only half a foot long, as if it were the plume of a white crane. It shined with a crystalline light, and the feather was stained with a beautiful line of red blood.

Although Soaring Feather God King’s incarnation was destroyed by Lin Ming, he could still feel a powerful strength contained within it. It continued to shine with a rainbow of lights, as if it wanted to jump out from his grip.

Lin Ming exerted his strength and formed numerous seals that bound the feather in layers of barriers until it could no longer move.

After finishing this, Lin Ming looked up at Fairy Blue Lotus, a smile on his face.

Chapter 2025 – The Angered Soaring Feather

Soaring Feather God King had been fighting with Empyrean Divine Dream for many years. But in truth, the number of times they had directly faced each other was extremely low, and they had never wholeheartedly attacked each other.

For most of the time, the two of them used arrays to break arrays, comparing their Laws and comprehending the battle with their spiritual seas.

Of the two of them, one dual cultivated energy and divine and the other dual cultivated essence and divine. Their cultivation systems were inextricably linked with their mental strength and spiritual sea, making it so that they used all sorts of fighting methods. A single battle of the soul could continue for several years on end.

For peerless masters, finding an opponent that was similar in strength and Laws was incredibly hard, especially upon reaching the level of Soaring Feather or Divine Dream. There were few people capable of making them use their full strength in this universe.

But if a martial artist were to only go into dark seclusion to cultivate and meditate on the Laws, then they would inevitably lack things they needed. They required an appropriate environment and opponents that were on their level. This was also one of the reasons why humanity’s martial arts civilization began to prosper 10 billion years ago.

Thus, for these past years, Soaring Feather and Divine Dream came to a tacit understanding in their ongoing battle. As they fought they constantly deepened their understandings into their spiritual sea and mental strength.

Originally, Soaring Feather didn’t place much importance on the war between the saints and humanity. She simply didn’t care about whether the saints won or not. The only reason she participated in this war was because the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had given her sufficient incentives, and at the same time she also believed that the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign might rule all beneath the heavens later and achieve a higher boundary so she didn’t want to offend him.

Her being able to keep Divine Dream busy in this different universe was already extremely beneficial to the saints’ war efforts. And, there was another advantage; that was that Soaring Feather could rest assured as she allowed Fairy Blue Lotus to partake in the war between the humans and saints.

Soaring Feather God King was confident that with Fairy Blue Lotus’s strength and intelligence, the incarnation that she had left with her, as well as the Legion of Famine that the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had allowed her to command, there was no one in the entire wild universe who would be able to do anything to her.

She would be the strongest fist of the saint armies. Not even Emperor Shakya would be able to contend with her.

And in every great calamity, although there would be disasters and tribulations that sweep through the 33 Heavens, this also meant that it would be an era where geniuses from all the various races would rapidly grow.

In a war that involved all universes, this would be the best battlefield for Blue Lotus to temper herself.

In Soaring Feather God King’s eyes, the greatest benefit of the war between saints and humanity was that her own disciple could adventure and gain experience within it.

As for Divine Dream, the opponent of Soaring Feather God King, she was actually not as calm or happy with the situation. In fact, Divine Dream could be said to be burning with impatience!

But no matter how anxious she was about humanity’s war, at this time she had nothing else she could do. She couldn’t do anything to Soaring Feather God King and definitely could not fight the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. And, if she wanted to meddle in the battles between Empyreans then she knew that Soaring Feather God King and Astral Vault God King would not allow her to.

Thus at this time, besides continuing to battle Soaring Feather God King and taking hold of every chance to increase her strength, there was no other road she could take.

She knew that humanity’s ultimate enemy was in the end just one person – the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. This was also an enemy that she would inevitably have to face in the future.

Perhaps there might be a day when she could emulate the actions of Empyrean Divine Seal of the past, burning away her life to cause heavy damage to the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. To Divine Dream, this was already the best result she could think of.

But there was only the slimmest of hopes in accomplishing such a goal. The more the war drummed on, the more Empyrean Divine Dream was able to feel just how strong Empyrean Divine Seal had been in the past. When he faced the extreme True Divinity level Famine he also had to face the previous Saint Sovereign who was no weaker than the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. Even then, Divine Seal was able to turn the tides of war and achieve an impossible miracle.

Divine Dream knew that there still existed a massive gap between her and Empyrean Divine Seal.

For a short period of time Soaring Feather God King wouldn’t be able to break through Empyrean Divine Dream’s dreamland space. Soaring Feather God King fell into contemplation. In truth, Empyrean Divine Dream didn’t place much soul force into this array formation and it was poor in intensity. If Soaring Feather God King wished for it, she could erase this array formation with absolute strength. But she didn’t do so. Rather, she slowly deduced its mysteries to exercise and further enhance her Laws.

But before even a third of the required time passed for Soaring Feather God King to unravel these Laws, her hands suddenly shook. She looked up, shock and disbelief flashing in her eyes.

Just now, she felt that the incarnation she had prepared for Fairy Blue Lotus had been shattered by someone else!

Soaring Feather God King had condensed a wisp of her life’s blood essence into her incarnation. Amongst Empyreans, her incarnation was nearly invincible.

Just who was it that had managed to break apart her incarnation?

How was that even possible!?

Then what about her disciple, Fair Blue Lotus?

In Soaring Feather God King’s eyes, Fairy Blue Lotus, who should not have encountered any truly perilous situations, must have suffered some disastrous defeat! Otherwise there was no way she would use her final trump card.

In order to ensure the integrity of Fairy Blue Lotus’s divine soul so that she would be able to break through boundaries more perfectly in the future, Soaring Feather God King didn’t have Fairy Blue Lotus leave behind a wisp of her soul in a lifesoul jade slip. So, she didn’t know what had happened to her.

Thinking of this, Soaring Feather God King’s eyes that were filled with disbelief began to turn icy cold!

She reached out with her sense, wanting to perceive her feather that had been suppressed. But what surprised her was that although she could sense that her feather still existed, it seemed to be sealed away in some mysterious space. The Laws of this mysterious space blocked out everything, making it so that she couldn’t lock onto her feather’s position.

Moreover, she could clearly feel that the blood essence she attached to this feather was being slowly refined by someone else!

This caused a thick killing intent to burst out from her eyes!

This was her source blood vitality from after she had broken into the True Divinity realm. If she were to lose it then it would be a tremendous attack upon her cultivation!

“Who could it be!?”

Soaring Feather God King grit her teeth, all sorts of thoughts rapidly racing through her mind.

She first thought of Emperor Shakya.

Amongst the humans, the only one capable of breaking apart her incarnation was Divine Dream. Since Divine Dream was being delayed here, then that meant her incarnation was invincible amongst humanity.

Unless Emperor Shakya were to make another breakthrough.

But as she thought of Emperor Shakya’s age, Soaring Feather God King didn’t think that this was possible. Emperor Shakya was just too young. According to his current battle strength and talent, it was completely unreasonable for him to suddenly break into the True Divinity realm.

But no matter who it was, Soaring Feather God King would not forgive this person!

If they harmed Fairy Blue Lotus then Soaring Feather God King would chase them to the ends of the world!

Peng!

Soaring Feather God King’s palm thrust out with strength. The dreamland array formation that Empyrean Divine Dream laid down suddenly burst apart, turning into countless motes of light.

At this time, Soaring Feather God King didn’t have any thoughts of slowly unraveling this array formation, but instead shattered it with absolute strength.

Soaring Feather God King was anxious to return. She stepped on the void, wanting to instantly leave this star territory. But at this time, force fields began to twist around her, causing the Space Laws to change so that she couldn’t use the great void shift.

In the next moment, purple fog gathered together once more, surrounding Soaring Feather God King and locking her in.

The difference now was that this purple fog was no longer a superficial comparison of Laws; rather, a truly terrifying amount of power was poured into it.

This was the divine dream space!

Shua!

The divine dream space gently quivered. Not too far away from Soaring Feather God King, a blue-clothed woman seemed to lift apart a curtain of stars, stepping through the surging space to appear in front of Soaring Feather God King.

This woman was similar to Soaring Feather God King in temperament and was similarly a goddess of her generation. She sat upon the throne in the highest heavens, overlooking the mortals below.

“Divine Dream!” Soaring Feather God King’s eyes blazed with anger. “You want to block my way?”

Empyrean Divine Dream faintly smiled. “Just now, I felt that there were tremendous fluctuations in your mood within the divine dream space, and you even broke apart my force field with absolute strength. Naturally, I had to come take a look. It seems as if… you have some urgent matters to attend to?”

Empyrean Divine Dream’s clothes fluttered around her. Her tone was not slow or hurried, like a warm spring through winter, beautiful to the ears.

But as these words fell into Soaring Feather God King’s ears, they were actually grating to hear.

“Get out of my way!”

Soaring Feather God King coldly said.

“I’m afraid that isn’t going to happen.” Empyrean Divine Dream gently raised her right hand, a flower petal slowly revolving around her fingertips. She faintly guessed that it was something related to battles between the juniors that had startled Soaring Feather God King so. And if it was bad news to Soaring Feather God King, then it was definitely good news to her. In any case, she couldn’t easily allow her to withdraw.

“The rivers run 30 years east and then 30 years west. Since you held me back here before so that I couldn’t return to the wild universe, it’s my turn to repay the favor.”

Soaring Feather God King flung out her sleeves, her face an icy mask. “Do you think that with Astral Vault God King also coming, you will still be able to hold me here?”

“To have you stay for a moment is another moment won.” Divine Dream’s voice was indifferent as she slowly pulled out a sword…

…………

The faint and ethereal starry skies were limitless and without end. Floating within these starry skies was a continent, and this continent was covered with spirit springs and wonderful treasures of heaven and earth.

This was a land contained within Lin Ming’s universe.

At this time, four of the saint generals – Highsun, Darkmoon, Blue Lotus, and Xishen, had all been thrown onto this continent after having their blood energy completely locked away.

Their bodies were bound with Law curse seals; even moving the tiniest fraction was difficult.

“Motherfucker, this hurts!” Highsun struggled to twist his neck, causing his bones to emit loud crackling sounds. “This damned demon, I have no idea what he plans to do with us.”

Highsun cursed. Considering things, he was in a relatively good situation; at the very least he was able to stand. The most pitiful one was Xishen. All of Xishen’s bones had been broken and he was lying on the ground like a puddle of meat, only able to emit weak groans.

At this time, Fairy Blue Lotus was carefully observing Lin Ming’s inner world. As she investigated the world around her, she began to discover the differences here.

“This world seems… like it doesn’t have any difference from the outside universe… could we really be in an inner world?”

Fairy Blue Lotus muttered, unsure of herself. Could this be the inner world of an abyssal demon? The Laws, matter, and origin energy here were so real…

Before Highsun and Darkmoon could respond, space began to distort in front of them. A black-clothed Lin Ming appeared, his spear in hand. As Lin Ming arrived on this continent, he firmly stood a hundred feet away from the four.

Chapter 2026 – The Wonderful Use of Captives

Seeing that dark star Lin Ming, the four saint generals felt their hearts tighten.

“What do you plan on doing to us?”

Fairy Blue Lotus asked. After reaching such a cliff, she couldn’t imagine any way to escape. Now the only way she could live was if she used this mysterious person’s greed against him. Since he had caged them here he inevitably must be plotting some scheme, otherwise he would have long since killed them.

Lin Ming didn’t reply. Fairy Blue Lotus sent Highsun and Darkmoon a sound transmission, “Follow my lead and don’t speak…”

Highsun and Darkmoon inwardly nodded. At this time they could only depend on Fairy Blue Lotus. As for Xishen, he could be entirely ignored. Right now, he couldn’t even speak.

Lin Ming remained silent. He stepped through the void and appeared right in front of Fairy Blue Lotus. He stood high above her in a commanding position, overlooking her below.

This was the suppression brought by the overwhelming disparity in strength. Fairy Blue Lotus held her breath. Facing a mysterious powerhouse like Lin Ming as well as the aura that rolled off his body, she felt as if she were gasping for breath every moment.

She was even afraid that Lin Ming would let loose his bestial nature in the next moment and return to his demonic origins. If so, the consequences would be unimaginable.

Fairy Blue Lotus bit her lips, her complexion slightly pale. “If you have any conditions, speak them.”

Fairy Blue Lotus was highly familiar with the weaknesses of the heart. Of course, this was entirely based upon the premise that this demon in human form also had a human-like disposition.

She already decided that no matter what conditions this person proposed, she wouldn’t fully agree nor would she fully reject.

This was the method of negotiations with the highest chance of survival.

If she were to directly reject him so that this person didn’t see any hopes of success, he might kill them off.

At the same time, if she were to agree to readily and allow him to easily achieve his goal, then he also might kill them off to erase all witnesses.

She had to look for that singular balance point between agreeing and refusing, so that this person would see hope but also not obtain victory immediately.

This balance point was what her life stood upon!

“This is the greatest test I have encountered in my life. I must calculate his mindset…”

Fairy Blue Lotus thought to herself. However, she never imagined that not only would Lin Ming not say any words, but he would instead reach out his hand, revealing four floating balls of meat above his palm!

These balls of meat slowly wriggled and crept, as if they were four hearts.

However, tiny tentacles danced around them like those of a jellyfish, all of them continuously waving about.

No matter what Fairy Blue Lotus could calculate, she would never calculate such a situation occurring. She didn’t need to use her sense to immediately understand that this was the flesh and blood of Famine!

Immediately, Fairy Blue Lotus’s face turned paper white!

She didn’t need to be a genius to understand just what this person was planning to do – he wanted to implant the flesh and blood of Famine within their bodies!

After personally experiencing this mysterious person’s ability to control the Legion of Famine, Fairy Blue Lotus didn’t doubt that as long as he implanted the flesh and blood of Famine within her, she would completely become his puppet. She would accept all orders obediently and lose all independent will.

If he wanted her to kneel then she would kneel. If he wanted her to die then she would die. If he wanted her to offer up her primordial yin then she would offer up her primordial yin. She would turn into the most loyal and most pitiful servant, one with no thoughts of her own.

She would rather die than be reduced to such a slave.

“Just kill me!”

Seeing the flesh and blood of Famine slowly float above Lin Ming’s palm, Fairy Blue Lotus felt her heart shrink in her chest.

Behind Fairy Blue Lotus, Highsun and Darkmoon, and even the half-dead Xishen felt as if they had fallen into any ice lake. This was truly a fate more horrifying than death.

“You want to die? Keep on dreaming.”

Lin Ming grabbed Fairy Blue Lotus’s neck and reached out his hand. The flesh and blood of Famine followed.

This flesh and blood of Famine had been taken out from a part of the Legion of Famine’s saint martial artists. It was the most distilled essence, capable of controlling an Empyrean level powerhouse!

Lin Ming wanted to know; once these four saint general top-level geniuses were fused with the flesh and blood of Famine, just what kind of combat strength would they be able to display?

The flesh and blood of Famine utterly obeyed Lin Ming’s command. After implanting it, he would gain four loyal and devoted super minions. To have them sweep away the saint armies would be no problem at all.

Of course, if Lin Ming wanted to he could take out the flesh and blood of Famine at any moment, restoring their freedom of will.

To possess such an ability was truly convenient. Lin Ming even felt a bit of envy towards the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s methods.

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign planned to use the flesh and blood of Famine to slowly take control of the entire world.

Then, why couldn’t Lin Ming do the same?

“You! You… my master will not let you go!”

Fairy Blue Lotus said between clenched teeth, her voice difficult to hear. For her to use her master as a threat already proved that her fear had reached the extreme, otherwise she wouldn’t use such a cheap and shameful threat. This was the same as a tussle between children, and then one of the children running away while screaming for their mother.

But at this time, Lin Ming had already grabbed Fairy Blue Lotus’s neck and had lifted her up.

“No… no…”

Even though Fairy Blue Lotus was normally calm, she had already lost her composure and was panicking, wildly struggling about. The ball of meat continued to wriggle about in Lin Ming’s hand, extending its small tentacles towards her. In her eyes, this was the most terrifying demon in the world.

“Just happily be my servant.” Lin Ming indifferently said, his words causing Fairy Blue Lotus to wish that she could commit suicide. At the same time, Lin Ming grabbed the flesh and blood of Famine and then placed it above Fairy Blue Lotus’s chest.

“Ahhh!”

Fairy Blue Lotus miserably cried out!

All she felt was numbness at her chest. The flesh and blood of Famine had bitten open her chest and was drilling into her body.

It was a strange and macabre feeling to know that she was losing herself. She felt itchy all over even as her entire body tingled with numbness.

This bizarre feeling nearly caused Fairy Blue Lotus to bite off her tongue in response; she would rather the process be agonizingly painful so she could faint here.

Hualala!

The flesh and blood of Famine continued to wriggle onwards. Fairy Blue Lotus’s eyes turned blood red. Her delicate body violently shook as she took great gasping breaths.

However, no matter how she struggled she couldn’t change her destiny.

“You… you… you… don’t…”

Fairy Blue Lotus could no longer form complete sentences. Fragrant drops of sweat rolled down her body, soaking her clothes.

And at this time, Lin Ming continued to grab onto Fairy Blue Lotus’s neck, his eyes so cold that they caused one to shiver.

His gaze fell upon Highsun, Darkmoon, and Xishen. All of them began to sweat all over. They finally realized that after falling into the hands of this demon, even dying might be an impossible hope!

Slowly, Fairy Blue Lotus’s struggles died down. Drool leaked out from the corners of her lips. Lin Ming released her, allowing her to slump onto the ground like a wet noodle.

Lin Ming looked at her. At this time, the flesh and blood of Famine had already turned into tiny threads that permeated her heart and every other inch of her body. Even her spiritual sea was invaded by the flesh and blood of famine.

The flesh and blood of Famine had thoroughly fused with her body.

As the more formidable life form, after Fairy Blue Lotus and Famine’s mortal body fused together into a single being, the flesh and blood of Famine naturally took command of her body and mind.

If Lin Ming wanted to he could have the flesh and blood of Famine remain in a slumbering condition so that Fairy Blue Lotus was no different from normal, and there would also be no influence on her thoughts. But once he activated the flesh and blood of Famine, she would become his most loyal slave.

Lin Ming looked at Fairy Blue Lotus. With a thought, he activated the flesh and blood of Famine.

Fairy Blue Lotus trembled. Bewilderment flashed in her eyes. She dazedly looked at Lin Ming with confusion. Slowly, this confusion turned into reverence.

This feeling was like a low level life form seeing the king of their own race. This was an obedience and respect that came from the depths of their bloodline.

She crawled up from the ground and knelt before Lin Ming. She lovingly kissed his feet, saying, “Blue Lotus greets Master.”

“Very good.”

Lin Ming smiled. With four Empyrean level super minions as well as over 90% of the remaining Legion of Famine, he would have an even greater advantage in his crusade against the saints!

Moreover, these four saint generals, in particular Blue Lotus, Highsun, and Darkmoon, would make it so that Astral Vault God King and Soaring Feather God King would be wary of acting against him, in fear that they would harm their disciples. These were truly multi-purpose servants!

At this time, Lin Ming turned towards Highsun, Darkmoon, and Xishen.

Highsun’s eyes stuck out of his head and he gasped like a cow. He had personally seen Fairy Blue Lotus’s fate and his body trembled with anger and fear. “You beast, if you have the guts then kill me! Do you dare to kill me? Come on! If you have the courage then kill me!”

Highsun pointed at his own neck, his eyes blood red. “You motherfucker, you fucking beast, if you don’t kill me today then there will surely be a day when I chop off your head and feed it to the… guh…!”

Highsun cried out pitifully. Because just now, the flesh and blood of Famine had been tossed out by Lin Ming and had flown in between his lips.

It had gone straight into his throat!

“Kah! Kuh!”

Highsun desperately grabbed at his neck, the blood vessels already sticking out like worms. But, he couldn’t stop this thing from crawling into his body.

“M-mother…”

Highsun spat out with difficulty. He flew backwards and landed on the ground, slamming his head into the floor and punching his chest. But, all his efforts were for naught.

He wanted to curse at Lin Ming but because his throat was filled his words became a blur.

“You want to goad me into anger so that I will kill you in a rage? Not even a child would fall for such little tricks.”

Lin Ming coldly looked at Highsun as he tumbled about on the ground. Because Highsun’s energy and blood vitality had been sealed away, he couldn’t even commit suicide by severing his meridians. With Highsun’s intelligence, he could only think of goading Lin Ming into anger as a way to find death. However, Lin Ming didn’t even care about his words.

Then, Lin Ming turned to Darkmoon.

Darkmoon had already started crying, truly crying. Great teardrops fell down like rain, making her seem pitiable.

She miserably looked at Lin Ming and held her hands against her chest. With her short height and slim figure, she looked like a 14-15 year old girl who had developed too early.

“N-no, don’t do it, I’ll do anything you want. You don’t need to implant anything in me. I am willing to be your servant, I beg you, I’ll do anything you…..”

Chapter 2028 – News Worth Celebrating

Emperor Shakya’s troops had managed to rout the Legion of Famine that had stayed in Potala Galaxy after their main force left. Although they didn’t manage to kill much of the saint armies, they still managed to completely recapture Potala Galaxy.

Outside of Empyrean Divine Dream, Mount Potala’s forces could be called the most formidable amongst humanity.

Since they had managed to stabilize their foothold they naturally wouldn’t think of hiding in this tiny little corner of the world. Rather, they would venture outwards and strike at the saints on their own initiative!

Now they were even preparing their attack plans.

“Everyone, we have now managed to bring together a considerable force. I believe that what we must first do is rescue our companions!

“Because we had to delay for time, many of our people dispersed and hid in the most hidden corners of the wild universe. Although this naturally made it much harder for the saints to find us, once they did find anyone then the only result was utter defeat. If this continues, then as long as the saints have enough time, they will sooner or later exterminate us all.

“We cannot sit by and idly wait for death; we must move immediately and rescue our fellow humans who have been forced into hopeless situations!”

Emperor Shakya iterated the key point of this meeting. Now with so many human influences in imminent danger, the question was: which ones should they rescue first?

Everyone looked towards Emperor Shakya and also felt troubled for him. To rescue one influence was to mean giving up on another. However, he had to make a choice.

“We have to consider the larger picture. There are currently two vital rescue targets that we have designated. The first is the Hidden Dragon Galaxy! It has already been a long time since our information network with the Hidden Dragon Galaxy was severed. I even suspect that Dragon Fang and Xiao Moxian have been encircled by the enemy. Whether it is Xiao Moxian, Lin Huang, or Dragon Fang, they are the future hopes of humanity. In particular, Xiao Moxian and Lin Huang. The two of them are the ones most closely related to Lin Ming, and Lin Ming was the one who risked his life for us in the past in order to exchange it for the slimmest possible hopes of survival for the human race and thus open the gates of the wild universe to us. Since Lin Ming has passed on, we must ensure the survival of his lineage no matter what.

“But besides the Hidden Dragon Galaxy, there is also another rescue target. That is… the mysterious man who has recently appeared! All clues indicate that the main force of the Legion of Famine left Potala Galaxy for this person. Since he has done his best to buy time for us, we cannot sit by and do nothing. Moreover, this mysterious person has formidable strength, and an enemy of an enemy is a friend. He might be able to provide us with good fortune and a turning pointing in our war against the saints. We cannot just let him perish beneath the Legion of Famine…”

As Emperor Shakya spoke to here, some people were already frowning, their eyebrows knit together. “Should we divide our forces?”

Although their current gathered forces were formidable, when it came to facing the Good Fortune Saint Son or the Legion of Famine, they were nothing to look at. And, dividing their forces would only make them weaker.

“This is what we are here today to discuss…” Emperor Shakya said, “We must weigh the advantages and disadvantages and then follow through with the most effective plan…”

As Emperor Shakya spoke, the sound of rapid footsteps echoed through the grand hall.

“Urgent message!”

A messenger shouted from outside the hall.

“Enter!”

Emperor Shakya felt his heart skip a beat. While a military meeting was being convened, outside disturbances were normally not allowed. Unless it was information of the highest priority it wouldn’t be sent here. Now that the messenger was at the entrance of the hall, it could be imagined how important this information was.

In these past years Emperor Shakya had received far too many urgent messages. But, over 90% of them were bad news. As the war in the wild universe continued, humanity had suffered defeat after defeat, and there was rarely a case of victory. Even if there were occasional victories, such as the successful elimination of the remnant saint forces in Potala Galaxy, those were simply superficial events.

What humanity needed now was a hearty great victory, a true success that would rouse their morale!

“Where is this news from?” Emperor Shakya’s complexion was solemn. He was afraid that whatever news this was, it wouldn’t be good. Humanity was already hovering on the edge of the abyss and they were finding it hard to weather the continued attacks of the saints.

“Urgent information from the Blood Cloud Galaxy!” The messenger proffered the combat report jade slip with both hands. This information was gathered by the scouts and the rank of the information was decided by the captain of the scouting team. As for what it was, the messenger didn’t know.

“Blood Cloud Galaxy!”

Emperor Shakya’s eyes shot wide open. Could this be a combat reported related to the mysterious person being ambushed by the Legion of Famine?

It wasn’t just Emperor Shakya, but everyone else in the hall felt their hearts tighten.

This mysterious person that had miraculously appeared from nowhere and also had the saints suffer defeat after defeat – they wouldn’t have perished like this, right?

Emperor Shakya took a deep breath and probed the contents of the jade slip.

He had already steeled himself for bad news. However, when he finally looked into the contents of the jade slip, he was shocked silent.

He even suspected that he had misread. He scanned the combat report jade slip several times and after making sure he read everything, he froze like a statue.

“How is this…”

“Senior Emperor Shakya, just what happened?”

All the eyes in the hall were focused on Emperor Shakya. They saw that he remained speechless after looking through the jade slip, and these actions left them a bit worried.

Seeing everyone’s curious gaze, Emperor Shakya finally responded. He looked at the gathered crowd and was at a loss for words.

“It is… you can take a look yourself.”

Emperor Shakya had a strange expression as he passed the jade slip to others.

These people immediately scanned the jade slip. This type of combat report jade slip was originally able to allow several other people to read it at the same time.

Then, as they read through the contents…

They were all left dumbfounded together, almost as if they were living some kind of dream.

This was truly explosive news that would rock the 33 Heavens!

The jade slip had some images recorded within, all of them showing the scene of the Blood Cloud Galaxy after the great battle. There were ruined fragments of celestial bodies all over, and beneath these images were a few lines of simple words:

“A great battle has occurred in the Blood Cloud Galaxy. We have discovered that Fairy Blue Lotus laid down an ambush for the mysterious person in the Blood Cloud Galaxy around a month or two ago and waited for them to rush in. A battle occurred, but as for exactly what happened or how the battle unfolded, we are not sure of the specifics. This is what we know after several days of investigating.

“The main force of the Legion of Famine has been completely annihilated within Blood Cloud Galaxy!

“Blood Cloud Galaxy’s Heavenly Palace and their spirit ships have all been disintegrated to dust!

“The Blood Cloud Galaxy support unit, besides those members that were carrying missions outside, were all destroyed, with not even a single stationed guard remaining!

“Four of the saint generals have gone missing!

“The above situation is suspected to be the work of the mysterious person. More details are being investigated…”

……

For a time, the entire meeting hall fell into silence. Several people felt their jaws drop down as they were unable to believe what was written in the jade slip. But, the images spoke for themselves. The saint race’s Heavenly Palace and the fleets of spirit ships had all been destroyed!

In particular, the nearly invincible Legion of Famine! There should be no force beneath that of a True Divinity capable of resisting their attack, yet such a legion had been annihilated!?

Was this possible?

In fact, it was thought that this mysterious person was incredibly powerful and would be able to escape the Legion of Famine’s pursuit. Of course, this was under the premise that he knew there was an ambush laid out ahead of time for them, so that he could preempt their actions.

But for this mysterious person to eliminate the Legion of Famine, that was a nearly unimaginable matter!

“This… there might be a mistake!”

Diwuhen said with disbelief thick in his voice. This news was simply too shocking. He had personally witnessed the strength of the Legion of Famine and wasn’t able to believe that there truly existed someone with such ability.

“The captain responsible for overseeing the scout team is this old monk’s great direct disciple. He was naturally born with inherent arcane abilities that could peer into the far-off distance and listen to voices on the endless wind. He should have been able to view the image of the saints from afar using some clues in order to analyze his information. He is a calm and alert individual, and even if the information we obtain is slightly different, it shouldn’t be anything too absurd…”

Great Limitless Buddha slowly said. Normally, he was the calmest and most peaceful of the eminent monks, but now even he found it difficult to maintain his composure. As he twisted his buddha beads the speed at which he did so was clearly much faster than normal.

“No matter what the case is, we must be careful. Could this be false news intentionally spread by the saints so that we walk into their trap?” Battle Sovereign To Bagui furrowed his eyebrows, still finding it hard to fully trust the combat report jade slip.

Emperor Shakya shook his head. “The possibility isn’t too likely. Originally, as long as Fairy Blue Lotus led the Legion of Famine to search through Potala Galaxy, we would have suffered defeat sooner or later. As for the Hidden Dragon Galaxy, any accident there would be a good situation for the saints. But, the Legion of Famine suddenly withdrew their forces from Potala Galaxy to return to Blood Cloud Galaxy which in turn gave us a chance to catch our breath.

“Moreover, the Heavenly Palace at Blood Cloud Galaxy was truly destroyed. The fragments of the spirit ships and the Heavenly Palace have been verified to be real. If this really was a charade, then why would they destroy a Heavenly Palace and kill off so many of their disciples, even giving us a chance to stabilize and restore morale? Just what would the goal behind such actions be?”

As Emperor Shakya spoke, everyone fell silent.

Indeed, when two armies faced off in a war, putting on a ruse or faking some weakness wasn’t a rare act. But, those who did such things were always on the losing end. Would the saints really harm themselves to put on such a meaningless act?

“Who is this mysterious person?” The god race’s Empyrean Lanlu muttered, a strange light flashing in her eyes.

“I also wish to know. If there is a chance, I would truly love to see him!”

……..

After Mount Potala obtained news of the Legion of Famine, other human influences also obtained this information.

But, because news of the Legion of Famine’s utter destruction still required proof, no one dared to publicize it. This was a precaution just in case it really was a smokescreen that the saints had put up. If it was, then these human influences would not only be made into jokes but the morale of humanity would also suffer.

So for these past days, whether it was the humans or saints, neither side found it easy to remain tranquil.

In fact, within the Blood Cloud Galaxy, there were even more saint scouts. But they didn’t manage to find much new information.

Lin Ming may control the Legion of Famine, but even at this point in time no one knew of it.

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign didn’t know either.

This was because Lin Ming had used the Magic Cube to completely erase the spirit marks that the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had left within the Legion of Famine, and according to the previous experiences of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, spirit marks being destroyed would only occur because the Legion of Famine had been destroyed.

If the flesh and blood of Famine was destroyed then the spirit marks would naturally disappear. As for someone capable of counter-controlling the flesh and blood of Famine, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had never met such an existence before.

Chapter 2029 – Diverting Troops to the Hidden Dragon Galaxy

Hidden Dragon Galaxy, Good Fortune Saint Palace –

Pah!

A terrifying detonation sounded out and astral essence so thick that it was visible to the naked eye began to spread out in white ripples. The surrounding void shattered as a red beast was smashed in the back by a tall man.

This beast emitted a sorrowful howl as it collapsed to the ground.

Kacha!

Because the large dragon crashed into the ground, a crater formed that was over a hundred miles long.

The tall man landed atop the peak of a rocky mountain. His naked upper body revealed sculpted muscles as hard as rock, making him look like a prideful war god.

This tall man dressed in red was the Good Fortune Saint Son.

This space was a martial arts practice field used by him. It was a small world located in the Good Fortune Saint Palace, and this beast that was wounded here was the hybrid descendant of a God Beast and ancient vicious beast.

Within the Good Fortune Saint Palace, there were super beasts with impure bloodlines being raised and bred all year long. These animals were used as opponents for the genius disciples of the Saint Palace to train with. Although these beasts possessed impure bloodlines, they were still incredibly precious creatures. Even so, here they were used as nothing but sandbags by others. From this one could see how ridiculously wealthy the Good Fortune Saint Palace was.

“Your Highness Saint Son, please take a break. If you hit this red dragon beast again it will die.”

From behind the Good Fortune Saint Son, a wild woman with wheat-colored skin stepped forwards. She carried with her a towel that she used to wipe the sweat from his face.

A cruel and fierce light flashed in the Good Fortune Saint Son’s eyes. He was in an extremely poor mood and was using this training period to vent his anger. Even so, his chest raged with a nest of fire.

This fire was all due to that mysterious person.

The Good Fortune Saint Son had obtained all news available about the Blood Cloud Galaxy at an even earlier time than Emperor Shakya.

If it were normal times, then he would have happily gloated over the losses of Imperial Prince Xishen and Fairy Blue Lotus. He would have even laughed himself awake in his dreams.

But now, the Legion of Famine hadn’t ‘suffered a loss’ but had been completely annihilated. Even four of the saint generals had gone missing!

And no matter how the Good Fortune Saint Son thought about it, he couldn’t imagine how the mysterious person had accomplished all of this.

This was the reason he felt anxious at heart. He sent for repeated investigations into the Blood Cloud Galaxy, yet he didn’t manage to find anything.

The Good Fortune Saint Son didn’t need to be clairvoyant to know that sooner or later, this mysterious person would come looking for him.

And when facing such a character that he knew nothing about, the Good Fortune Saint Son felt a headache even though he had the avatar of Famine. He didn’t know what cards this mysterious opponent possessed or how they had eliminated the Legion of Famine.

“Your Highness Saint Son, there is no need to worry. If things are truly unwell, how about notifying His Majesty the Saint Sovereign?”

The young and beautiful woman tentatively suggested as she saw the Good Fortune Saint Son’s expression.

“Inform His Majesty the Sovereign Ancestor?” The Good Fortune Saint Son immediately frowned and the young woman fell silent.

“Do you think that His Majesty the Saint Sovereign doesn’t know the Legion of Famine has been destroyed? Every martial artist within the Legion of Famine has a spirit mark left behind by His Majesty the Sovereign Ancestor, and whether they are dead or alive, His Majesty the Sovereign Ancestor is well aware!”

The Good Fortune Saint Son coldly muttered.

The 33 Heavenly Daos were the most common Great Daos of the universe; they were no trifling matter. As for Famine, it was being used to swallow up the causal relationship that humanity had with the 33 Heavenly Dao’s Nine Divine Shifts.

But even so, this causal relationship was a part of the Heavenly Dao Laws. For a mortal to dare reverse the rules of the Heavenly Dao, they would be forced to suffer the scourge of the heavens!

This wasn’t something that one could stop just because they wanted to.

And in the process of swallowing the Nine Divine Shifts, Famine and the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign would have to withstand heavenly tribulation.

In the world of martial artists, heavenly tribulation wasn’t some incredibly rare phenomenon. Whenever someone rose to the level of the Heavenly Dao rules they would have to withstand heavenly tribulation.

But the Heavenly Dao rules were also divided into those that were lower and those that were higher. For instance, when a martial artist broke into the Empyrean realm, when a transcendent divine might was created, when a transcendent divine pill was refined, when a God Beast underwent nirvana and grew up, all of these actions would summon heavenly tribulation.

However, these types of heavenly tribulation were only of the lowest order. When compared to the Nine Divine Shifts that Famine was swallowing, the difference was as great as the heavens and earth.

The Good Fortune Saint Son couldn’t imagine just what the heavenly tribulation that fell upon Famine’s body would be like. But, what he knew was that if the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign and Famine could both withstand and survive this heavenly tribulation, that would be an incredible advantage for them!

With swallowing a portion of the Heavenly Dao, Famine might be able to undergo another evolution. If so, then the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign would be another step closer to reaching the boundary Beyond Divinity.

High risks meant high returns. In fact, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had undergone a hundred million years of preparation before daring to attempt something like this. He wanted to try what Famine did 3.6 billion years ago.

The dangers were astronomical. The slightest mistake would mean him disintegrating into nothing!

With this in mind, the Good Fortune Saint Son couldn’t disturb the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign no matter what. In fact, the area where the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had gone into seclusion was a secret of the highest magnitude; not even he knew where it was.

When it came to something like this, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign wouldn’t trust anyone.

In particular, there was still his greatest rival – the Soul Emperor. With this person’s transcendent methods, it wouldn’t be difficult for him to extract any information he desired from the Good Fortune Saint Son’s mind.

This mysterious Soul Emperor was the character that the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign feared most in his life.

Even now, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign didn’t know what endgame the Soul Emperor was playing towards. However, he had no doubts about how vast the Soul Emperor’s ambitions were. If he wanted to contend with the Soul Emperor then he could only rely on Famine.

If Famine was able to evolve further then it would be able to devour the infinite energy, matter, and Laws of the universe, allowing it to become infinitely close to the Beyond Divinity boundary. The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign might even be able to use Famine to swallow the Soul Emperor’s destiny, and perhaps even the karma between the spiritas and the Heavenly Dao!

At that time, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign would no longer fear the Soul Emperor.

The chess game of the world and its secrets, the true thoughts within the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s heart, these were things that the Good Fortune Saint Son only vaguely knew about. The eyes of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign and the Good Fortune Saint Son saw the world differently.

All that the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign saw was this world chess game, and the only ones playing it were the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign and the Soul Emperor. As for everyone else, including the Good Fortune Saint Son, the many saint Empyreans, the Legion of Famine, humanity, Empyrean Divine Dream, everyone else within the world, they were nothing but mere chess pieces!

The only difference was that these board pieces varied between big and small, important and unimportant.

Towards all of this, the Good Fortune Saint Son didn’t feel sad or chagrined at all; this was the inevitable result that came from a disparity of absolute strength.

At the same time, he naturally wasn’t resigned to forever remaining a chess piece. Thus he had to continuously increase his strength.

And presently, this mysterious person before him was a great challenge!

If he couldn’t pass this test and had to rely on the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign who couldn’t and wouldn’t help him, then what qualifications did he have to become a chess player in the future?

Thinking of this, the Good Fortune Saint Son began to seethe with fighting spirit.

If they want to come then come, if they want to fight then fight!

The Good Fortune Saint Son circulated his astral essence and evaporated all the sweat and grime that covered him. Then, he put on his robes and battle armor and stepped out of the small world. He arrived at the official meeting hall, and it was at this time that a scout passed him another combat report jade slip. This jade slip left the Good Fortune Saint Son completely stunned.

This was something that the saint scouts had found in the wreckage of the Heavenly Palace at Blood Cloud Galaxy – it was a crystal fragment with an image contained within.

And coincidentally, this crystal fragment recorded the incomplete image of that mysterious person.

In this image, a mysterious man rode atop a Black Dragon. He held a spear, shattering planets with a wave of his hand!

This recording only lasted a brief moment, but the moment that the Good Fortune Saint Son saw it he felt his heart skip a beat and his complexion turn ugly.

As for the saint race military officers that were standing in the meeting hall, none of them dared to speak as they saw the Good Fortune Saint Son glower upon obtaining this information jade slip. They were afraid of attracting his anger.

For a time, the entire hall fell silent.

The Good Fortune Saint Son’s complexion changed again and again, all sorts of thoughts rapidly racing through his mind.

“The weapon is a spear… the mount is a dragon… how can there be such a coincidence…”

He definitely remembered what occurred over 6000 years ago when he fought in the most shameful battle of his life. During the Monster Emperor’s grand longevity feast, Lin Ming had jumped ranks to defeat him. Moreover, Lin Ming had leapt past an entire large boundary to do so – a Divine Lord had defeated a Holy Lord.

At the time, Lin Ming had taken out a stake for his gambling fight. That was – a dragon egg!

In addition to this mysterious person’s weapon… the Good Fortune Saint Son suddenly felt an ominous premonition cloud his heart.

Although the person in this image, whether it was in cultivation methods or appearance, didn’t match with Lin Ming, the Good Fortune Saint Son still thought that this person might be him.

This was a speculation purely based upon his intuition. In the past when Soaring Feather God King said that Lin Ming had died, the Good Fortune Saint Son was a bit disbelieving of this news. In his opinion, Lin Ming possessed an incredibly tough life. Would he really die so easily?

“It shouldn’t be…”

For a time, the Good Fortune Saint Son felt a cold chill creep in his heart, an unease and nervousness that shot up his back.

Those bitten by a snake would be afraid of ropes for 10 years. The Good Fortune Saint Son was a proud and lofty individual, but he actually held an unusually profound fear towards Lin Ming. This was a scab in his heart that was hard to heal.

“Relay my orders, issue an emergency command! Summon the Empyreans at Saint Convocation Heaven that are guarding the entrance to the wild universe! From the first legion to the sixth legion, have all of them move to the Hidden Dragon Galaxy!”

“What?”

Suddenly hearing the Good Fortune Saint Son’s orders, the saint military officers present were left bewildered. Just what was the Good Fortune Saint Son planning?

Saint Convocation Heaven was the supreme stronghold of the saints and also where their main forces were located. If the first to sixth legions were all transferred here, wouldn’t that just flood the Hidden Dragon Galaxy?

Could so many people be summoned just to deal with one Xiao Moxian?

“This is… His Majesty the Saint Sovereign ordered these armies to guard Saint Convocation Heaven in order to prevent any sneak attacks from the spiritas. If we are only dealing with the humans in the wild universe, they are already a race that has been beaten and broken by us. Is there really a need to draw in so many people?”

“Are you questioning me!?”

The Good Fortune Saint Son frowned, his eyebrows looking like a lion ready to pounce in the next moment. The general gulped and shook his head. After the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign went into seclusion, the Good Fortune Saint Son was now the highest authority of the saints; he would naturally obey these orders.

“What do we do about the spiritas?” Another veteran officer couldn’t help but ask.

The Good Fortune Saint Son thought for a moment before saying, “If the spiritas truly intend on coming do you think those peak Empyreans can stop them? If things really devolve to the worse situation possible then we will give Saint Convocation Heaven to them. But, I have a feeling that they will not come, otherwise His Majesty the Sovereign Ancestor would not have dared to go into seclusion at this time. Perhaps His Majesty has already guessed a part of that old freak Soul Emperor’s plans…”

“This… understood.” The several veteran officers glanced at each other and nodded in agreement.

Chapter 2033 – Scattered Like Leaves

Roar!

The great dark dragon roared upwards, a terrifying dragon roar stirring up a storm. Its giant jaws opened wide and bit down on a primal saints’ ancient space beast!

The ancient space beast was over a hundred miles long and yet it was unexpectedly ripped open by the Black Dragon’s jaws. It cried out miserably, violently struggling, but in the end it couldn’t free itself from the Black Dragon’s grasp. Its body was torn in half and the ruined pieces of flesh and blood were directly swallowed up into the Black Dragon’s stomach.

The Black Dragon didn’t pause. It waved its thick tail, wildly sweeping out like a knife!

Peng! Peng! Peng!

Multiple iron lion battleships were slashed in half by the dragon tail. Space beast after space beast was severed in two by the Black Dragon’s razor-sharp wings!

Storms of energy whipped up as blood filled the skies!

The ancient space beasts were horrifying monsters of the void, but how could they stand side-by-side with a Black Dragon that possessed a king bloodline and had also swallowed the flesh and blood essence of Famine?

Roar!

The Black Dragon threw itself onto a thousand-mile long king of the space beasts. This giant squid was only as long as the Black Dragon’s body, and it wielded its thick tentacles, wanting to pierce through the Black Dragon and push it away.

However, the Black Dragon’s strength was at a level this squid simply couldn’t compare with.

The Black Dragon’s sharp claws dug deep into the ancient space beast’s body. Beneath the rending claws, the massive tentacles of the space beast were truly no different from those of an actual squid; they were torn apart at the roots!

“Attack! Attack that Black Dragon!”

A peak Empyrean cried out in alarm. The ancient space beast being torn apart was his life’s contract beast, and as he saw his own contract beast being ripped apart to the point of death he felt his heart drip blood.

However, just as he shouted out these words he wasn’t able to open his mouth again nor did he have any way to help his contract beast. This was because he could feel an even more terrifying energy storm brewing within the black fortress, one that was completely beyond his control.

Even though they had eight peak Empyreans joining together, in addition to support from the second and third legions, they still couldn’t contend with the might of this black fortress!

It was hard to imagine just how deep and horrifying the background of the character in the black fortress was!

Woosh! Woosh! Woosh!

In that moment, three figures flew out from within Primordius Heavenly Palace; these figures were Lin Ming’s avatars.

They were completely similar to Lin Ming in appearance. As the four of them stood in the center of the array formation, Lin Ming’s aura doubled and doubled yet again!

Lin Ming’s hands weaved together, forming a yin yang diagram. The power of divinity and demons as well as the power of the Holy Scripture and Heavenly Sutra were all fused into the array formation through him.

The other three Lin Mings also used their own methods. Pure strength of essence, energy, and divine constantly flowed into the great array.

For a time, the array formation began to light up like a massive sun. A terrifying strength erupted like ten thousand tsunamis smashing out together.

Bang!

Energy erupted, colliding with the eight peak Empyreans surrounding Primordius Heavenly Palace and causing them to all tumble backwards, vomiting blood!

In that brief moment, their meridians had broken in innumerable places and their blood vitality had been overdrawn, causing their strength to fall to the lowest ditch.

“Ahh!”

Two peak Empyreans cried out in pain. The instant they flew backwards, two incredibly thick beams of light shot out from Primordius Heavenly Palace, directly piercing through these two peak Empyreans!

Puff!

Blood shot out. The mortal bodies of peak Empyreans were incredibly tough. Even after being struck by these terrifying beams of light they didn’t instantly die, but were simply pierced through.

Yet in this battle, being struck by a light beam was no different from immediately dying. The Black Dragon howled into the starry space and swiftly flew over. Its two great claws stretched out, fishing up these two peak Empyreans and swallowing them into its stomach.

As a top rank God Beast, the Black Dragon also possessed the ability to absorb the essence energy of powerhouses and transform it into its own strength. However, it just didn’t possess the abnormal swallowing talent that Famine did.

In this battle, the Black Dragon reaped far too many benefits. The ancient space beasts were recklessly eaten up by it. This scene was similar to a tiger leaping into a flock of sheep, their crimson blood turning space red.

Six peak Empyreans were heavily wounded and two perished. The joint saint legions had taken these eight saint Empyreans as the core of their resistance, and with this strike their energy net they cast over Primordius Heavenly Palace was immediately torn open.

In a flash, the energy of Primordius Heavenly Palace was like a flood bursting out from a shattered dam, recklessly hurtling outwards!

Beams of crimson divine light shot out, passing through the joint saint legions like divine blades!

These beams of light were unstoppable. Every iron lion spirit ship that was struck immediately exploded into space dust, and the ancient space beasts were sliced in half, their blood flying out.

Primordius Heavenly Palace was a giant meat grinder that tore through the joint saint legions. Wherever it went, the amazingly powerful saint legions would disintegrate; this was no different from a one-sided slaughter!

From tens of millions of miles away, the scouts of Mount Potala saw beams of divine light illuminate the horizon.

“What is happening?”

“That’s where the joint saint legions are. Could they have started fighting?”

After the joint saint legions came to a stop and stationed themselves, the human alliance naturally had to keep an eye on their actions. This distance was already the limit that these human scouts could investigate from. If they were to approach any close then there was a high chance they would be discovered by the saints. If so, the consequences could be imagined.

But now, as they saw such a massive change occurring in the joint saint legions, they couldn’t sit idly by.

“Let’s go and take a look! Everyone be careful!”

“Understood!”

Scouting was a dangerous field of work, but at this time it was their duty to gather information on what was occurring.

Six World King level scouts quietly disappeared into the void, rapidly rushing towards the area where the great battle was erupting!

More and more explosions rang through the world. The divine light shining from all over became increasingly bright!

The saint fleets had been scared silly from the amount of slaughter occurring. They were all top elites, but in a battle where the disparity in strength was so massive, and in facing this enemy that was like a death reaper, they simply couldn’t summon the courage to keep fighting.

“Retreat! Everyone, scatter and retreat…”

The primal saint Patriarch endured the pain in his heart to issue this order. But just as he was issuing the order, his voice fell silent, as if his words had been cut in half by an icy saber.

At this time, the primal saint Patriarch felt his entire body turn cold and his pupils contract. Just 100 feet away from him, a black-clothed shadow had torn open space and walked out from a space crack like a death god paying a visit.

This man held a black spear, his eyes overflowing with killing intent!

The primal saint Patriarch immediately understood that this was the mysterious person the Good Fortune Saint Son spoke of!

Although the Good Fortune Saint Son had repeatedly emphasized that this mysterious person was not to be underestimated, if the primal saint Patriarch didn’t see with his own eyes it would be impossible for him to profoundly realize just how true the Good Fortune Saint Son’s words were.

Originally, he even believed that the Good Fortune Saint Son was making a great fuss over nothing to order the six legions of the saints to transfer over to the Hidden Dragon Galaxy. After all, this was all in order to deal with a single mysterious person.

But now, the primal saint Patriarch realized he had been wrong, and wrong to an outrageous degree!

The primal saint Patriarch looked at Lin Ming. His eyes flashed with red light, and in that moment he burnt his blood essence without hesitation!

The blood vitality of a peak saint Empyrean was extremely powerful. Now that it was burnt, it was like a sun rising in the night sky. For the surroundings hundreds of thousands of miles, everyone began to heat up because of this peak saint Empyrean burning up his blood essence!

The primal saints were a brave and bloody clan. Although they were cruel and merciless to other races, when the moment of life or death truly arrived, they wouldn’t shrink backwards!

Several peak Empyreans appeared around Lin Ming. They all started to burn their blood essence together. At this time, none of them had any other choice!

Lin Ming faced four peak Empyreans together; the remaining two were dealt with by the Black Dragon.

As for Primordius Heavenly Palace, Lin Ming had handed down command to Fairy Blue Lotus. She already possessed the ability to command the Legion of Famine, and now that the flesh and blood of Famine had been fused into her, commanding them was even easier.

The reason Lin Ming didn’t have Fairy Blue Lotus under body metamorphosis was to have her command the Legion of Famine in the most clear-headed manner possible.

More beams of light shot out. Another spirit ship was torn apart!

And it was now that Lin Ming attacked!

Four peak Empyreans stood in four different directions. Lin Ming swept out his spear, first targeting the primal saint Patriarch!

The Patriarch was the strongest of the four but he was Lin Ming’s first target. This was self-confidence that stemmed from his own strength!

Lin Ming’s attack wasn’t flashy; it was only a simple straight thrust. But, his speed was too fast, surpassing the rate with which one could react.

Spear light howled out. Behind Lin Ming, nine great stars floated in the air. Five Dao Palaces opened up together and the power of divinity and demons wildly flooded outwards!

There was simply no time to dodge. The primal saint Patriarch could only roar out loud and take a giant axe to smash down at Lin Ming!

In that instant, Lin Ming and the primal saint Patriarch were like two meteors clashing together in space.

Bang!

Energy ripples visible to the naked eye began spreading outwards. From this single clash, the primal saint Patriarch was hurled backwards like a comet!

The blood vessels on his body had burst open due to the excessive impact force and his arms were stained with blood. The great axe in his hands was pounded into a curve, making it look like a drawn bow.

“Damn it!”

The three other Empyreans roared and rushed towards Lin Ming. Lin Ming’s blood bubbled over with heat. He grasped his long spear, sweeping out!

Peng!

Three peak Empyreans that burnt their blood essence were sent flying away, all of them vomiting blood. This was simply a one-sided massacre!

Just as the primal saint Patriarch recovered, he saw Lin Ming rapidly flying towards him. With another great bellow, he grabbed his great axe and brought it crashing down at Lin Ming’s head.

However, Lin Ming didn’t even attempt to evade. He grasped the Black Dragon Spear and also smashed it outwards.

With another collision, the primal saint Patriarch’s arms fractured and he spat out a mouthful of blood!

His body ripped open like a bag of blood, and even white bones were visible.

Tens of thousands of miles away, everything that occurred fell into the eyes of the human scouts. They used specialized eye techniques to see what was occurring.

Whether it was the black fortress that continued to shoot out beams of divine light or that peerless powerhouse that easily suppressed four peak saint Empyreans, everything left them utterly dumbfounded!

“That person, that must be the mysterious person!”

A scout said with a sound transmission, his heart shocked.

“It must be him, it can only be him!”

The scouts looked at each other, a burning heat visible in their eyes.

Chapter 2036 - Return

Mount Potala Wartime Alliance, the great golden buddha spirit ship –

Emperor Shakya, Great Limitless Buddha, Dark Demon Monarch, and the others were all sitting in a circle around a great table, listening to the report by the scouts.

“The approximate situation is like this!”

The scout captain succinctly said, clearly reiterating the process in which he met the mysterious person. In addition, he took out a battle array disc that had recorded some of the scenes they witnessed.

This was a scene of Lin Ming fighting four peak Empyreans as well as Primordius Heavenly Palace shooting out innumerable light beams, instantly slaying the ancient space beasts and destroying the iron lion battleships.

Seeing the images replayed through the array disc, the Empyreans present were filled with an emotion beyond description.

Shock, excitement, worry, joy, all sorts of emotions swelled up within them, leaving everyone in the hall silent for a long time.

The array disc played on for a full quarter hour. Because the scene was hastily recorded and from very far away, the images were extremely blurry, and even Lin Ming’s face wasn’t clearly recorded.

However, this didn’t prevent the commanders of humanity present from replaying the scenes in their heads.

Such an intense battle had left their hearts surging and their emotions wildly fluctuating. They even felt their blood feverishly boiling over!

In particular, when they saw the Black Dragon bite through the ancient space beast, Lin Ming brutally beating the peak Empyreans, and Primordius Heavenly Palace tearing through the saint fleets like a meat grinder, the martial artists present couldn’t help but grip their fists together, their eyes shining with glory.

To Bagui thumped his own chest. Such an image truly let one vent their anger. He clearly recalled the scene from several days ago when they had fought with the second saint legion. That sort of feeling where he hated the enemy to the bone and yet wasn’t able to do anything to them left To Bagui feeling crazed.

Humanity had been suppressed for far too long. Now, they finally saw hope. Even though they were still drowning in the endless night, they finally saw the first rays of dawn.

“This mysterious person is simply a legend! When it comes to him, there is nothing he cannot accomplish!”

Dark Demon Monarch said, praising Lin Ming from his heart. In truth he had already approximately judged Lin Ming’s strength; he was someone that surpassed a peak Empyrean, an existence that could reluctantly be called invincible amongst Empyreans. Such combat strength was in truth superior to Emperor Shakya but worse than that of a True Divinity.

According to common logic, if a person didn’t reach the True Divinity realm, it would be hard to play a pivotal role in a war between two races.

But reality defied all expectations in such a bizarre manner. This mysterious person, with his strength alone, was nearly able to reverse the entire tide of the war!

“Perhaps you should no longer call him that mysterious person, but instead call him Lin Ming.”

Emperor Shakya smiled as he spoke. It had been many years since Emperor Shakya had last revealed such a heartfelt smile.

“Lin Ming… you are sure it is him?”

Dark Demon Monarch glanced over at Emperor Shakya. In truth, he hadn’t had much contact with Lin Ming. The only time he saw Lin Ming was at the Monster Emperor’s grand longevity banquet, and the rest of his understandings had come from rumors and hearsay.

“It’s him!”

Jun Bluemoon firmly nodded as he stroked the rusty sword in his arms. Back when he participated in the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting and fought with Lin Ming, that battle still remained a vivid memory.

Emperor Shakya said, “He referred to Xiao Moxian as Xian’er. In the entire 33 Heavens, there are only several people who would call Xiao Moxian by this name and care for her so much. In addition with that Black Dragon and spear, so many coincidences joining together mean it is no longer a coincidence, but the truth.

“Lin Ming hasn’t died! He has returned!

“He is someone who always brings about miracles. After more than 6000 years passing, he will surely bring us a favorable turn!”

Emperor Shakya tightly clenched the armrest of his stone chair. It could be seen just how excited he was.

Many young disciples noticed Emperor Shakya’s actions. In their view, Emperor Shakya was the high commander of the Mount Potala Wartime Alliance and could be called the second leader of humanity. He was always calm and rarely lost his composure.

“Is this person really so fierce? If he doesn’t have the strength of a True Divinity could he really bring us a favorable turn? The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign is still a powerhouse even amongst True Divinities.”

A disciple of the younger generation couldn’t help but say.

The young disciples that were able to stand in this meeting hall were all geniuses. Most of them were born in the wild universe, and by the time they were born, Lin Ming had already ‘died’. They had never seen Lin Ming and had only heard tales about him. They knew that he was the man who brought the Asura Decree to humanity and who possessed talent far surpassing all others in the 33 Heavens.

In the history books of humanity, Lin Ming was described as invincible amongst the heavens and earth, unique and singular. As the stories of him were retold again and again, Lin Ming eventually became an omnipotent presence.

Towards this, some young geniuses were incredibly proud and worked hard with Lin Ming as their goal.

But there were also some young geniuses who remained suspicious about these tales. They thought that humanity had propped up the Lin Ming of the past and had nearly deified him. They believed this was an attempt to give the younger generation a boost of confidence and also so that the younger generation could feel comforted and infatuated with their own possibilities. After all, it was human nature to boast about the heroes of one’s own race.

Sable Ink was the second type of person. When she heard the fanatical Linmaniacs chatter away, she would often ask, “If he was so fierce, how come he’s dead?”

This single question often silenced the mouths of many people.

However, upon receiving news that Lin Ming hadn’t died, a strange color appeared in Sable Ink’s eyes. She traced her scythe, a feeling that was hard to place filling her heart.

“Everyone adjust yourselves. Four hours from now, we will set out!”

Emperor Shakya suddenly said. Lin Ming’s appearance had lifted their morale, but now was not the time to celebrate any victories because there was still an extremely important matter to resolve. That was – Xiao Moxian’s safety.

Previously, because the second and third saint legions were stationed nearby, the Mount Potala Wartime Alliance was simply unable to enter. But now that the periphery was cleared out, Mount Potala would naturally take this chance to rush in.

No matter how much help they could provide Lin Ming, they still had to try their best.

The Hidden Dragon Galaxy was amazingly large and there was no sound transmission mark that could be used to locate Xiao Moxian. Thus, finding her wouldn’t be easy at all. Even the Good Fortune Saint Son had failed to do so for several years. It couldn’t even be compared to looking for a needle in the sea.

In terms of war strength, they weren’t able to compete with Lin Ming. But in terms of looking for people they possessed an advantage. In the end, it was always best to have more people.

Mount Potala’s great golden buddha as well as many spirit ships slowly broke through the void, driving deep into the Hidden Dragon Galaxy.

As Mount Potala embarked towards the depths of the Hidden Dragon Galaxy, the Good Fortune Saint Son had also obtained similar news.

The second and third legions had been routed, but the truth was that most spirit ships had survived. This included those people that belonged to the Good Fortune Saint Palace’s intelligence network.

They completely reported the scene of Lin Ming routing the joint saint legions to the Good Fortune Saint Son.

Because they were closer to Lin Ming, the information they were able to record was much more detailed than that of the scouts from Mount Potala.

At this time, in front of the Good Fortune Saint Son, the phantom projections from the battle array disc constantly flashed and changed. Iron lion spirit ships burst apart one after another and numerous ancient space beasts were slain.

The entire hall was filled with only these silent images, without a single other sound. Several dozen high level saint officers held their breath. Even the drop of a needle could be heard in the present atmosphere.

Such a situation left them all in fear and apprehension. They all knew just how stimulating this must be to the Good Fortune Saint Son!

It had to be known that the several saint legions had been transferred here under the orders of the Good Fortune Saint Son in order to deal with that mysterious person. But before all the legions had fully gathered, they had already been routed by Lin Ming, suffering a catastrophic defeat!

In front of the mysterious person, the saints had already suffered two great defeats. This was undoubtedly a great blow to the eternally arrogant Good Fortune Saint Son!

At this time the Good Fortune Saint Son was like a volcano ready to erupt at any second. However, as the images of the array disc finally ended, the Good Fortune Saint Son remained ghostly silent.

His elbows were propped up on the table and his face was hidden in the shadows of his arms. It was impossible to see his expression.

The messenger that brought over the battle array disc didn’t even dare to take a breath, lest he be killed by the Good Fortune Saint Son in a fit of anger.

“Draw back!”

The Good Fortune Saint Son suddenly said. The messenger felt as if he had been granted a pardon from a capital crime; he left the hall with his entire forehead dripping sweat.

The military officers all looked at the Good Fortune Saint Son. They never thought he would remain so quiet.

“The rest of you can also draw back.”

The Good Fortune Saint Son waved his hand and stood up. From his standing position, everyone could see that his eyes had turned blood red, like a wild animal in a seething rage. They all felt a sense of dread as they looked at him.

The military officers glanced at each other and left the meeting hall in droves. Finally, the only one left remaining was the Good Fortune Saint Son.

The Good Fortune Saint Son gripped the armrest of his chair, his eyes sparkling with thick killing intent.

“So in the end it was you after all. This… is our predestined battle…”

Chapter 2039 - Dawn

Empyrean Evernight turned his head with disbelief. He saw that behind him was a black-clothed man with an indifferent expression playing on his face. The eyes of this black-clothed man seemed to contain the blood ponds of hell.

This man was Lin Ming.

Lin Ming had already explored the Hidden Dragon Galaxy for a long time. If he wanted to, he could easily travel from one end of the Hidden Dragon Galaxy to the other in a single day.

However, while traversing straight through the Hidden Dragon Galaxy was easy, wanting to find someone in it was far too hard. Whether it was looking for Xiao Moxian or the Good Fortune Saint Son, it was no different from searching for a needle in a sea.

Fortunately Lin Ming possessed the Magic Cube. After he routed the second and third saint legions, Fairy Blue Lotus had purposely captured several martial artists so that Lin Ming could interrogate them.

Lin Ming read through the memories of these people using the Magic Cube. Compared to using a soul searching technique, this method was a hundred times more detailed. Moreover, in most situations it was extremely difficult to use the soul searching technique on an Empyrean and there were many limits.

Lin Ming followed the clues to find several other saint strongholds. He used 10 days to entirely destroy these strongholds. Afterwards, he captured new saints and obtained newer information from them using the Magic Cube.

For every piece of valuable information, Lin Ming would chase it down to its source. Finally, in another saint stronghold, he found a sound transmission mark of Good Fortune Saint Palace!

This sound transmission mark was concealed as an ordinary jade slip. But with the Magic Cube, Lin Ming managed to easily find it.

According to this sound transmission mark, Lin Ming arranged a sound transmission array and was able to lock onto the origin. This was also New Ming Planet.

The truth was that New Ming Planet’s coordinates were no longer at its original location.

Mount Potala had New Ming Planet’s location listed in its records. But, because the saints wanted to hide it from humanity, and in particular prevent Lin Ming from easily finding it, the Good Fortune Saint Son had used the great strength of Famine’s avatar to push New Ming Planet to another location.

This distance wasn’t too far from the Good Fortune Saint Son’s encirclement ring. It was convenient to manage and also easy to conceal.

Thus, the Good Fortune Saint Son could slowly torture the citizens of New Ming Planet and force Xiao Moxian to reveal herself.

The Good Fortune Saint Son didn’t worry that Xiao Moxian wouldn’t know where New Ming Planet’s new position was, because she had left her informants on it.

As long as the Good Fortune Saint Son could capture Xiao Moxian, then he could vent his anger on her, bringing his hatred of over 6000 years to completion. Moreover, he could use her to threaten Lin Ming!

Imagine. If Xiao Moxian were to be swallowed into Famine’s avatar and then the Good Fortune Saint Son were to use Famine’s avatar to fight Lin Ming, just what scene would that be?

Because Lin Ming would fear to harm those he loved, this would place the Good Fortune Saint Son in an invincible position.

This was the Good Fortune Saint Son’s final plan; he was simply too frightened by Lin Ming. Even with Famine’s avatar on his side, the Good Fortune Saint Son didn’t feel safe. Thus, he wanted to grab hold of Xiao Moxian. This would be tantamount to grasping hold of Lin Ming’s weak point. Like this, he could slowly torment Lin Ming to death.

The Good Fortune Saint Son looked forwards to capturing Xiao Moxian and then fighting with Lin Ming. He wanted to see the utter hatred and loathing that would cloud Lin Ming’s face.

Only like this would he be able to resolve his 6000 plus years of hatred.

However, although the Good Fortune Saint Son had found a good method to deal with Lin Ming, he miscalculated Lin Ming’s ability to gather information. In just two months Lin Ming found the new position of New Ming Planet.

But what a pity, Lin Ming didn’t find the Good Fortune Saint Son on New Ming Planet. Still, this wasn’t a major problem.

Lin Ming quietly reached out and grabbed Empyrean Evernight’s neck. His fingers squeezed down and Empyrean Evernight felt his own neck crack apart. Empyrean Evernight’s eyeballs bulged out and he desperately grabbed hold of Lin Ming’s hand, wanting to crush his wrist.

However, Lin Ming’s mortal body was too formidable and his strength too terrifying. Nine stars appeared behind him and layers of starlight fell upon his body. Empyrean Evernight was a dog stuck in an iron trap, unable to break free.

“You… you…”

Empyrean Evernight uttered with difficulty. And at this time, all of the other saint martial artists were in a dire situation. Those that surrounded Lin Ming had faces full of shock and fear. They couldn’t imagine just what kind of person could be so ridiculously powerful that they could approach Empyrean Evernight without him noticing and then use a single spear strike to pierce through his protective astral essence. After all, the body of a saint Empyrean would have been tempered for so much and for so long that it was as hard as an Empyrean spirit treasure.

As the spear penetrated through Empyrean Evernight’s body, he didn’t even suffer much impact. This was proof that the spear which broke into his body did so as easily as a knife slicing into tofu.

Kacha!

With a loud crack, Lin Ming twisted and directly broke Empyrean Evernight’s neck.

In front of Lin Ming, a lower Empyrean was simply far too weak.

A saint Empyrean possessed an extremely tenacious vitality. Even if their chest were pierced through or their neck were broken, they would still hang onto that single last breath without dying.

With wide and large eyes like a black fish, Empyrean Evernight stared at the black-clothed man, no longer able to speak.

Lin Ming casually waved his hand and threw Empyrean Evernight down onto the square of the holy mountain. This was also right in front of the statues of himself and Xiao Moxian.

Lin Ming had already sealed away all the astral essence within Empyrean Evernight. Now, he was even weaker than a common mortal.

Seeing that previously cruel and insufferably arrogant saint Empyrean being tossed onto the ground like a dead dog, all of the humans present were shocked. Who was this man in the sky?

Although those in the square were mostly common mortals, they still knew what concept an Empyrean was. If there was someone capable of pinching an Empyrean to death like an ant, just how powerful would that person be?

Even Emperor Shakya, the second-ranked powerhouse of humanity, might not be able to accomplish this!

“Everyone!” Lin Ming floated above the holy mountain, flying before his own statue. He exuded the aura of a king throughout the entire square, causing everyone to quiet down.

Every human looked up at Lin Ming with awe and worship in their eyes.

To them, Lin Ming was like a god sent down from the heavens.

Lin Ming pointed towards this shivering Empyrean Evernight and said, “For anyone that comes up and spits on him, you will receive a pot of cooked meat and 10 jins of rice.”

These words were calmly spoken, but as they fell onto the ears of the human commoners, it caused them to explode with fervor!

Towards this Empyrean Evernight, these people wished that they could eat his raw flesh and drink deeply of his blood!

Now that they could spit on him and also obtain such luxurious food, all of them were bubbling with excitement!

There were immediately human commoners that pushed themselves forwards, wanting to spit on Empyrean Evernight. For a time, the square that could hold 100,000 people suddenly fell into chaos.

“Do not crowd forwards!”

Lin Ming only spoke a single phrase, but his words contained a calming magic to them. Immediately, the square of 100,000 people suddenly fell quiet.

Everyone shuffled towards Lin Ming’s statue in an orderly manner. Then, they spat on Empyrean Evernight. Some people would be so angry that they would even stomp on him a few times to vent their hatred.

An old man with the appearance of a beggar coughed up an especially thick glob of phlegm and spat it onto Empyrean Evernight’s face.

A seven or eight year old child untied his pants and immediately began peeing on Empyrean Evernight’s head.

When would a proud and lofty Empyrean be treated like this? To be stepped on by a flock of commoners and be recklessly humiliated?

Slowly, Empyrean Evernight started to suffocate beneath the torment of despair and humiliation. With his neck broken and his astral essence sealed away, severing his meridians to commit suicide was not possible. Even moving his fingers was incredibly difficult.

After the common citizens spat on Empyrean Evernight they walked forwards and took their food. The saint martial artists that were responsible for guarding the food were already scared silly. Their faces were paper white and none of them dared to stop any of the humans.

The common human mortals grabbed the fragrant rice and cooked meat and began eating it in great gulps. After starving for a couple of months, suddenly having such a delicious meal was the greatest happiness of their lives…

As for Empyrean Evernight, he was already submerged in spit.

The several saint martial artists drew back with pale faces, wanting to disappear into the crowd. But as they were about to succeed, Lin Ming suddenly turned his head and coldly said, “Where do you plan on going?”

The several saint martial artists turned to flee. Some of the more intelligent ones hurtled towards the commoners, wanting to use them as hostages to threaten Lin Ming.

However, no matter what they tried, they couldn’t change their fates.

Black spear light shot out from Lin Ming’s fingertips, sinking into the bodies of these people like arrows. Their bodies imploded as their organs and meridians burst apart.

Then, they slumped to the ground with fresh blood flowing out in streams.

As the human commoners saw these saint powerhouses die so violently and look so pathetic after death, they began to cheer out loud.

Even shy young girls no longer feared these miserable corpses.

Seeing this, Lin Ming smiled from his heart. He slowly flew into the skies. New Ming Planet still had several thousand saint minions here and he wanted to purge all of them from this planet, to return an easy and comfortable life to the people of New Ming Planet.

As Lin Ming flew away, many people fell to their knees in worship. Their faces were filled with admiration as sweet words of praise gushed out from their lips.

They knelt on the ground for a long time without rising back up. A young 11-12 year old child pulled at his father’s hem and said with some hesitation, “Father, that brave and amazing big brother just now, he… does he look a bit like this statue?”

The young and naïve voice was especially crisp in the quiet square. As the people heard it, they were left in a daze.

Look like?

It didn’t feel like it, but for some unknown reason, the man actually did bear an amazing likeness…

Everyone glanced at each other, unable to find the words to express themselves. But, no matter who that black-clothed man was, there was one thing they were sure of – the endless night had finally passed. That single ray of light that illuminated the way forwards had begun to grow into a bright and dazzling dawn!

In the quiet square, some people began to cry. A young girl in rags was too excited. She couldn’t contain her emotions as great drops of tears fell down her cheeks. Finally, she fell onto the floor, her face covered with her hands as she wept away all her bitterness.

Husbands and wives held each other, their tears freely flowing. Even as they wiped away their tears, more fell down to replace them.

A man gripped his fists and roared into the heavens…

On this day, throughout New Ming Planet, there were crowds of people who lost their composure. They ran through the streets cheering, telling everyone that the powerhouses of humanity had returned!

They had endured so many trials and tribulations, and now those times were coming to an end!

Tears recklessly flowed down. Shouts and screams filled the skies.

After having experienced true tribulations and death, and now facing sudden freedom and victory, there was no one that was able to maintain their calm.

In particular, when people looked up and saw the Heavenly Palace that represented the might of the saints being destroyed, all of them exploded in shouts like volcanoes that finally erupted after being suppressed for too long.

“Humanity forever!”

Someone shouted out. More and more people chanted this phrase until it became a tide that rushed through all 100,000 cities of New Ming Planet, their voices echoing into the horizon!

At this moment, everyone’s hearts were connected as one.

And in the joyous crowd, no one noticed a beggar-like woman hurriedly rushing into an alley as she saw this scene.

She entered a shabby and unremarkable room. Then, she opened a hidden concealing array formation there, revealing a hidden chamber…

Within this chamber, she placed a jade slip onto the center of a sound transmission array formation. As she did this, her heartbeat accelerated and her face flushed red. It was clear she was shivering from excitement.

She had to report everything that happened on New Ming Planet, including the image of that mysterious black-clothed man to Xiao Moxian.

This woman was the informant Xiao Moxian had left on New Ming Planet.

She believed that the sudden appearance of this mysterious powerhouse would truly leave Empyrean Demon Fairy delighted…

Chapter 2040 - Voice

Within a dark nebula of the Hidden Dragon Galaxy –

Xiao Moxian stood before a bronze mirror, quietly tidying her military garb. At this time, the door to her room was pushed open and a red-dressed woman walked in, speaking in a soft voice.

“Little Sister Xian’er.”

Xiao Moxian turned and saw that the woman who came in was Mu Qianyu.

Xiao Moxian pressed her lips together as if she wanted to say something. But in the end, she couldn’t find just where to start. She silently turned back and started to comb her long hair.

“Have you decided that you will go to New Ming Planet?”

Mu Qianyu asked, her mood complex. Her voice was filled with sadness. In these past years it had always been Xiao Moxian taking the burden for those around her. Ever since the news of Lin Ming’s death, she had carried far too many things on her shoulders.

Xiao Moxian bitterly shook her head.

“Although it is said to be returning to New Ming Planet, the truth is that this will be a final showdown with the Good Fortune Saint Son… when we go to New Ming Planet and cross the space blockade, the Good Fortune Saint Son will sense it. He will surely be waiting nearby in ambush. With the avatar of Famine on his side, he will be much faster than we are. It will inevitably devolve into a life or death slaughter. We… will not be able to reach New Ming Planet.”

Xiao Moxian was well aware of what plot the Good Fortune Saint Son was planning. In fact, this couldn’t be called any plot at all, but a clumsy means to force her out of hiding.

But this clumsy method was one that Xiao Moxian was unable to ignore. Even if she turned a blind eye to her own people, her battle with the Good Fortune Saint Son was inevitable.

Since that was the case, she might as well launch an attack on her own initiative.

To die proudly and heroically in battle would be better than being slowly searched for and hunted down like some prey. In this final battle, blood was sure to stain the starry space. To her, the best result she could think of was sacrificing herself and heavily wounding the Good Fortune Saint Son, so that her followers would have a chance to escape.

The atmosphere in the room became heavy and solemn. Mu Qianyu picked up and separated Xiao Moxian’s long black hair, slowly combing it. Her movements were slow and meticulous.

During these past years, Mu Qianyu had helped Xiao Moxian comb her hair more than once. She truly did cherish and love Xiao Moxian. Ever since Mo Eversnow left, it had been Xiao Moxian who kept everything together.

But because of the limit of her strength, there was actually very little that Mu Qianyu could help Xiao Moxian with.

“Big Sister, you cannot go. Stay here with Big Sister Xingxuan. After our battle with the Good Fortune Saint Son, no matter what the result is, he will not continue searching through this nebula.”

As Xiao Moxian spoke, Mu Qianyu’s hand suddenly froze.

Mu Qianyu bit her lips, not knowing what to say. She didn’t want to stay, but what could she change if she went? She would only die in vain, and if she were to fall into the hands of the Good Fortune Saint Son, the consequences would be unimaginable.

If something occurred that she couldn’t revert, even if she died she wouldn’t have the face to see Lin Ming.

Xiao Moxian had already guessed Mu Qianyu’s thoughts. She held onto Mu Qianyu’s hand and brightly smiled, and there were actually innumerable meanings contained in this smile. Mu Qianyu couldn’t help it as tears began freely flowing down her cheeks.

Perhaps this might be the last time she would be able to help Xiao Moxian comb her hair. When everything was finished, Xiao Moxian and Lin Ming would still need someone to worship and clean their spirit tablets…

Mu Qianyu covered her mouth, her tears quietly falling. And at this time, Lin Huang pushed open the door and stepped in. “Mother, Aunty Mu…”

Mu Qianyu quickly dried her tears. “Ah, Huang’er came too.”

“Mm.” Seeing Mu Qianyu’s wet face, Lin Huang could approximately guess what had just happened. But, he didn’t speak of it.

In these past years Lin Huang had already broken into the half-step Empyrean realm. Skyrend Godlord’s original advice had been for Lin Huang not to be hasty in reaching this boundary. However, because the saints invaded the wild universe, Lin Huang had no time to wait. He broke into the half-step Empyrean realm about 500 years ahead of time, but even if he did so he still wasn’t able to change anything.

He possessed an Empyrean level combat strength, and even amongst Empyreans he wasn’t considered weak.

But if he were to face the Good Fortune Saint Son it would be like a little white rock facing off against the bright moon; the disparity was too great.

With the avatar of Famine on his side, the Good Fortune Saint Son was far, far too strong, strong to the point that no human alive besides Empyrean Divine Dream could battle him. Even Emperor Shakya was not his match.

“Huang’er, what matter are you looking for me about?” Xiao Moxian noticed Lin Huang holding a sound transmission array disc in his hands. This was naturally information that he had just received.

Towards this, Xiao Moxian was already numb. What news could be worse than the present situation?

“There seems to have been an emergency development. This is urgent news sent from New Ming Planet…”

As Lin Huang spoke, he set the array disc on the table. After placing a violet sun crystal within it, a projection shot out from the array disc.

This projection was a bit confusing and chaotic at the start. There were great crowds of excited people eating food in joy and revelry. These grains that martial artists wouldn’t take a liking to were actually the most treasured delicacies to mortals.

Seeing this, Xiao Moxian and Mu Qianyu were stunned.

These projections were all scenes of the people of New Ming Planet cheering. The originally suffering and starving citizens were actually beating the saints and oppressing them. They even saw someone dead on the ground, submerged in spit and phlegm. This person was someone that had been previously reported about – Empyrean Evernight, New Ming Planet’s ruler!

“This is…”

Xiao Moxian’s face was filled with disbelief. An Empyrean actually ended up in such a miserable fate where they drowned to death in the spit of common mortals?

Xiao Moxian’s first thought was that Emperor Shakya or Empyrean Divine Dream had done this.

But soon, the explanation in the reported refuted her eyes. According to Xiao Moxian’s informant, the one who saved New Ming Planet was a man of mysterious origins who had never been seen before.

He wore black clothes and grasped a spear in his hands. He was proud and tall, his strength terrifying.

The battle array disc also held a glimpse of this man.

The black-clothed man wielded a black spear. As he ruined the saint palaces atop New Ming Planet and the statues of the Good Fortune Saint Son, he did it as easily as kicking down sand sculptures.

And as Xiao Moxian saw this man’s figure, her eyes could no longer move from him.

“Freeze it!”

Xiao Moxian nearly cried out loud, her voice filled with excitement. Lin Huang was bewildered; his mother rarely lost her composure like this.

“What is it?”

Lin Huang was unsure of what was happening, but he still paused the battle array disc.

The images recorded in the array disc weren’t too clear; this was because the distance was too great. It only recorded half of the black-clothed man’s blurry face, and because the speed of the spear was too fast, it was impossible to clearly see.

For this sort of image capturing array formation, recording this was already the limit.

Xiao Moxian’s eyes shined brilliantly as she stared at this man’s figure. Mu Qianyu was also dazed. For a time, no one knew what to say. All she felt was her heart rapidly racing, as if she had lost and then found the most important thing in her life.

This demeanor, that aura, that sweeping black spear, all of it was an eternal mark that fell onto her heart. Even through the river of time, even through the changed appearance, there were many things carved into the bone that couldn’t be changed.

Xiao Moxian and Mu Qianyu looked at each other. In truth, they couldn’t be sure of what they were seeing. However, they had shared a bed with that person, passed nights with that person, had crossed through life or death challenges with that person and had formed a connection of the heart. This was an inexplicable feeling, an intuition that came from the depths of one’s heart.

However, in this environment of despair, underneath the strong feelings of longing, this touch of intuition was more than enough to leave Xiao Moxian and Mu Qianyu incomparably excited!

“Go and call your Aunty Qin over.”

Xiao Moxian said, her voice shaking. Lin Huang nodded.

A moment later, Qin Xingxuan appeared in Xiao Moxian’s room. She had brought Lin Ming’s little sister Lin Xiaoge with her.

“What is it?”

Qin Xingxuan and Lin Xiaoge looked towards the projection of the array disc. As they saw the black-clothed man wielding a spear, a trace of confusion appeared in the eyes of the two women.

“He is…”

Qin Xingxuan gently covered her mouth.

“Let’s wait a moment before we speak about it.”

Xiao Moxian took a deep breath and calmed her mind. She untied the band around her neck and took out an ancient and simple necklace.

This necklace was the Thousand Mile Heartlink!

This was also the last time the Thousand Mile Heartlink could be used. This necklace had Lin Ming’s soul mark recorded within. If Xiao Moxian activated the array formation within the necklace, she could use it to search for Lin Ming. As long as they existed in the same world she could use it to contact Lin Ming. Of course, this was only true if Lin Ming was alive.

Seeing the Thousand Mile Heartlink, Mu Qianyu held her breath. She was afraid that everything occurring was an illusion.

They only had a single chance. She didn’t want her hopes to be dashed away; she would rather die.

Seeing the Thousand Mile Heartlink, Lin Huang’s dry lips twitched. He certainly knew what the function of the Thousand Mile Heartlink was. For all the years he knew her, his mother had taken this necklace as her life’s most precious treasure. When he thought about the response that his mother and Aunty Mu had, could it possibly be…

As Lin Huang realized this impossible possibility, his heart began to speed up.

At the same time, similar reactions occurred with Qin Xingxuan and Lin Xiaoge.

Xiao Moxian’s shivering fingers laid the Thousand Mile Heartlink down on the obsidian tabletop. Her movements were slow, as if she were afraid that any sudden actions would wake her from this dream.

Xiao Moxian carefully injected her energy into the Thousand Mile Heartlink.

The candlelight in the room gently swayed, the light dim. In this environment, the Thousand Mile Heartlink flashed with a faint light.

The Thousand Mile Heartlink recorded both Xiao Moxian and Lin Ming’s spirit marks. Only Xiao Moxian could activate it.

At this time, Xiao Moxian’s heart was caught in her throat. She was afraid, afraid that this was all an illusion. She was afraid that the Thousand Mile Heartlink’s array formation would suddenly break down. She was afraid of any possible accident.

As everyone’s hearts were gripped, approaching despair, that simple necklace began to gently and slowly, as if it was just now awakening from a dream that had lasted for almost seven thousand years, start to emit a vague and long-lost voice…

Chapter 2042 – Bloodline Connection

Right after Xiao Moxian flew up, Mu Qianyu, Qin Xingxuan, and Lin Xiaoge all flew towards Primordius Heavenly Palace.

Atop the palace walls, the women looked towards Lin Ming, their eyes flowing with tears.

They threw themselves into his arms. He tightly held onto them. At this time, all tribulations, all grievances, all the pain and sorrow they suffered was burned away in this moment of happiness.

No one spoke because there were no words that needed to be said. Their hearts had become one and they could clearly feel the innermost feelings of each other.

Xiao Moxian, Mu Qianyu, and Qin Xingxuan were like fish while Lin Ming was like water. Their lives were linked together, unable to be separated!

Lin Ming held onto them for a long time before slowly separating. He carefully wiped away the tears that fell down each woman’s face and said in a soft voice, “You have all suffered hardships…”

More tears fell. Mu Qianyu said, “In these past years it has been Little Sister Xian’er supporting us.”

“Mm, I understand.”

Lin Ming gently stroked Xiao Moxian’s cheek. She had abandoned her own race to follow him, but soon after he had disappeared and everyone had assumed he had died. Thus, Xiao Moxian and her unborn child had arrived at the wild universe without him. Facing the great wilderness and the covetous gaze of the saints, the burden she had to endure could be imagined.

As he thought back to that innocent and strangely eccentric young girl, that image still reverberated in Lin Ming’s heart. The Xiao Moxian of that time had been filled with happiness and perpetual joy.

Step by step, she had walked to where she was today. From a naïve young girl she had become an Empyrean of humanity who carried the lives of several dozen billion subjects on her shoulders, helping in propping up the fate of the human race. Such a gradual transformation left Lin Ming even more in love with her.

Lin Ming pulled Xiao Moxian’s hand and tightly held onto her. He gently kissed her forehead and then bent down to whisper in her ear, “With me here, everything will be fine again.”

As these words fell onto Xiao Moxian’s ears, she felt her heart ache. Emotions surged in her like a raging sea.

Yes. No matter where it was or when it was, no matter how difficult the situation was, as long as he was here he would use his broad shoulders to prop up the heavens for them.

In the past, within the Asura Road, she and Lin Ming had faced the pursuit of Tian Mingzi…

After returning from the Asura Road, she had to face the surprise of her unborn child, the marriage proposal of the Good Fortune Saint Son, as well as the rage of Empyrean Demondawn…

And beyond that, when the great calamity of humanity erupted ahead of time and when almost all Empyreans felt the situation was hopeless…

It was him. It was he who had faced all of this without turning back, who had faced all of this without hesitation. Leaving behind only the image of his back, he silently shouldered the responsibility, experiencing unimaginable difficulties and tribulations before finally creating a miracle and changing everything.

Time and time again he had made the impossible possible, writing his own legend as he lived.

He was a man who she could always feel peace of mind to stand behind.

Xiao Moxian knew that she could never leave him. Every inch of her flesh, every drop of her blood, her entire soul, everything she was belonged to him…

“Yu’er, Xingxuan…” Lin Ming hugged Mu Qianyu and Qin Xingxuan into his chest, feeling their hearts beat in tandem, feeling their breath against him. Originally, these two women should have remained safely in the lower realms. Although they wouldn’t live overly grand lives, they would still live lives that all mortals would envy. However, they had been caught in the great stormy war between the saints and humanity and were forced to drift in desolate loneliness for thousands of years. Lin Ming felt that he had been unfair to the both of them. Secretly he firmed his resolve that these two women would never be harmed in any way again.

And finally, Lin Xiaoge…

He traced and patted her head. His parents had already passed away. Although he had been at the side of his parents, protecting them until the end of their lives and finally seeing them leave with smiles on their face, Lin Xiaoge had actually never managed to see her parents one final time. This would inevitably be a regret deep in her heart.

“Xiaoge, you’ve grown up…”

After nearly seven thousand years, Lin Ming said the exact same words he said to her so long ago…

The first time he said these words was when he returned to the Sky Spill Continent and saw Lin Xiaoge suppress her rivals at the martial arts meeting, winning the crown of champion.

At that time, Lin Xiaoge had been in her prime. She had a beautiful figure and the vitality of a youth. When Lin Ming had said she had grown up then, he had been referring to her physical maturity.

But this time, Lin Ming was referring to the evolution of her mind.

After experiencing tribulations for thousands of years, even a carefree person would grow up…

“Big Brother, I’m doing well.”

Lin Xiaoge grabbed Lin Ming’s hand and firmly hugged him, her actions speaking louder than words.

The brother and sister separated after some time. Lin Xiaoge looked at Lin Ming and said, “Big Brother… do you know what happened to our parents? I have been in the wild universe all these years so I never had a chance to return to the Sky Spill Continent and see them…”

Lin Ming sighed. He shook his head and said, “I’ll tell you everything that happened later.”

Seeing Lin Ming’s eyes, Lin Xiaoge was startled, as if she suddenly realized something. She slowly nodded. In truth, when she asked this question she had already faintly guessed the answer.

It was impossible for her parents to live for such a long time…

And at this time, Lin Ming looked at the approaching Lin Huang.

The first time that Lin Ming saw Lin Huang, he could feel a faint bloodline connection from his body. Even without Xiao Moxian explaining things to him he could still guess that this was his child.

As Lin Huang saw his father turn and regard him, he was a bit wary.

To Lin Huang, his father was the god in his heart, and the person he respected and worshipped the most. Now that he actually met his father, his heart began to speed up.

He tidied his robes and stepped forwards. Then, he kneeled before Lin Ming and deeply bowed in obeisance.

“Child Lin Huang greets Father.”

Lin Ming received this bow. Then, he stretched out his hands to help Lin Huang up. With this touch, Lin Huang could feel just how strong his father was.

In fact, this couldn’t be called helping him up, but pressing him down.

This was a strength greater than that of any ancient wild beast Lin Huang had ever encountered. It was like a hundred thousand foot tall mountain pushing down on his body.

Lin Huang was shocked. Then, he immediately began summoning strength to resist his father’s pressure. He knew that his father was testing him!

Ka ka ka ka!

Lin Huang’s body and joints began to emit explosive cracking sounds.

Xiao Moxian was startled to see this. Although she was a bit worried, she didn’t stop them.

Lin Huang gasped, his breath coming in heaves. His forehead dripped with beads of sweat. Finally, he forcefully lifted Lin Ming’s hand and stood up.

“Good!” Lin Ming said a single word of praise, a strange light flashing in his eyes.

In Lin Ming’s eyes, the invasion of the saints was bitter distress for Mu Qianyu, Qin Xingxuan, Xiao Moxian and Lin Xiaoge. Lin Ming didn’t want them to suffer any tribulation or injury.

But to Lin Huang, his own son, this was a time to temper himself!

Without being by his side for these 6000 some years, Lin Ming was looking forwards to seeing just how Lin Huang had grown.

“Tonight, I will test your strength here.”

Lin Huang was stunned. He didn’t think that during the first time he met his father, the words his father would say to him were that he wanted to test his strength.

However, these words caused Lin Huang to slowly stir with excitement.

To fight with the father he respected most in his life was also what he anticipated.

“You just came back and now you want to fight with your son?”

Xiao Moxian muttered, a bit begrudgingly. Although Lin Huang was strong, up until now he had lacked fatherly love.

Lin Huang was like a little wolf growing up, lonely, cold, and proud.

He had incredibly high standards that he set for himself. Although he seemed strong on the outside, the truth was that his innermost feelings were quite fragile. Xiao Moxian hoped that after Lin Ming returned, he would take good care of Lin Huang and show him the love that he had missed.

However, the way that Lin Ming cared for Lin Huang was completely different from what she had thought.

“Mother, allow me to fight Father!”

Lin Huang’s eyes flashed. Xiao Moxian looked at Lin Huang’s eyes and was startled. She immediately understood what he wanted…

Lin Huang was born with overflowing talent, but he had never been complacent or satisfied with himself. He had worked harder than anyone else.

He had to use his own achievements to win the recognition and praise of others.

Because he could not bring disgrace to his father’s honor!

But even all the praise he had ever received added up could not compare with the praise that came from Lin Ming’s mouth. Today, he wanted to personally obtain praise and affirmation from his father!

……..

News of Lin Ming’s return soon spread throughout the entire Demon Fairy Palace.

Lin Ming no longer concealed his identity, because he knew that after he appeared again and again, no matter if it were the saints or humans they would have approximately guessed his identity. There was no meaning in continuing to hide who he was.

Humanity worshipped Lin Ming. And if one had to think of a group of people that worshipped Lin Ming the most, then that would absolutely be those of Demon Fairy Palace and New Ming Planet!

As it was confirmed that the black fortress that appeared in the skies was Lin Ming’s Heavenly Palace, the entire Demon Fairy Palace went crazy with celebration!

To New Ming Planet or to Demon Fairy Palace, the name Lin Ming contained far too much meaning!

Afterwards they learned that Lin Ming had saved New Ming Planet recently. And not just that, but in the process they also learned that Lin Ming, with his own strength, had destroyed two great saint legions. And before that he had even defeated the Legion of Famine! This left the disciples of Demon Fairy Palace roiling with jubilation!

After being chased down by the saints for dozens of years, they thirsted for a victory.

They were fed up with the days of hiding like rats. They were willing to exchange their lives for a great and hearty victory!

“Lin Ming! Lin Ming!”

Everyone shouted out Lin Ming’s name, their voices echoing like ocean waves, reaching into the nebula.

They leapt in joy, running around to spread the news.

Their hero had returned. When Lin Ming opened up a path to the wild universe and saved humanity, he had only been at the Holy Lord realm. But now he could easily strike down Empyreans! If so, then he would surely be able to lead their Demon Fairy Palace to charge out of the Hidden Dragon Galaxy and rule the world once more!

In their gloomy lives filled with despair, they finally saw the eternal lighthouse shining in the horizon. That light left them intoxicated with dreams!

Many people gathered in front of Primordius Heavenly Palace, loudly chanting Lin Ming’s name and chanting humanity forever. It was difficult for anyone to restrain themselves from shouting this.

“Brother Lin, the disciples of Demon Fairy Palace all want to see you.” Xiao Moxian said.

“I understand.” Lin Ming smiled and stood up, walking into the square in front of Primordius Heavenly Palace.

Chapter 2045 – Two Armies Meet

As Lin Ming saw Xiao Moxian, he couldn’t help but laugh. “It’s fine,” he said. “We’ve suppressed our cultivation to the Divine Sea realm and even our bodily strength has been limited to the first four of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates. We haven’t used much energy and we aren’t injured either.”

Lin Ming and Lin Huang’s mortal bodies contained the bloodline of God Beasts; they were incredibly potent. In a situation where they suppressed their cultivation, even if they stood still and allowed themselves to be hit, it wouldn’t matter much.

“We’re just warming up for the upcoming battle.” Seeing Xiao Moxian’s not-too-happy expression, Lin Ming shrugged.

Still, Xiao Moxian couldn’t find it in her to laugh. Even with Lin Ming here, they had to face the Good Fortune Saint Son and also the most powerful Good Fortune Legion of the saint race. It was hard for her to relax.

Every single person in this fleet was a brave and loyal warrior who had followed Xiao Moxian and fought for her with all their might.

Today, they decided to march against the Good Fortune Saint Son, fearing neither danger nor death. Even against the Good Fortune Legion that was over a dozen times stronger than they were, they still boiled over with fighting intent.

All of this came from the glory of their race, the hot-blooded instinct carved into the marrow of their bone, as well as their deep faith and trust in Lin Ming.

However, although they didn’t fear death, Xiao Moxian didn’t wish for them to simply toss away their lives. She wished for as many of her followers to survive as possible. They were her most beloved subjects.

“Mm, I understand.”

Lin Ming knew what Xiao Moxian was thinking and hinted for Lin Huang to stop fighting. At this time, his heart suddenly stirred. He could feel the soul of Famine within his spiritual sea starting to beat.

Compared to when he met the Legion of Famine, this beating was now several times more intense!

For this sort of response to occur, there was only a single possibility!

“What is it?” The sensitive Xiao Moxian noticed the change in Lin Ming’s countenance.

“It’s fine.”

Lin Ming waved his hand and left the martial arts training room, moving towards the square outside Primordius Heavenly Palace.

Primordius Heavenly Palace had already been disguised as one of the flagships of Demon Fairy Palace. The Good Fortune Saint Son didn’t have much of an impression toward Primordius Heavenly Palace, and with the camouflage added by the Ancient Elysium Seal’s array formation, it was impossible for anyone to recognize it.

After the martial artists of Demon Fairy Palace realized that Lin Ming had walked outside, they hurried to the platform of their spirit ships and waited for him.

Each one of them stood tall and upright, like a towering tree!

The army was filled with a dignified solemnity. This was the aura of a people unafraid of death or destruction, ready to perish in iron and blood!

“After a little more time we might fight against the trump card of the saint armies – the Good Fortune Legion. Do you all have any thoughts about this?”

Lin Ming smiled as he spoke. With such a critical war approaching, everyone was strung taut. Yet, he was still able to smile like this. This left many warriors dumbfounded. Indeed, this person was worthy of being called the number one hero of humanity; he could actually still talk and happily smile at this time.

Invisibly, Lin Ming’s calm infected them. Their taut minds slightly relaxed.

“We will battle them!” A martial artist shouted as he rolled up his sleeves.

“Killing one is enough and killing two is a gain. Even if we only have our teeth left remaining, we will still bite down on the heads of those saints!”

“Whoever fears death is a woman!” A ruffian soldier carelessly shouted. But as he did so, he noticed Xiao Moxian who stood near Lin Ming suddenly cast him a frosty look.

The soldier quickly shrunk his neck, immediately changing his statement, “Whoever fears death is a coward!”

Lin Ming smiled. “You all seem prepared to sacrifice yourselves?”

“Sacrifice isn’t anything at all! Even if we must cross through seas of boiling oil, us brothers will jump in without batting an eye!”

Several large fellows strained their necks and wielded the sabers in their hands, showing their determination and lack of fear.

Lin Ming suddenly asked, “From your words, it seems we are not going to battle, but…committing suicide?”

The martial artists present dazed. Because of Lin Ming’s previous speech and because they had been repressed for so long, they were like barrels of powder, ready to explode with the slightest spark. Now they faced the Good Fortune Legion, an enemy that stirred panic and fear at the mere thought of fighting directly against them. So, they had all readied themselves to throw up their heads and sprinkle their blood on the ground. To the soldiers, this only seemed natural.

This was sure to be a tragic battle. Even if Lin Ming alone could deal with the Good Fortune Saint Son, it would still be difficult – the other Empyreans of the Good Fortune Legion weren’t some random cabbage. Just those people alone were over ten times stronger than Demon Fairy Palace.

They had to deal with such a formidable and tricky enemy. They had to delay this powerful enemy to give Lin Ming time to deal with the Good Fortune Saint Son.

Naturally, the vast majority of people thought this was how a war was fought.

General against general!

Soldier against soldier!

Facing such a powerful enemy, there was also the chance that they would be completely annihilated. Even so, they would continue pushing forwards without fear of death. As for how many people would need to be sacrificed, they simply hadn’t considered this at all.

What they wanted was their bravery and dignity!

It was only after Lin Ming asked his question that these people were left in a daze. Could it be that even in a battle where there was such a massive disparity in strength, there was still a favorable turn somewhere?

Could it even be that Lin Ming had already called for support troops?

Thinking of this possibility, many people grew excited.

Lin Ming continued, “Not being afraid to sacrifice yourself is a necessary quality for any legion that wishes to be strong. But those who do not fear death are not just the brave warriors but also ordinary men! Do not make meaningless sacrifice; this will only turn you into the military exploits of your enemies, something that they can use to show off. Even at the very end, none of us must easily give up on our lives. Rather, we must exchange it for the greatest possible value!”

“If each and every one of you can accomplish this, we will sweep away all obstacles!”

Lin Ming’s words caused the human warriors to calm down.

A brave and hot-blooded legion was terrifying, but a legion that could be all that and also be calm, that was even more terrifying.

Lin Ming drew out the Black Dragon Spear.

Weng –

With a loud rumbling sound, the roar of a dragon seemed to spread throughout the starry night sky.

Lin Ming shouted out, “Now, everyone, man your stations! You will have around one incense stick of time to prepare. Afterwards, we will go into battle with the Good Fortune Legion! At the time of battle, everyone obey my command!”

An incense stick of time!

After hearing this, the disciples of Demon Fairy Palace were startled. Before, they had heard that they would fight in a ‘while’, but they didn’t expect this ‘while’ to be so short!

Everyone hastily rushed over to their stations.

“And me?” Xiao Moxian hurriedly asked.

“Follow me.” As Lin Ming spoke, he strode into Primordius Heavenly Palace.

An incense stick of time was an extremely short period of time. And in fact, before an incense stick of time passed, the human army was able to see the vast and roiling Good Fortune Legion in the distance!

The spirit ships, the Heavenly Palace fortresses, they were as magnificent and unsurpassable as a great wall!

What led the legion was a massive blood red sphere. The sphere was as large as a planet and wielded thick tentacles.

This was the avatar of Famine. And beside the avatar of Famine was a golden temple.

This temple was half the size of Famine and wildly gushed out astral essence. A golden halo spun around it. This was the Good Fortune Saint Palace – a True Divinity spirit treasure level immortal palace!

This immortal palace was usually located within Saint Convocation Heaven and was the main temple of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s influence!

When people spoke of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s influence, they usually referred to the Good Fortune Saint Palace to represent everything. From this it could be seen how terrifying this temple was. This could be called a landmark of Saint Convocation Heaven.

Now, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign possessed the true body of Famine, so he didn’t need to use the Good Fortune Saint Palace in battle. At the same time, the Good Fortune Saint Son had no use for it either. Thus, the Good Fortune Saint Palace had been made into the flagship for the Good Fortune Legion.

The ones responsible for driving the Good Fortune Saint Palace were nine peak Empyreans. Only by joining forces were they just barely able to display the terrifying strength of this war fortress.

When Demon Fairy Palace and the Good Fortune Legion met, if one disregarded the massive disparity in strength, the Good Fortune Legion already suppressed Demon Fairy Palace in momentum! When contrasted with each other, it was no different from a fighter to a little baby.

“Hahaha! Ji Xian’er, you truly are stupid! You really brought yourself to my door!” The Good Fortune Saint Son stood above the flesh and blood of Famine, wildly cackling. He gazed up the fleet of Demon Fairy Palace as if they were all prey waiting to be cut down.

Within Primordius Heavenly Palace, Xiao Moxian grit her teeth, hatefully staring out the array formations at the Good Fortune Saint Son.

“Dealing with you is easy; I alone am enough. But even so, I brought my greatest strength here in order to ensure absolute victory. You no longer have the slightest chance of doing anything, and I will not make any mistake either. Why don’t you be a good little girl and surrender yourself to me. You should already be content that I brought so many people here just to capture you!”

As the Good Fortune Saint Son spoke, he waved his hand and issued an order, “Seal off the surrounding space!”

With the Good Fortune Saint Palace as the head, dozens of saint spirit ships shined with brilliant beams of divine light. These beams of divine light shot into the void, linking together into a massive net of light. The net of light spread out until it formed a titanic enchantment that sealed up the surrounding space for millions of miles.

Such a massive array was based upon the defensive array formation of the Good Fortune Saint Palace. Whether it was activating or deactivating it, it wasn’t easy at all. Moreover, starting it up required a massive amount of energy.

After the great array was formed, it would be impossible for normal spirit ships to break through. The only exception would be if the spirit ships of Demon Fairy Palace all attacked in a joint strike. However, the Good Fortune Saint Son would not give them the chance to do this.

“Are you satisfied? Ji Xian’er, this is the cage that I specially prepared for you. In order to capture you, I took great pains in arranging all of this and soon you will also understand why I tried so hard to catch you. Several days from now, I’ll give you a pleasant surprise!”

“If you know your limits then you will hurry up and surrender to me and be my slave. If you serve me well every day then I will let you keep your life and enjoy it too.”

The Good Fortune Saint Son recklessly laughed. But at this time, there was also a response from Demon Fairy Palace’s flagship. This was Xiao Moxian’s voice, icy cold and clear, “You stupid!” These two simple words caused the Good Fortune Saint Son’s complexion to darken.

The clear voice continued in sharp contention, “If you know your limits then hurry up and surrender to me and be my dog. But...I don’t think I can stand it. To have such an ugly dog, just thinking of it makes me nauseous.”

Good Fortune Saint Son diabolically grinned. “Very good. I also feared you might not be in that fleet and had sent in this rubble to die. Now that I know you truly are here, I can rest assured.”

“The flagship is mine and I leave the rest to you all. Kill them all to the last, do not let a single man live.”

Chapter 2046 – Lin Ming VS Saint Son

After confirming Xiao Moxian’s presence, the Good Fortune Saint Son revealed his fangs.

As the Good Fortune Saint Son issued his order, the Good Fortune Legion started moving forwards. This was an incredibly powerful army. The spirit ships pushed forwards, surrounding the fleet of Demon Fairy Palace.

With the Good Fortune Saint Palace taking the lead, hundreds of spirit ships gathered together to form a battle array. Each spirit ship possessed their own array formations, and with several hundred array formations gathered together, this was actually a net of battle arrays. With these battle arrays coordinating with each other, they could display an incomparably terrifying strength. By joining together, the sheer amount of energy they released would be several times that of a True Divinity!

However, in terms of Laws, this spirit ship battle array couldn’t compare with a True Divinity nor could they focus their energy like a True Divinity. So, the actual threat was less than that of a True Divinity.

For such a joint attack, no matter how much it was enhanced it wouldn’t reach the height of a True Divinity.

Nevertheless, this attack had a massive area of effect and the power behind it was enormous. Against a group of spirit ships, this was a devastating attack.

It wasn’t an exaggeration to say that if the Good Fortune Legion had sufficient time to prepare, gathering their complete group of battle arrays for a single barrage of attacks, they could blow away over half of the spirit ships of Demon Fairy Palace.

This was an overwhelming disparity that came from the difference in strength.

Seeing the spirit ship battle array that was led by the Good Fortune Saint Palace, even someone like Xiao Moxian who refused to give up found it hard to maintain her composure. It was hard not to waver in front of such a terrifying weapon.

At this time, Lin Ming raised his Black Dragon Spear and stepped out of Primordius Heavenly Palace.

“Brother Lin!” Xiao Moxian grabbed onto Lin Ming’s hand.

“Just wait here.” Lin Ming gave Xiao Moxian a comforting look. Then, he stepped outside.

“Ji Xian’er! The destructive attack of the Good Fortune Legion nears that of a star! Aren’t you afraid? Don’t worry, before I capture you alive, I will not let them attack. Only after I catch you will I have you personally watch as all your subordinates turn to ash beneath this world-destroying light!”

The Good Fortune Saint Son wildly laughed. At this time, the planet-sized body of Famine rapidly rushed forwards, flying straight towards the flagship of Demon Fairy Palace!

Compared to the giant body of Famine, the disguised Primordius Heavenly Palace was like a bird in front of a tiger; they were completely disproportionate in size.

However, just as Famine’s several dozen tentacles were poised to attack, the flagship suddenly flashed with a strange black light. It began to change shape, becoming taller and wider and transforming from a linear spirit ship to a black fortress.

Seeing this, the Good Fortune Saint Son was shocked. “What!?”

The shape of this transformed spirit ship caused a foreboding to rise in his heart. He watched as a man holding a spear jumped out from the black fortress.

This man wore black battle armor. His eyebrows were like swords and his eyes were profoundly deep.

As the man grasped the spear, he pointed it straight towards the Good Fortune Saint Son.

“You…? It’s you!?”

The Good Fortune Saint Son’s complexion became incredibly ugly. At this time, Lin Ming had already recovered his appearance of 6,500 years ago. One didn’t even need to guess that this was Lin Ming!

To the Good Fortune Saint Son, this man was no different from a nightmare!

“Is that so…? So it’s like this. Because you were a step earlier than me and found Xiao Moxian first, you had the courage to break into my blockade…”

The Good Fortune Saint Son’s lips twitched. His complexion became increasingly grim and dark. His eyes clouded over with killing intent!

“You really are as stubborn as a cockroach! Even after being hunted down by a True Divinity, you still won’t die! You swept through the joint second and third saint legions, extinguished the Legion of Famine, and you plan on eliminating me today? Hahahaha!” The Good Fortune Saint Son raucously laughed. “Over 6,000 years ago, the battle between you and I became the greatest shame of my life. But today, the heavens have given me a chance for revenge. Since this is a battle of destiny, I cannot ask for anything more! Today, let me see just what makes you so brave! Die!”

The Good Fortune Saint Son exploded with a roar. The dozens of Famine’s tentacles attacked together, thrusting forwards like the spears of a divine god!

Bang!

A horrifying detonation sound surged out and the void was crushed apart. The Good Fortune Saint Son’s strike was comprised of dozens of attacks. Its pressure was greater than innumerable mountains smashing into Primordius Heavenly Palace!

At this moment, it looked like Famine was branching out a giant pile of its flesh and blood to swallow up Primordius Heavenly Palace.

For some time, everyone felt their hearts gripped with fear. In particular, the disciples of Demon Fairy Palace. They all watched with bated breath. Although they had a nearly zealous faith in Lin Ming, this avatar of Famine that the Good Fortune Saint Son commanded was still a being at the True Divinity level. No matter how strong Lin Ming was, this would be a difficult battle!

“Kill Lin Ming! With your strongest attack, blow him up together with Famine’s flesh and blood!” The Good Fortune Saint Son crazily shouted. He didn’t take back the flesh and blood of Famine nor did he see whether or not Lin Ming died. He instantly severed this part of Famine’s flesh and blood and had it surround Lin Ming. He wanted to use the combined attack of the Good Fortune Legion’s battle array to unleash the ultimate killing blow.

This was a sinister and decisive choice. The Good Fortune Saint Son would rather sacrifice a portion of Famine than to give Lin Ming the smallest chance of survival!

At this time, behind the Good Fortune Saint Son, the battle array network with the Good Fortune Saint Palace as the lead began to gather a mind-boggling amount of energy, preparing for their world destroying light attack!

On the side of Demon Fairy Palace, a giant man wielding a war flag rushed out of a spirit ship. He rode on a great wild beast, shouting out as he rushed into the saint fleet, “Brothers! Move forwards! Protect senior Lin Ming and Palace Master Demon Fairy!”

He was a human genius born after the great calamity and also the flag bearer of Demon Fairy Palace!

The scarlet war flag he carried on his shoulders was emblazoned with the symbol of Demon Fairy Palace – the image of a black phoenix bathing in the fires of nirvana!

A Dark Phoenix was Xiao Moxian’s God Beast bloodline, and the fires of nirvana represented the rebirth of humanity!

“Kill them!”

“Fight with them!”

“Destroy those saint dogs!”

The army of Demon Fairy Palace roared and charged forwards. They rushed directly toward the flesh and blood of Famine. Placing Primordius Heavenly Palace behind them, they used their fleet to form a great protective iron wall in front of it!

They began gathering all of their energy, preparing to meet the direct attack of the Good Fortune Legion!

Even if their attack was pitifully weak compared to the battle array network of the Good Fortune Legion, at this time no one felt fear and no one shrank backwards. No one was scared of death!

“A tiny pearl dares to compete with the shining moon!”

The Good Fortune Saint Son derisively sneered. He wielded the giant blood dragon tentacles and lashed out at the disciples of Demon Fairy Palace.

The one he targeted was the youth in front carrying the war flag. With the strength of Famine’s avatar, a single strike could easily turn this man into muddy meat!

A war flag was the faith and symbol of an army. If the flag fell, so too would group morale.

Hu - !

The tentacles of Famine shrouded down with an unstoppable force. A tremendous pressure locked down the surrounding space, making it impossible to avoid.

The flag-wielding youth’s complexion changed. In this moment of life or death, he turned around and exhausted all of his strength to throw the war flag. The war flag howled and broke through the space blockade with difficulty as it fired towards the direction of another flag bearer.

The man could die, but the flag could not fall!

“Brothers, for the glory of humanity! Charge!”

The youth seemed to exhaust every last dreg of his blood vitality to shout out these earth-shaking words. The morale of Demon Fairy Palace erupted like a volcano!

“For humanity!” they yelled, their blood boiling over!

But as everyone thought the flag bearer’s blood would dye the starry space, something unexpected happened. From Primordius Heavenly Palace that was wrapped in the flesh and blood of Famine, a blood dragon tentacle whipped out!

This blood dragon tentacle was even thicker than the one shot out by the Good Fortune Saint Son. With inconceivable speed, it crossed the void and collided with the Good Fortune Saint Son’s strike!

Bang!

The void collapsed! As the mountain-thick tentacles clashed in the air, a deafening explosion rang outwards!

A terrifying tide of energy wildly surged out, sending the flag-bearer flying away! Because this other tentacle of Famine had blocked the attack, the flag-bearer only felt his blood vitality tumbling in his body. He wasn’t even seriously wounded.

“What!?”

“This is…”

Everyone was bewildered. The Good Fortune Saint Son watched all of this with disbelief thick in his eyes. In the air, two tentacles intersected, just like two blood dragons twisting together!

But that other tentacle was clearly linked to Primordius Heavenly Palace.

How was this possible!?

“The flesh and blood of Famine that I discarded would actually protect the flag-bearer on its own? Why would this happen!?”

The Good Fortune Saint Son was panic-stricken.

At this time, the flesh and blood of Famine that surrounded Primordius Heavenly Palace began to slowly split up. Within it, a channel formed.

A black-clothed youth wielding a long spear stepped out. His long hair fluttered behind him. His clothes were clean and meticulous, his appearance was sharp and resolute, and his aura was as deep as the sea.

He stood firm above the flesh and blood of Famine, like a peerless war god who had descended from the highest heavens.

The flesh and blood beneath his feet slowly rose up to form a round table that lifted up the man. This feeling was as if the flesh and blood of Famine was revering this demon-like man!

Seeing this scene, not to mention the Good Fortune Saint Son and the Good Fortune Legion, even the disciples of Demon Fairy Palace were dumbfounded!

What was happening?

“Your words are wrong,” Lin Ming casually said as he pointed his spear toward the Good Fortune Saint Son. “Between you and I, there is no battle of destiny. In my life, I might have a destined opponent, but that person is not you. You are not worthy!”

Lin Ming’s cold voice resounded through the vastness of space, spreading over both the Demon Fairy Palace and the Good Fortune Legion!

The Good Fortune Saint Son regarded Lin Ming as the greatest opponent in his life, but Lin Ming only regarded the Good Fortune Saint Son as one of the many goals he had to surpass in life. Moreover, this was in the past. Now, Lin Ming had completed the dual transformation of his body and mind. The Good Fortune Saint Son could only be called an enemy and not his match!

Chapter 2047 – Dazzling

“Lin Ming, you are seeking death!”

As the Good Fortune Saint Son listened to Lin Ming’s words, his complexion turned incredibly ugly!

He regarded Lin Ming as the greatest opponent in his life, but Lin Ming only treated him as a little clown, mercilessly trampling him and humiliating him in front of his subordinates!

This struck the Good Fortune Saint Son’s nerves!

At this time, in the starry space, the hundreds of thousands of saint martial artists and the disciples of Demon Fairy Palace were watching as this conversation took place.

‘You are not worthy’. These three words echoed in the ears of everyone, enraging the martial artists of the Good Fortune Legion even as it caused the human martial artists to bubble over with excitement.

This was arrogance! This was pride!

If someone else were to say such ridiculous words, others would only call them an idiot. But as Lin Ming said these words, they actually contained an unparalleled deterring force.

This was a happy and hearty feeling that filled one with exuberance!

“Fight!”

The disciples of Demon Fairy Palace emitted an earth-shaking cry, their voices sounded out into the vastness of space!

At this time, the morale of the disciples of Demon Fairy Palace had climbed to the extreme!

“You can go die!” The Good Fortune Saint Son roared out. His mortal body emitted explosive crackling sounds as he began to grow taller. Fierce bone plates jutted out from his body. He had used the strength of the saint race’s bloodline body metamorphosis. By using this new power to control the flesh and blood of Famine, the Good Fortune Saint Son could reach his highest level of strength!

The enraged Good Fortune Saint Son suddenly burnt his blood essence. Dozens of new blood dragon tentacles gushed out from the avatar of Famine, and all these tentacles sparkled with blinding divine light as they shot towards Lin Ming!

At this time, even if a sun were in front of the Good Fortune Saint Son, it would still be torn apart by these tentacles!

Facing this heaven-shaking strike, Lin Ming merely focused his thoughts. Beneath him, the flesh and blood of Famine shot out!

Lin Ming had a limited amount of Famine’s flesh and blood; it was impossible for him to form tentacles that were as thick as mountains. As he formed tentacles to meet the Good Fortune Saint Son’s attack, his tentacles were only as thick as a tree.

Compared to the Good Fortune Saint Son’s attack, Lin Ming’s counterattack was nothing at all.

Puff! Puff! Puff!

All of the comparatively slender tentacles shot into the much thicker tentacles. And in that moment, the scene of those far thicker tentacles rolling over the thinner tentacles didn’t occur as everyone thought it would. Instead, the tentacles struck out by the Good Fortune Saint Son were completely frozen in place!

Like snakes that were caught by their necks, these tentacles began to twitch.

At this time, everyone was amazed to discover that these thinner tentacles had become like blood-drinking snakes, sucking in the flesh and blood of the thicker tentacles!

Gu! Gu! Gu!

The tips of the thicker tentacles began to wither at a speed visible to the eye. The rich flesh and blood essence of Famine flowed through the thinner tentacles and into the flesh and blood of Famine beneath Lin Ming’s feet.

The flesh and blood of Famine beneath Lin Ming wildly wriggled.

On the other side, the avatar of Famine that was controlled by the Good Fortune Saint Son began to restlessly stir as if it were greatly stimulated by something. It emitted deep roars.

“What!?”

This situation left the Good Fortune Saint Son stunned. Could it be… that Lin Ming could control Famine!?

This conclusion left the Good Fortune Saint Son panic-stricken. Was this even possible!?

But now, he was already able to clearly feel Lin Ming’s soul force pass through the flesh and blood of Famine and permeate into Famine’s avatar!

“You - !!”

The Good Fortune Saint Son went wild with rage. There was no time for him to think about how Lin Ming had accomplished this. If he were to discard the avatar of Famine, just what sort of consequences would he suffer? It was simply unimaginable!

If he were to lose the avatar of Famine, it would be impossible to escape Lin Ming chasing him down. Disregarding that, even if he somehow survived, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign would not let him live.

He would die either way!

In that moment, the Good Fortune Saint Son felt a cold sweat seep out of his entire body.

But right after that, a crazed and fierce light flashed in his eyes.

Blue veins twisted on his face like worms. His eyes that stared at Lin Ming seemed dyed with blood, overflowing with killing intent.

“Do you really think you can kill me like this? Stop dreaming! You are destined to die here! Good Fortune Legion obey my command! With the World Destroying Light, attack with everything you have! Kill them, kill them all!” the Good Fortune Saint Son shouted.

At this time, behind the Good Fortune Saint Son, the Good Fortune Legion had already prepared their battle formation and gathered their energies for several breaths of time. It was enough to send out the World Destruction Light!

In a small scope, this attack was inferior to that of a True Divinity. But as a mass range attack, it was a terrifying strike that surpassed that of a True Divinity!

In this critical situation, the Good Fortune Legion didn’t fall into chaos. With nine peak Empyreans calmly directing the troops, the Good Fortune Legion took the Good Fortune Saint Palace as the core and struck out with the World Destruction Light!

In that moment, it seemed as if every sound in the universe was swallowed up!

A heaven-shaking energy swept through the vastness of space before converging in front of the Good Fortune Saint Palace. It gathered together and collapsed into a black energy ball. The surrounding space cracked and shattered, as if this black ball was one of the fabled black holes.

Shua!

Energy recklessly shot out from this black hole, shooting towards Lin Ming as well as the fleet of Demon Fairy palace!

The black light was too terrifying. It covered a massive range, and with this part of space being sealed up, it was impossible for the fleet of Demon Fairy Palace to avoid it!

At this time, the demented Good Fortune Saint Son sent out more massive tentacles. These tentacles didn’t directly attack Lin Ming but covered him instead, forming a wall of flesh and blood around him. It was clear he wanted to block off every possible escape route!

In truth, even if the Good Fortune Saint Son didn’t do this, Lin Ming wouldn’t have been able to dodge this World Destruction Light. At this time, he had poured his soul force into the avatar of Famine in order to erase the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s spirit mark and capture the avatar. If he were to dodge this attack, the least of his problems would be the injuries to his soul; the key problem was that the flesh and blood of Famine that he controlled beneath his feet would also be destroyed.

And this flesh and blood of Famine wrapped around Primordius Heavenly Palace. Xiao Moxian and the others were all inside!

Lin Ming was doomed to not avoid this attack. He could not abandon Xiao Moxian nor could he abandon the 100,000 warriors of Demon Fairy Palace!

At this time, the warriors of Demon Fairy Palace didn’t give up on Lin Ming. They stood in front of Lin Ming, using their relatively weak spirit ships to face off against this attack.

“Brothers, attack!”

“For humanity!”

“For honor and freedom!”

The warriors of Demon Fairy Palace shouted out from the depths of their heart. They poured every ounce of their strength into the array formations of their spirit ships!

At this instant, even without anyone directing them, these 100,000 warriors burnt their blood essence together, burning it all without reserve!

Because they knew that this was likely the final and most dazzling attack in their lives!

This was the brilliance of burning their lives away, as gorgeous and as blazing as the hot sun.

A martial artist was born like a summer flower and died like a spring thunderstorm!

The attack of the Demon Fairy Palace’s disciples gathered into a surging current of golden light that welcomed the World Destroying Light!

Bang!

A terrifying explosion rang out. In a flash, energy beams recklessly shot outwards. It was unknown just how much matter was destroyed in that explosion…

Even so, the attack of Demon Fairy Palace’s disciples was unable to eliminate the World Destroying Light. After the World Destroying Light slowed down for a brief moment, it suddenly overwhelmed the energy wave from Demon Fairy Palace’s disciples and continued forwards without hesitation!

The disparity in energy was too great. They were simply unable to deal with it!

In the next moment, dozens of Demon Fairy Palace disciples became like little beasts beneath a giant tsunami, soon to be utterly submerged.

At this time, from beneath Lin Ming’s feet, the mass of Famine’s flesh and blood split open. Primordius Heavenly Palace rose up from within, wrapped in an all-devouring black light!

“Legion of Famine, attack!” Lin Ming coldly commanded. Within Primordius Heavenly Palace, the 60,000 warriors of the Legion of Famine had already undergone their body metamorphosis a quarter of an hour ago. They had prepared their battle formation and had gathered their energy earlier, waiting for the moment to erupt!

After the battle with the join saint legions, the Legion of Famine had rested and built up their strength for over a month. All of that was done for the sake of this one strike!

By now, even Fairy Blue Lotus had undergone body metamorphosis!

Four of the saint generals, Lin Ming’s three avatars, one miniaturized Black Dragon, and 200 Great World Kings that were comparable to the weakest of Empyreans after body metamorphosis…

Every person and beast poured all their energy into the array formation without reserve!

In particular, the flesh and blood of Famine beneath Lin Ming’s feet that he controlled also lent its strength to this attack!

The flesh and blood of Famine burned itself without holding back. Energy surged into Primordius Heavenly Palace as a horrifying black beam of light pierced through the universe and clashed with the World Destroying Light!

“Xian’er, lend me your help!”

Lin Ming’s sound transmission reached Xiao Moxian’s ears. Next, Xiao Moxian, Lin Huang, and some of the disciples of Demon Fairy Palace who had followed her to Primordius Heavenly Palace all poured their greatest strength into the array formation, preparing to meet the World Destroying Light!

A beam of divine light joined together with the divine light emitted by the 100,000 disciples of Demon Fairy Palace, ruthlessly colliding with the World Destroying Light!

Rumble, rumble, rumble!

An explosion sounded out as if the universe was being torn to shreds. Energy gushed outwards, able to collapse space and wash away the stars!

With this all-out strike from Demon Fairy Palace, the Legion of Famine, and even the flesh and blood of Famine burning away its essence, the might of this attack managed to suppress the terrifying beam of energy emitted by the Good Fortune Legion!

Right after, the beam of energy shot out by the Good Fortune Legion began to be pushed backwards, drawing back at an increasingly quick pace!

Finally, Lin Ming’s strike carried with it a heaven-shaking strength as it forcefully extinguished the World Destroying Light and then fired towards the direction of the Good Fortune Legion!

“Noo!!!”

The Good Fortune Saint Son’s eyes nearly cracked open. And behind him, the several hundred thousand saint martial artists of the Good Fortune Legion all seemed to lose their spirit!

“Ahhhh!”

Some people cried out in despair and sorrow. Others rushed out their spirit ships and fled into deep space. And still others moved their spirit ships, wanting to withdraw.

But no matter how they struggled, everything they did was useless. This beam of light was too fast, faster than any spirit ship or martial artist.

Much less, this space had already been sealed away by the Good Fortune Legion.

They were caught in their own trap!

Bang!

Divine light exploded within the Good Fortune Legion. Divine light swallowed all, drowning out all sight in a sea of blinding light.

Before, in order to arrange the battle formation that would send out the World Destroying Light, the Good Fortune Legion had crowded together their spirit ships. But this now became the reason for their complete destruction!

Large swathes of saint spirit ships were struck head-on by the light and directly disintegrated into powder, without leaving behind any fragment of space debris.

Innumerable spirit ships were swept up in the explosion before bursting apart in the horrifying energy storm, turning into dazzling fireworks in space!

The Good Fortune Legion had suffered far too heavy losses in this attack.

The Good Fortune Saint Son watched all of this from a distance, his heart trembling. At this moment, he knew that the Good Fortune Legion, the trump card of the saint armies, was done for!

Chapter 2048 – End of the Road

The World Destruction Light along with the Good Fortune Legion was completely overwhelmed by the blast of energy sent out by the human alliance. The defensive barrier laid down by the Good Fortune Legion was torn apart like a soap bubble. Even from trillions of miles away, one could see a brilliant light blazing in the distance, as if a massive star had burst into a supernova.

The energy waves recklessly washed out the dark nebula, thoroughly destroying the surrounding star territory and causing the light to spread even further out!

The trump card of the saint armies – the Good Fortune Legion – was utterly ruined. They didn’t even have half their spirit ships remaining. The Good Fortune Saint Palace managed to remain intact. Even though it was at the center of the energy beam, it barely made it through due to the fact that it was a True Divinity spirit treasure. But for hundreds of miles around the Good Fortune Saint Palace, every spirit ship was reduced to ashes.

Even those that were far away and relatively well-off were greatly damaged in the explosion. The battle strength of these spirit ships was reduced to near nothing.

In truth, the truly fatal strike was the impact on their morale. The Good Fortune Legion was like a fierce tiger descending the mountain, possessing an absolute faith in their strength and ability to win. This was a terrifying army that feared no opponent.

But that strike just now had completely smashed apart their arrogance and confidence.

They were defeated, completely and utterly defeated!

Even for the several peak Empyreans as they faced Lin Ming, this man that seemed like a demon god, all of them felt a fear come from the depths of their souls. This Lin Ming was too horrifying, simply unbeatable!

And while the saints were wallowing in their low morale and fervently wishing to retreat, the morale of humanity reached the zenith!

That incredible all-out attack just now caused their blood to boil over!

The human martial artists that burnt their blood essence should have been exhausted due to overdrawing their blood vitality. But because of this great victory, all of them had gone crazy with elation.

“Brothers, onwards!” the officers of Demon Fairy Palace wildly roared. The soldiers were like starving wolves that saw fresh meat, swarming forwards.

The flapping war flag of Demon Fairy Palace was lifted high into the air. The Dark Phoenix in Nirvana embroidered upon the war flag seemed to come alive. It guided the anger of the human army, stabbing into the Good Fortune Legion like a sharp blade!

The Good Fortune Legion was the top army of the entire saint race. But facing the brutal onslaught of Demon Fairy Palace, they were unexpectedly routed!

The explosion had blown up their battle formation. Now, every spirit ship had to operate independently, contributing more to the chaos in the field. And most importantly, according to how the original battle formation was arranged, the more powerful spirit ships were placed closer to the center of the battlefield. Like this, they could support the main strike force.

When the energy beam exploded within the Good Fortune Legion, the spirit ships near the center took the brunt of the attack and almost all of them were destroyed as a result.

The spirit ships that were farther away and survived the explosion were much weaker than the spirit ships near the center. It could be said that the Good Fortune Legion had lost almost three-fourths of their total war strength.

Divine light shot out and an explosion lit up space. Demon Fairy Palace pushed forwards with unstoppable momentum and the Good Fortune Legion withdrew in defeat again and again.

At this time, on the other side of the battlefield, the flesh and blood of Famine beneath Lin Ming’s feet was still entangled with the Good Fortune Saint Son’s avatar of Famine. A massive amount of flesh and blood essence from the avatar of Famine was being swallowed up by the flesh and blood of Famine that Lin Ming controlled!

The Good Fortune Saint Son’s complexion had already turned horrendously ugly.

Lin Ming could swallow and control the flesh and blood essence of Famine. Even if the flesh and blood essence of Famine had the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s spirit mark within it, it was still useless!

The Good Fortune Saint Son didn’t know how Lin Ming managed to accomplish this, but this part was no longer important because he had been pushed into a dead end!

He wasn’t like Fairy Blue Lotus, someone who had a master willing to damage their own cultivation to protect her with a wisp of an incarnation. How could the greatly ambitious Good Fortune Saint Sovereign ever make a sacrifice to help his disciple? As far as the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was concerned, everyone else was nothing but a pawn to be used.

So, as the Good Fortune Saint Son faced Lin Ming, he no longer had any cards in his hands.

Perhaps it should be said that even if he did have hidden cards, these cards would be nothing but toys in front of Lin Ming.

At this moment, the Good Fortune Saint Son felt what true despair was!

He could feel that Lin Ming was not just sucking out Famine’s flesh and blood essence, but also drawing out his own flesh and blood!

He was no different from a convict who had his artery slashed open. He could only stare helplessly on as his blood flowed out from his body, awaiting the moment he died from blood loss.

This way of waiting for death truly left one grasping in craziness!

The Good Fortune Saint Son went mad. He wildly injected his soul force into Famine’s body, wanting to compete with Lin Ming in controlling it.

However, the moment that the Good Fortune Saint Son touched Lin Ming’s soul force, his face turned paperwhite and his body shook. Blood started seeping out from his nose.

The difference between his soul force and Lin Ming’s was far too great!

Moreover, the crux of the issue here was that the Good Fortune Saint Son’s soul force couldn’t control Famine’s avatar to begin with. He had only barely managed to indirectly control Famine’s avatar using the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s spirit mark. When compared to Lin Ming who possessed the soul of Famine, the difference was unfathomable!

With a great roar, the Good Fortune Saint Son leapt out from Famine’s body!

He grasped a heavy sword and slashed out at Lin Ming. In that instant, golden astral essence surged out from the Good Fortune Saint Son, as if there were a golden sun burning within him.

His aura also changed. The endless starlight around him distorted, gathering towards him. The origin energy of the universe, the cosmic dust, all forms of energy were drawn out by the Good Fortune Saint Son.

This was the Good Fortune Saint Son’s Good Fortune Divine Art. Once the Good Fortune Divine Art was used, it could seize the power of the world’s good fortune. In other words, it was wrestling away the spiritual energy and life of the world!

A martial artist skilled in the Good Fortune Divine Art could convert this energy into their own strength, using it to destroy their enemies.

By this time, the Good Fortune Saint Son had cultivated the Good Fortune Divine Art to an extremely high boundary. Once he used it, weaker Empyreans couldn’t even stand before him. This was because the Good Fortune Divine Art would sever their connection with the energy of the world, and the Good Fortune Saint Son would brutally take it away!

Only a peak Empyrean would be barely able to deal with the Good Fortune Saint Son’s Good Fortune Divine Art.

But to Lin Ming, not even peak Empyreans could stand before him!

This was the disparity between the two!

When the Good Fortune Saint Son attacked, so did Lin Ming. But it wasn’t Lin Ming that moved, but the flesh and blood of Famine beneath him!

Dozens of blood dragon tentacles shot out towards the Good Fortune Saint Son!

The Good Fortune Saint Son’s eyes turned blood red. He could use the Good Fortune Divine Art to absorb origin energy from the universe, but to use it to steal away origin energy from Famine was actually impossible!

This was because of the difference in their ranks.

He rushed left and right between the dozens of tentacles. But to his shock, he discovered that Lin Ming’s ability to display the strength of Famine’s avatar far exceeded his own!

Every tentacle of Famine seemed to be alive, as if they had their own thoughts and sensations. They coordinated their attacks, their barrage of strikes, without flaw.

The Good Fortune Saint Son dodged over a dozen attacks. But in the next few attacks, as his speed slowed down by just a bit, a blood dragon tentacle slammed him in the back!

Puff!

The Good Fortune Saint Son spat out a mouthful of blood. The organs in his body tumbled around as he was sent flying backwards.

At this time, the Good Fortune Saint Son’s heart was filled with shame and humiliation. Lin Ming had actually stolen away the avatar of Famine and then used it to deal with him!

He had mobilized the several saint legions in Saint Convocation Heaven to come here and wait for Lin Ming. But these legions were completely defeated by Lin Ming.

He had led the Good Fortune Legion, the trump card of the saint armies, to encircle Xiao Moxian. But in the end, the Good Fortune Legion had been demolished!

And from beginning to end, the Good Fortune Saint Son had never truly fought with Lin Ming. Lin Ming simply stood where he was without moving, gradually taking control of Famine’s avatar!

The Good Fortune Saint Son hurtled himself at Lin Ming. But Lin Ming only used Famine’s avatar to deal with him.

Lin Ming’s methods matched what he had said before. He simply didn’t take the Good Fortune Saint Son to be his match.

Humiliation, frustration, despair, in the final waning moments of his life, the Good Fortune Saint Son went crazy. He burnt his blood essence to the limit, but no matter how he attacked, all that greeted him were the fierce and terrifying blood dragon tentacles!

These tentacles were endless. Even if the Good Fortune Saint Son cut them off, they would rapidly regrow. Then, these tentacles were reabsorbed by Famine’s body. It was simply an unkillable monster.

Moreover, as more and more flesh and blood of Famine was absorbed by Lin Ming, the tentacles that fought with the Good Fortune Saint Son became increasingly thick even as more and more of them appeared!

The Good Fortune Saint Son was covered in blood. His organs had broken apart in countless places and he was covered in innumerable wounds.

His movements gradually slowed down. He knew he had reached the precipice of death.

In the final moments of his life, the Good Fortune Saint Son’s lips curved up in a humorless smile. He used his remaining astral essence to flood his limbs. These energies started to boil like magma…

“You want to implode?”

A cold light flashed in Lin Ming’s eyes. How could he allow the Good Fortune Saint Son to do as he wished. To him, the Good Fortune Saint Son was still of great use.

Whoosh!

A wisp of soul force shot out from between Lin Ming’s eyebrows like the sword of a divine god, piercing into the Good Fortune Saint Son’s spiritual sea at an inconceivable speed.

For an instant, the energy gathered within the Good Fortune Saint Son froze. And in this instant, a thick tentacle rushed forwards and bit down upon the Good Fortune Saint Son!

Puff! Puff! Puff!

Immediately, hundreds of tentacles the thickness of a worm drilled into the Good Fortune Saint Son’s body. Like leeches, they started to recklessly swallow the Good Fortune Saint Son’s flesh and blood essence and energy alike!

The Good Fortune Saint Son’s eyes bulged out and his expression turned dull. At this moment, he was no different from a living corpse.

In these last moments of his life, he could feel Lin Ming using Famine’s avatar to swallow him!

He had controlled the avatar of Famine for a long time and had used it to swallow an incalculable amount of lives and energy. Finally, he had been reduced to becoming this avatar’s food. This was truly life’s greatest joke!

Slowly, the Good Fortune Saint Son’s mortal body withered away. His skin wrinkled and his eyes deepened into their sockets.

The flesh and blood of Famine wriggled about and fed the disabled Good Fortune Saint Son into Primordius Heavenly Palace…

Chapter 2052 – True Divinities Gather

Within the Hidden Dragon Galaxy, in a separate starry space isolated out by an array formation. Lin Ming sat within the flesh and blood of Famine, his eyes closed in meditation.

At this moment, Lin Ming had already completely refined this avatar of Famine. It was simply far too large and even if Lin Ming had already refined it, wanting to easily control every part of its body required a long period of adaptation.

This was all because Lin Ming’s soul force was formidable and he also possessed Famine’s soul. As for someone like the Good Fortune Saint Son, he had controlled Famine using the spirit mark that the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign left behind. In the Good Fortune Saint Son’s clumsy hands, this avatar that possessed a middle True Divinity level strength, could only display abilities that made it invincible at the Empyrean realm.

When Lin Ming swam in the flesh and blood of Famine and completely controlled this True Divinity level avatar, it was only then that he could feel how terrifying it was. From appearance, it seemed to be a massive ball of flesh and blood. But the truth was that it was filled with an incomparably mystical strength and incredibly complex Laws, as if there was a bizarre and strange demonic world within.

This world was filled with bloodthirst and rage. Every wisp of blood soared into the skies, filled with 10,000 phantoms that wailed and cried.

But at the same time, this world was overflowing with spiritual matter. It was flooded with divine chains composed of infinite Law runes, vast and boundless.

The source of some of these Laws originated from Famine itself, but the majority of them had been swallowed up. The ever-changing Laws formed this macabre yet magnificent scene before him.

As Lin Ming wandered through this sea of Laws, he continued to look and search, his divine sense rapidly passing over thousands of Law chains. He didn’t bother with Empyrean level Laws, instead he was searching for something in particular.

Even though Lin Ming’s divine sense was powerful, Famine had simply swallowed far too many Laws in the billions of years of its life. He had to withdraw his mental strength several times before finally finding an unusual divine chain in this endlessly mystical world.

This divine chain spanned across the skies, seeming to be sprinkled with endless starlight. It shined with a myriad of colors. It was as beautiful as a dream.

The moment Lin Ming saw this divine chain, his mind shook. His eyes began to shimmer with excitement.

He could feel his blood vitality being drawn toward this divine chain’s alluring strength. His heart began to race and the blood within his body quickened. Within his spine, between his eyebrows, in his heart, and all throughout his body in a total of nine spots, he began to feel a burning heat. He faintly sensed something wonderful, as if he were resonating with this divine chain.

“This is it!”

Lin Ming’s breath paused for a brief moment. This divine chain was the causal link between humanity and the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace Heavenly Dao Law that Famine had swallowed, and then condensed into a chain of the highest Laws of the 33 Heavens!

If he could cut this off and refine it, what would happen then?

This divine chain wasn’t complete, and only contained a small portion of the samsara of cause and effect that linked the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace and humanity together. The vast majority was undoubtedly located in Famine’s true body, underneath the control of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign.

Only when he obtained the main body of Famine would Lin Ming be able to truly liberate the causal link that connected humanity with their lost Heavenly Dao. This would be equal to doing a great deed for the entire human race.

3,6 billion years ago, the ancient era’s Saint Sovereign had cut off one of humanity’s arms. Now, Lin Ming would take it back!

Lin Ming even suspected that the destiny of the primal god race and celestials might be sealed within Famine’s body.

Why would the ancient races decline, why would the primal god race find it difficult to reproduce, all of this might be connected to the abyssal demons.

Lin Ming sat down beneath the divine chain. He didn’t immediately sever it. After all, this was something that involved the highest existences of the Heavenly Dao and might trigger a heavenly tribulation.

With Lin Ming’s current strength, wanting to shake Laws of this level was a bit beyond him.

So, he planned to first break into the Empyrean realm!

By this point in time, Lin Ming had more than enough accumulations. He had used almost 7,000 years to cultivate through multiple reincarnations, slowly firming his foundation. Now, he was ready to take the next step!

Slowly, Lin Ming entered the fused martial intent state, becoming like a statue. As he sensed the demonic power emanating from Famine’s avatar, he also quickened the divine spiritual power in his inner world. Within his mind, countless deductions took place as he slowly forgot the passing of time.

The highest Laws within existence were in these two strengths. If he could fuse the power of divinity and demons together, forming a yin yang balance and achieving harmony, there would be inconceivable effects that followed.

But this was also extremely dangerous. In order to have two extreme forces achieve harmonious integration, there were billions of ways the balance could be lost. Once Lin Ming lost control of the process, he could even fall into obsession.

If anyone else were to try this, it would be the same as suicide.

Even for Lin Ming, he had to be cautious.

The flesh and blood of Famine melted into beams of energy that poured into Lin Ming’s body. He began to breathe blood vitality.

The demonic power in this flesh and blood dissolved into threads of blood red Laws that rushed toward Lin Ming’s divine soul.

Lin Ming stood still. His eyes were slowly infected with red, as if he were soaking in a blood pond of hell.

He didn’t hurry to refine this power of demons. Rather, he spurred on the power of divinity within his body, allowing it to resonate with the power of demons within him.

The so-called power of divinity was actually a fusion of astral essence, true essence, and spirit essence.

Whether it was the power of divinity or the power of demons, in the end they were merely forms of energy.

Energy and Laws were two different things.

The amount of energy that one possessed was the symbol that represented their strength. It could nearly be equated with their cultivation rank.

But comprehension of Laws represented the rate at which a martial artist could utilize this energy. The higher the Laws one comprehended, the greater their combat strength would be amongst those of the same rank.

The quality of energy was divided into ranks and Laws were also the same.

Now, Lin Ming’s Laws nearly stood at the peak of martial arts. His fusion of the Holy Scripture and Heavenly Sutra was something that had never occurred, from ancient times until now!

In terms of energy, he wanted to fuse together the power of divinity and demons, stepping onto a path no one had ever traveled…

Slowly, more and more demon power gathered within Lin Ming. He began to recklessly absorb and refine it.

Great Dao Laws drilled out without end, drawing in the power of Famine’s avatar into Lin Ming.

All of this power was the essence of Famine’s strength, and every wisp was extremely precious.

As Lin Ming swallowed more and more of this strength, his body slowly turned blood red. Every pore on his body exuded demonic energy, as if he were transpiring blood.

This strength was far too powerful. Even for Lin Ming who possessed a nearly indestructible body, the strength of this attack nearly burst him apart.

Underneath this wild impact, Lin Ming’s skin and flesh began to peel away in fragments. But as his skin and flesh peeled away, the life essence within them turned into a red flow of energy that was reabsorbed into Lin Ming’s body. Finally, all that was shed was old skin.

This situation continued without end. One day, two days… a month, two months…

Lin Ming had no idea how long this period of seclusion would continue on for. The power of demons contained within Famine was far too formidable. If he wanted to absorb it all and also achieve yin yang harmony within his body, this would be a long process and there couldn’t be a single accident that occurred in the meantime.

This period of time was long enough for many matters to occur!

Soaring Feather arrived.

And she arrived abruptly.

In fact, ever since Lin Ming went into seclusion, the human leaders within the Hidden Dragon Galaxy were all waiting for Soaring Feather to appear. After all, as the gathering point for all human influences in the wild universe, they were in a semi-open space within the Hidden Dragon Galaxy.

In addition, Fairy Blue Lotus had been held by them for several months. It would instead be strange if Soaring Feather didn’t come.

However, they didn’t think that not only would Soaring Feather come, but Astral Vault God King would follow her here. His figure was as great as an iron tower and his entire body seemed to be formed from metal. He didn’t have a single hair on his body. He didn’t even have hair or eyelashes and his head shined like translucent crystal.

In normal times, Astral Vault God King’s body would shimmer with a glorious light that emitted a powerful pressure. But now, this light had weakened a great deal, indicating that Astral Vault God King had consumed a great deal of energy.

He had strained himself in his battle with Divine Dream.

Two True Divinities had gathered!

As Emperor Shakya, Dark Demon Monarch, Skyrend Godlord, and the many other human Empyreans simultaneously faced these two legendary existences of the saint race, their hearts shrank and their complexions turned ugly.

Facing these two people, the strength they had gathered at the Hidden Dragon Galaxy wasn’t worthy of mention at all.

But as humanity was in a tense state, the distant skies twisted once more.

A woman in a pale blue dress walked out. She held an ice blue divine sword in her right hand and a sea blue band was wrapped around her left, like a goddess who had stepped out of the highest nine heavens.

Seeing this woman, Emperor Shakya let out a breath of relief.

Divine Dream!

Divine Dream had also arrived. With the saints and humans combined, three True Divinities had gathered!

Chapter 2053 - Threaten

Seeing Divine Dream appear, a cold light flashed in Soaring Feather’s eyes.

If it weren’t for Divine Dream, it wouldn’t have been such a long time before she was able to return to this wild universe.

The 33 Heavens were simply far too broad. No matter how fast a True Divinity was, it was impossible for them to travel through an entire universe by flying.

If they wished to travel through a universe, they had to use great void shifts.

But using great void shifts required time, and not just that but it couldn’t be interrupted midway. For someone in the midst of battle it was a nearly impossible feat to complete.

Although Divine Dream couldn’t harm Soaring Feather, just harassing her so that she couldn’t use a great void shift wasn’t difficult.

It was only afterwards that Soaring Feather God King helped Astral Vault God King in ridding himself of the shackles of the divine dream space. Then with Astral Vault God King delaying her, she had been able to withdraw and use the great void shift to travel through space.

Divine Dream certainly wouldn’t allow Soaring Feather to return to the wild universe so easily. She had already locked onto Soaring Feather and like this, a grand chase began. During the process they exchanged moves several times.

With Astral Vault God King butting his way in, the three True Divinities blocked each other. It was only after several months that they just managed to return to the wild universe.

Because of this, whether it was Soaring Feather, Divine Dream, or Astral Vault, all of them had consumed a great deal of energy.

At this time, their appearance in the Hidden Dragon Galaxy had caused the situation to become complex.

As Soaring Feather God King saw Emperor Shakya and the others, her face darkened. When she entered the wild universe and was flying towards this area, she quickly contacted the intelligence networks of the saints to find out whatever information there was, and she discovered that the humans had started to gather in the Hidden Dragon Galaxy. However, she didn’t think this gathering would be so thorough. As she roughly passed her sense over the area, she noticed there were dozens of human Empyreans in the Hidden Dragon Galaxy and nearly all of the several peak Empyreans were here.

“Divine Dream, you chased me for such a long time, from that nameless universe all the way to this wild universe and now you’ve finally caught up to me. Are you in such a hurry to fight me? Then, let’s do it here!”

As Soaring Feather God King spoke, feathers drifted down from the endless skies, forming an invisible force field that rapidly expanded outwards.

This force field formed incredibly quickly. It almost instantly covered the surrounding million miles of the star territory, completely shrouding the human alliance!

With this True Divinity force field here, it would be difficult for humanity to break out. And once three True Divinities started to fight in the Hidden Dragon Galaxy it would be catastrophic for the humans gathered here!

At this time, Soaring Feather’s expressionless face was filled with cold killing intent!

“Hahaha! Wonderful idea! We’ve been playing around all this time and today we should finally get serious! Even if I have to consume a little of my life it doesn’t matter; perhaps I might even be able to gain some comprehensions in this fight!”

Astral Vault God King laughed and pure golden astral essence gushed out from his body, burning all around him like a blazing golden flame. As he struggled with Divine Dream he had spent most of the time trapped in the divine dream space. From start to finish he had never truly fought her, causing Astral Vault God King to be extremely annoyed and angry. Now, he wanted to vent his frustrations!

Astral Vault and Soaring Feather’s response caused Divine Dream to frown. After she entered the wild universe, it became much easier to transmit news and she had already received a sound transmission from Emperor Shakya that informed her of Lin Ming’s return. She had been overjoyed to learn this but she didn’t think the situation would devolve to this step.

If they really did fight here then the consequences would be inconceivable.

“Where is Lin Ming? Call him out!”

Soaring Feather God King’s voice seemed to come from the nine nether abyss. Her incarnation had been defeated by Lin Ming and then refined by him!

As for her most beloved disciple Fairy Blue Lotus, she had no idea whether she was alive or not.

When she first learned Lin Ming was still alive, Soaring Feather God King was unbelievably shocked. She had killed Lin Ming thousands of years ago!

But reality had been laid before her. Soaring Feather carefully recalled her memories of killing Lin Ming, and she came to an incomparably startling result, one that even left her feeling a bit fearful. That was that some mysterious person had used an unbelievable technique and illusion skills far more profound than her own to deceive her!

The one she actually killed might have been a scapegoat who looked similar to Lin Ming, but at the time she had sincerely believed that she had killed him. Just who had the ability to do this?

Without a doubt, this mysterious person was far stronger than she was. And according to the techniques this person used, they must be a peerless master in terms of the soul and mental strength. Once she realized this, the person’s identity became far too apparent.

When it came to the soul and mental strength, no one could compare with the spiritas. And although the spiritas had several True Divinities, including even Soul Emperor Divine Void in the Asura Road, none of these people possessed the ability to fool her. If she disregarded those powerhouses that were hidden away and no one knew if they actually existed or not, and she also disregarded the rumored old monsters that were said to still exist from 10 billion years ago…

Then this mysterious person could only be the 33 Heavens’ Soul Emperor!

Soaring Feather didn’t know why the Soul Emperor would help Lin Ming. Could he be planning to cultivate Lin Ming so that he could be an enemy of the saints?

To sit on the mountaintop and watch tigers fight – this was a reasonable explanation. However, to raise a fierce tiger just so he could send it out to fight, didn’t the Soul Emperor fear that his actions would bring disaster unto himself?

All sorts of doubts passed through Soaring Feather’s mind, but right now she couldn’t think of all of this.

This time she had come to capture Lin Ming and settle the account of her incarnation being destroyed as well as the unknown fate of her disciple.

If Lin Ming wouldn’t come out then she would wash the Hidden Dragon Galaxy in blood!

Shua –

At this time, another divine light came shrouding down. A thin force field emerged from Empyrean Divine Dream’s body, covering the Hidden Dragon Galax. But, the scope of this force field was smaller and merely covered humanity’s spirit ships; this was equal to isolating Soaring Feather from humanity.

Seeing this, Astral Vault God King sneered. “Divine Dream, do you think that this alone is enough to block me? Destroying is always easier than protecting, and we have two people!”

Astral Vault crossed his arms against his chest and his voice began to drip with murder. “There are also my two disciples. I want to find out what happened to them!”

With two God Kings aggressively approaching, the situation had spiraled out of control. It seemed that a battle would be sparked at any moment!

At this time, Emperor Shakya stepped forwards. “Two God Kings, do you both believe that Blue Lotus, Highsun, and Darkmoon slaughtering humans is just and fine, that the countless trillions of human lives should be their military exploits, and our bones should be used to pave the road to True Divinity for those three people? And once we resist and harm your disciples, we should be damned to destruction by the heavens and earth?”

Soaring Feather didn’t respond to Emperor Shakya’s words.

With a blank face, she said, “There is no right or wrong in war, only others killing others. If Blue Lotus kills your people then you are perfectly justified in killing her. And if you’ve killed Blue Lotus, then it is simply cause and effect that I kill you in return!”

“Indeed, there is no wrong party in war. Since ancient times the winner has always been king and the loser always the villain! Then, let me tell you something, regardless of whether it is Blue Lotus, Highsun, or Darkmoon, none of them have died. They are still alive.”

With this information, Soaring Feather felt her heart tighten. She let out a long breath; Blue Lotus was still alive!

However, the icy expression on her face didn’t melt away. “Then have her come out.”

Soaring Feather God King said with a determined voice. However, Emperor Shakya flatly refused. “I’m sorry but this is impossible. Otherwise, once you forcefully take Blue Lotus away you could then turn around and kill us all. How could we believe you?”

“Are you threatening me?” Soaring Feather God King slowly descended, her clothes fluttering all around her. Her terrifying pressure slowly seeped through Divine Dream’s force field and covered Emperor Shakya.

Emperor Shakya frowned. He summoned energy to resist the pressure and proudly said, “We are far from being able to threaten you. However, Lin Ming was the one who captured your apprentice and releasing her is something that only he can decide.”

“Where is he?”

Astral Vault God King asked. After he returned to the wild universe he had still continued fighting with Divine Dream so he had only hurriedly received information. He approximately understood that Lin Ming had appeared and that he had created a reversal in the war.

He wanted to see just what this legendary super genius was like, the person said to be the number one talent in the 33 Heavens and also the youth who managed to somehow escape Soaring Feather’s chase in the past!

“Lin Ming, he is in seclusion.”

“Seclusion?”

“Yes. He is breaking through to the Empyrean realm!” Emperor Shakya didn’t hide anything. “We have taken into account the possibility the saints might worry that once Lin Ming breaks into the Empyrean realm, his strength will reach the level of True Divinities and the two of you will not be his match. So, you might try to eliminate Lin Ming ahead of time to remove any future troubles. Because of this I can only keep your disciples as guests so that you two will quietly wait here for a few days.”

Emperor Shakya slowly said. Then, Astral Vault God King began to laugh. “What did you say? After breaking through to the Empyrean realm his strength will rise above True Divinities and I won’t be his match? That’s too funny!”

Astral Vault God King mocked.

The disparity between a True Divinity and Empyrean was far too great. This wasn’t something that originated from just the difference in cultivation but also the difference in talent.

There was no True Divinity who wasn’t a peerless genius. Long before Astral Vault God King stepped into the Empyrean realm, he had been able to battle peak Empyreans without being defeated. But afterwards, let alone at the Empyrean realm, even after reaching the True Divinity realm Astral Vault King couldn’t say that he could be a match for those existences who had already been True Divinities for a long time. It could even be said that he was relatively weak amongst True Divinities.

Of these True Divinities, when they were at the Empyrean realm, just which ones had an inferior talent to Astral Vault? They had similar levels of talent and cultivation, so who could say they could jump ranks to fight?

But in comparison to Astral Vault God King’s mocking words, Soaring Feather was much more considerate.

She thought for a moment and then said, “You have no need to try provoking me. It is useless. Lin Ming must be in seclusion within the Hidden Dragon Galaxy!”

Emperor Shakya didn’t reply. Lin Ming had indeed gone into seclusion in the Hidden Dragon Galaxy. Before, Emperor Shakya had urged Lin Ming to search for some hiding place so that it would be more difficult for Soaring Feather to find him. This was to prevent Soaring Feather from experiencing a stroke of rage and disregarding Blue Lotus’s life to strike out at Lin Ming.

However, Lin Ming didn’t do this. He was the one who called the human forces here, so how could he abandon them as soon as they arrived, using them as his shield?

Moreover, Lin Ming believed that Soaring Feather wouldn’t be rash in her actions. There were all sorts of reasons involved in this…

Chapter 2056 – The Restriction of the Nine Stars

“Let us go over and take a look!”

As Soaring Feather spoke, the yin yang vortex swept outwards, growing increasingly large. It already covered a 100,000 mile region and was able to cover an entire planet.

“This phenomenon… is truly special… this brat!”

Astral Vault God King huffed out. He couldn’t help but acknowledge that Lin Ming’s phenomena when he broke through the Empyrean realm were far greater than his own. Generally speaking, the phenomena of an Empyrean breakthrough were a manifestation of the Laws that the martial artist cultivated, or the types of energy they used.

This was because when a martial artist broke through to the Empyrean realm, the Laws they cultivated within themselves would sublimate, becoming a part of the Heavenly Dao.

Of course, the Heavenly Dao was divided into higher and lower divisions. There was the Heavenly Dao of a great world and the 33 Heavenly Daos, and even more beyond that. An Empyrean’s Heavenly Dao only consisted of a small portion in which they specialized, and that part would manage to achieve a lower standard of the Heavenly Dao. However, this was terrifying enough; it meant that when a martial artist became an Empyrean, they were able to break free from the shackles of mortality, becoming sanctified, becoming the true ruler of a world.

Within the three great cultivation systems, every one of the 33 Heavenly Daos revealed a different phenomenon. Astral Vault God King could be considered a person with vast experience, but he had actually never seen this phenomenon that was occurring around Lin Ming, nor was he able to recognize it.

And at this time, a change occurred!

In that incomparably large yin yang vortex in the air, energy raged and the Heavenly Dao Laws gathered!

Layers of thick clouds grew, every wisp of the dark cloud woven together with profound dao patterns.

These dao patterns were multi-colored and magnificent, incredibly deep and seeming to contain the vicissitudes of time within them, as if some unknown divine god had carved the years inside so that they would shine on for eternity.

Dao patterns revolved and the sound of the flowing Great Dao echoed through the air, sounding like countless mountains colliding as it resonated with the world.

Just this flowing dao rhythm shocked the mind, capable of scattering one’s divine soul.

The surrounding observers all felt a tremendous pressure on them.

As more dark clouds gathered, the beat of thunder sounded from within, as if some unparalleled divine king was smashing battle drums within.

These dao patterns finally wove together in the dark clouds and formed into crimson thunder!

This crimson thunder contained overwhelming infernal energy. Accompanied by the boundless Great Dao Laws, it howled over Lin Ming’s head!

Waves of thunder beat in the skies, every wisp of lightning as thick as a mountain as they tore through the star territory.

Sonic waves of the Great Dao continued to ring, like the original sound of the universe itself, the bell of twilight that deafened the ears.

“Heavenly tribulation! When a martial artist breaks into the Empyrean realm they must experience heavenly tribulation and now it has arrived! It contains the true sounds of the Great Dao and is interwoven with the judgment of thunder created by the Laws!”

The many martial artists present felt just how terrifying this heavenly tribulation was.

Most of them were the elites of humanity and they knew that when a martial artist broke into the Empyrean realm, their Laws would sublimate, rising to the will of the Heavenly Dao, and their incarnation would also become the ruler of a world. This was a challenge against the Heavenly Dao, thus they had to experience heavenly tribulation!

However, amongst humanity, Empyreans came around once every several hundred thousand years, thus only a minor number of those present had witnessed other Empyreans crossing their heavenly tribulation!

The tribulation clouds became increasingly rich and gloomy. Everyone could feel how horrifying the energy contained in these dark clouds was. Many young martial artists couldn’t withstand the pressure and began breathing in great heaving gulps, and there were even some martial artists with weaker cultivations that began streaming with sweat, finding it nearly impossible to stand.

However, no matter how difficult it was, no matter how much they suffered, they stubbornly endured, their eyes staring unblinkingly towards the far off tribulation clouds.

This was Lin Ming crossing heavenly tribulation, an event you wouldn’t even see in a hundred million years!

In the past, when martial artists broke through to the Empyrean realm they would invite all their good friends and comrades, including even their own disciples to attend this grand ceremony. To young martial artists, this was a rare lucky chance!

This was because when an Empyrean crossed heavenly tribulation the Great Dao Law would descend. For young martial artists this was a mental baptism that would provide them with great inspirations, clearing their minds and hearts!

Hum –

The true sounds of the Great Dao continued to circulate. Let alone the juniors of the younger generation, even the Empyreans felt a faint pressure in this environment. As for Empyrean Vast Universe, Lan Xin, and the others, goosebumps had risen all over their bodies. As they looked at these tribulation clouds, even they were gaining enlightenment.

To an Empyrean, the Laws they cultivated were mostly settled thus they comprehended slightly less. Those that truly profited were World Kings and Great World Kings!

Their cultivations were higher than the juniors’ and their understandings of the Heavenly Dao were also more profound than the juniors’. As they respectfully listened to the true sound of the Great Dao, they all felt as if their bodies were being washed through by the clearest spring, their dao understandings being smashed by countless hammers, becoming even stronger and more durable.

In particular, before this heavenly tribulation, some Great World Kings that were close to breaking into the Empyrean realm seemed to hear countless Supremes whispering the secrets of the Great Dao into their ears. Some puzzles that had long plagued their cultivations and had formed walls suddenly showed signs of loosening.

Because of Lin Ming crossing heavenly tribulation, the skies above the originally confusing road to becoming an Empyrean seemed to open up, shining down light that illuminated the path forwards!

This was an inestimably valuable great lucky chance. Thus, many World Kings went wild with happiness, all of them wishing they could dive into those tribulation clouds!

Of course, those tribulation clouds were too terrifying. If they really did rush in then they would instantly disintegrate into ashes.

“This brat! He has drawn down tribulation clouds of the 33 Heavens! That is the highest level of Empyrean heavenly tribulations, and looking at it, it seems to possess the most terrifying kind of power.”

Astral Vault God King thoughtfully said.

Soaring Feather God King’s response was much slower. “With Lin Ming’s current strength, it would be strange if he didn’t bring down 33 Heavens tribulation clouds. These tribulation clouds are terrifying but it is unlikely to affect him. Rather, this will be his chance. He will borrow this heavenly tribulation to temper his body and consolidate his foundation. That would be the best choice for him.”

Listening to Soaring Feather’s words, Astral Vault’s face darkened. When a new Empyrean crossed heavenly tribulation, this was a lucky chance for those observing. But, the greatest beneficiary was of course the new Empyrean themselves.

The more terrifying the heavenly tribulation was, the greater the lucky chance. When Astral Vault compared the scale of the heavenly tribulation clouds he summoned in the past, he knew they were much worse than Lin Ming’s. This left him with a strange taste in his heart.

At this time, beneath the divine might of heavenly tribulation, every inch of Lin Ming’s skin began to shine.

Basked in endless light, he was like a great sun floating in the skies. No matter how mighty the heavenly tribulation was, it didn’t seem to affect him; he didn’t even bat an eye.

Rumble rumble rumble!

Heavenly tribulation approached. The power fermenting in the clouds became increasingly terrifying. At this time, an Empyrean that lacked sufficient skill would have already challenged the tribulation clouds ahead of time.

No one believed Lin Ming lacked skill. Thus, he would wait until the heavenly tribulation clouds fermented to their limit before he fought them.

“It’s almost at the limit!”

“It’s finally about to start!”

By now, the tribulation clouds in the skies had expanded to several hundred thousand miles, covering this entire region of the star territory!

The energy contained within was saturated to the limit. Although more and more heaven and earth origin energy gathered, it was a tiny amount compared to what was already there.

According to previous experiences, heavenly tribulation was about to begin!

At this point, let alone the juniors, even Emperor Shakya, Dark Demon Monarch, and the others all held their breath, their concentration completely focused on what was occurring.

But below the tribulation clouds, Lin Ming still hadn’t started preparations to withstand the heavenly tribulation. He didn’t even look up. All of his attention was focused on absorbing the mystical power of Laws to further stabilize his inner world.

Within the chaos, the energies of yin and yang seemed to evolve into all living creatures.

The light and clear power of divinity soared into the skies, condensing into auspicious clouds that lingered about.

The heavy and thick power of demons sank to the ground, forming blood red continents that stretched towards infinity.

The surrounding Laws became increasingly condensed and perfect.

Suddenly, Lin Ming’s eye flashed open. His eyes seemed to contain pitch black chaos that swallowed all. Even when lower Empyreans saw him they felt their minds shake, as if their divine souls would be dragged in and absorbed.

Seeing Lin Ming’s aura finally erupt, everyone held their breath.

The vast and overwhelming momentum of this heavenly tribulation was simply unprecedented, whether it was in the past or present.

It was hard to imagine just what scene would occur when Lin Ming crossed heavenly tribulation.

But at this time, another change occurred!

Lin Ming breathed thunder. With a bass roar, the surrounding galaxy shook.

A vast aura rose from within his body. Wisps of starlight gushed out from every pore, forming mystical runes in the air. These runes transformed into chains that waved back and forth within the boundless dark heavenly tribulation clouds.

“What is he doing?” Seeing this, some human martial artists couldn’t help but ask in bewilderment, finding it hard to respond.

Just as everyone was puzzled, marvelous fluctuations of the Great Dao rules appeared in the heavenly tribulation.

Small swathes of starry space began to appear from within those dark clouds.

This was a breathtaking sight. From those obviously thick tribulation clouds, part of them was actually turning into starry space.

Nine titanic stars appeared, exuding the aura of the Great Dao Laws.

Their starlight fell upon Lin Ming, bathing him.

“This is…”

Everyone peered deeper in. They could see that these nine stars seemed to be imprisoned and locked in by chains that twined about them like red dragons.

These chains emitted an irresistible mystical strength that blocked the divine light of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace so that the stars couldn’t move.

“This is the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace. This is…”

Many of the human martial artists present were vastly experienced individuals so they naturally recognized the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace immediately.

But, the one with the most profound understanding was in truth Astral Vault God King.

At this time, what people paid attention to were not the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace themselves, but the dark red chains that bound them!

From their far-off point of view, these chains appeared extremely slender. Compared to the incandescent stars, the chains seemed insignificant. However, the divine spiritual light woven into them caused the mind to shake!

“This is…”

In Mount Potala, Great Limitless Buddha’s wizened eyes flashed with a brilliant light!

Great Limitless Buddha was already old. Although he was a peak Empyrean, in terms of strength he was much worse than Emperor Shakya. However, he possessed an incredibly rich trove of knowledge. As he saw these dark red divine chains, the first thing that came to his mind was the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace that was swallowed by Famine 3.6 billion years ago!

In truth, Famine didn’t swallow the 33 Heavenly Dao Laws. Rather, it had swallowed the destiny that linked humanity to the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, the causal relationship that connected the two.

And, this sort of swallowing was actually a type of Laws unto itself. These Laws wove together into divine chains that locked away the starlight, causing it so that human martial artists couldn’t be illuminated by the starlight of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace.

Because of this reason, ever since 3.6 billion years ago, the human martial artists that cultivated the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace had nearly gone extinct!

“So that’s what it is!”

Divine Dream muttered. Within her normally quiet and placid eyes, ripples appeared, showing just how difficult she was finding it to compose herself.

At this moment, she finally understood just what sort of relationship bound together Famine, the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, and the Nine Divine Shifts that the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign desired to change!

Chapter 2057 – Break Past the Martial Song

After Famine swallowed the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, the starlight was locked away by the divine chains so it was naturally isolated from humanity.

Then, where did all this starlight that should have been humanity’s go to?

Divine Dream suspected that it had all been swallowed by Famine. In other words, Famine had swallowed the destiny that originally belonged to humanity and turned it into its own destiny.

The light of the Nine Stars that should have fallen upon humanity was transformed into Famine’s energy.

Then… the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign swallowing the Nine Divine Shifts should be a similar situation.

Not only did the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign wish to utterly destroy humanity but he also wished to swallow humanity’s destiny, turning it into his own!

Humanity’s current strength was already weak enough. The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign would first strike out at humanity and slowly eat away at them. In the future, once he was powerful enough, he would extend his tentacles to the spiritas and also swallow the destiny of their race.

At the end, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign might even use Famine to take over the world!

Thinking of this, Divine Dream felt just how heavy the ambitions of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign were. At the same time she also worried about Lin Ming. Since he caused the divine chains that blocked the Nine Stars of the Heavenly Dao to appear, did he plan on cutting them apart?

To cut apart the order of the Heavenly Dao, this was no minor matter.

The one doing so would have to bear the sanction of the Heavenly Dao, spurring on heavenly tribulation!

Now, within this star territory, heavenly tribulation had already formed above Lin Min’s head. But Lin Ming didn’t try to cross this tribulation now and instead chose to use this moment to face the Nine Stars Heavenly Dao. This was an extremely dangerous choice!

All the human martial artists held their breath. At this time, only a small number of Empyreans knew what he was doing; most people weren’t sure what was occurring.

As everyone couldn’t help but ask, at this moment they saw Lin Ming shoot up into the skies, tearing through space!

His body emitted resounding crackling sounds, as if mountains and rivers were breaking apart, as if planets were collapsing.

He drew out the Black Dragon Spear!

The Black Dragon Spear seemed to condense the heaviness of a great world. Endless dao patterns wove together on the surface of the spear shaft, looking like a black dragon that soared upwards!

Blood red scales with a cold metallic luster appeared on Lin Ming, as if something were trying to struggle from the depths of his body.

At this moment, Lin Ming had used the power of the Asura blood!

At the same time, five Dao Palaces opened up within his body. These five Dao Palaces corresponded to the power of the Nine Stars in the sky, faintly forming the divine brilliance of order.

Lin Ming’s speed increased with every moment. In his eyes he no longer saw surging tribulation clouds but only those divine chains.

The Black Dragon Spear slashed out, cutting down on those chains as if it would rip apart the world!

In that moment, an all-swallowing divine light covered the surrounding endless space. Beneath the pall of this divine light, even Empyreans were forced to close their eyes.

As for the younger generations, they were long since unable to withstand it!

“Draw back!”

People cried out in alarm. Human rulers formed protective true essence shields to shelter the young disciples as they rapidly retreated. Many people were faint of breath and nearly fell down where they stood.

The Black Dragon Spear collided with the divine chains in the divine light. Yet, it was strangely silent without a single sound. Even so, people could see the endless runes being destroyed and the impact shockwaves rushed out like a raging tide in all directions.

Shua!

The void in front of Lin Ming was cut into countless fragments by the tide of energy.

As for those blood red divine chains, cracks began to appear within them under Lin Ming’s assault.

Time seemed to come to a standstill. Everyone watched as the divine chains that sealed away the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace turned into fragments of starlight as they thoroughly disintegrated!

The Nine Stars of the Dao Palace were released from their confinement and began to shine ever brighter. That endless starlight fell upon Lin Ming’s body, fell upon all the martial artists of humanity.

At this moment, every human martial artist could feel their blood vitality starting to race beneath the shimmer of this starlight. Some martial artists who had cultivated body transformation Laws and even some martial artists who had opened the Eight Inner Hidden Gates felt all of their blood energy seeming to condense in their bodies, becoming a billowing rocket that desired to hurtle towards the heavens!

“This is the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace! The strength of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, I felt it!”

Some martial artists uttered with shock, completely filled with disbelief.

When human martial artists cultivated the Eight Inner Hidden Gates, in truth the main reason they did so was because they wanted to open the Gate of Opening and enhance their own perception.

As for the true Gate of Life and Gate of Death, and the even higher Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, they had never considered it.

This was because cultivating the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace was restricted by the Heavenly Dao rules, and required a titanic level of resources, an amount that not even Empyrean Holy Lands were able to withstand!

Moreover, the chance of success was near zero!

After all sorts of reasons were added together, and especially since cultivating the body transformation system didn’t provide benefits that were too heaven-defying, very few people chose to dual cultivate essence and energy; it was simply far too difficult a road.

If it was said that some martial artists only faintly felt the strength of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, then Lin Ming was completely bathed in this starlight, undergoing a baptism of the Nine Stars!

When those divine chains broke, as the one who broke them, Lin Ming directly faced the Nine Stars. The endless starlight fell onto him like a gushing waterfall, bathing him!

This was the starlight accumulated over 3.6 billion years!

Although Famine had swallowed this starlight, the 33 Heavenly Daos were incomparably huge to begin with. No matter how strong Famine’s Laws of Swallowing were, it was impossible for him to swallow all the starlight.

Because of the restriction of the divine chains, after the light of the Nine Stars accumulated year after year it had undergone a qualitative change!

As this starlight violently poured into Lin Ming, his mortal body began to be reborn as his muscles and marrow were washed!

Beneath the divine light, his skin, skeleton, muscles, organs, everything became completely translucent.

The five Dao Palaces within his body recklessly absorbed this divine light, becoming increasingly grand and complex.

If the Dao Palaces within Lin Ming’s body were comparable to the imperial palace of a mortal, then after constantly growing, it had already turned into something like Divine Dream Heavenly Palace or the Good Fortune Saint Palace!

After lifting the shackles upon the Heavenly Dao, Lin Ming obtained the greatest advantages. The Dao Palaces that were suppressed within his body suddenly became several times more powerful. Their surging power was no longer blocked from Lin Ming’s body!

It was like his flesh and blood blended with the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, becoming a part of his instinct.

At this moment, Lin Ming could feel his strength wildly grow; it was already difficult to measure with numbers alone!

Without a doubt, 3.6 billion years ago when Famine swallowed the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, it had suffocated humanity’s body transformation system, making it impossibly difficult to train in.

But if one could be like Lin Ming and break through the chains of the Heavenly Dao even when that path was blocked, forcefully opening up the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, then once those divine chains were lifted and the connection of Lin Ming’s mortal body with the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace restored, then the body transformation system strength he possessed would far outstrip anything that human martial artists were able to attain in the past!

In the world of martial arts, the deeper the price the greater the profit. Now that Lin Ming had paid so much to break past the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace in the past, his harvests were that much greater!

The light of the Nine Stars was simply too vast. Lin Ming’s body had long been fully saturated and it was difficult for him to continue digesting all this starlight.

But at this moment, without any hesitation, Lin Ming compressed this infinite starlight and thrust it into his limbs!

Bang!

Lin Ming’s arms and legs were flooded with energy. His blood vessels stuck out like earthworms, nearly blowing open.

And in the skies, amongst those nine great stars shining up high, one of them shined with an incomparable brilliance, like a dawning sun!

For one of those stars to turn into a blazing sun, all of the martial artists present were shocked.

“What is happening?”

Someone cried out in alarm.

“That is one of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace – the Martial Song Star!”

An Empyrean who understood the Laws of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace slowly whispered. Although humanity’s inheritances concerning the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace had been lost, there were still Empyreans who had peered through ancient records concerning them.

Within the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, the Martial Song Star was the one that corresponded to war and slaughter.

It was diametrically opposed to the Merciful Song Star.

The Dao Palace that the Martial Song Star corresponded with was the Martial Sovereign Dao Palace, also known as the Cardinal Direction Dao Palace!

The heavens had four extremes – east, west, south, and north, the four directions that led to the ends of the world.

Humans also had four extremes – they were the arms and legs. They were the limbs that allowed humans to walk, work, fight, live, they were the limbs that were related to all movements!

When essence gathering system martial artists fought, they could manifest the Laws within their inner world and manipulate the power of the world.

But when a body transformation system martial artist fought, they relied on their four limbs!

These four limbs seemed simple, but the truth was that they were the ultimate manifestation of a body transformation system martial artist’s combat strength!

Thus, the Martial Sovereign Dao Palace was an extremely important Dao Palace within the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace. Once opened, a martial artist’s bodily strength would increase several times over!

Wu –

Wu –

Wu –

Stars trembled. Starlight surged.

The Martial Song Star shined bright in the skies, open and honest, yet bringing with it a terrifyingly suppressive feeling. Every martial artist could feel an extremely tyrannical momentum from within, an unbending strength!

The Martial Song Star was a brave star, one decisive in killing, one that roamed the world without fear!

Of the Nine Stars, it wasn’t just the Martial Song Star that was a brave star, but it was the one filled with a firm and straightforward meaning!

The Martial Song Star shined and starlight fell down. Lin Ming felt the strength within his arms and legs, the saturated starlight, being compressed without end, as if a smoldering volcano were ready to erupt from within him.

“Martial Sovereign Dao Palace – open!”

Lin Ming pushed against the starlight, firing towards the Martial Song Star.

With his incomparably formidable accumulations and the momentum from just breaking into the Empyrean realm, Lin Ming compressed the power of this starlight to the limit!

But at this time, blood red divine thunder fell onto Lin Ming’s body!

Bang!

Lin Ming’s body shook. The moment the blood red thunder struck him, his speed slowed and blood flowed out from the corners of his lips.

He paused, staring into the skies like a hawk. He saw that the tribulation clouds of the nine heavens had already condensed to a terrifying degree!

Moreover, the surrounding light of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace also seemed to gather towards the tribulation clouds. The tribulation clouds had yet to reach their most potent stage!

However, the heavenly tribulation was already impatient to descend!

Chapter 2058 – Heavenly Tribulation Tempering Body

The thunder of the highest nine heavens savagely howled.

It was only now that people discovered their eyes had been focused on the Martial Song Star, but because the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace had appeared, the tribulation clouds were beginning to experience a heaven-shaking change!

That heavenly tribulation was no longer in the form of dark clouds, but was now a golden lake that rippled outwards.

Endless streams of the Great Dao surged in this lake, breeding a terrifying divine thunder of heavenly tribulation within.

This divine thunder came in crimson, gold, purple, and an even more terrifying rainbow hue.

That seven-colored thunder was bizarrely peaceful. Just by looking at it, one’s soul seemed to fall into illusion.

“This is… a variation change in heavenly tribulation! As Senior Lin is crossing heavenly tribulation, he severed the divine chains of order and touched the Heavenly Dao Laws once more, causing the power of the heavenly tribulation to be even more terrifying!”

“How can anyone withstand such horrifying heavenly tribulation!?”

At this moment, the complexions of many human martial artists changed. Originally what Lin Ming faced was the highest level of the 33 Heavens tribulation, and now that it changed, even a peak Empyrean would be smashed into ashes. If a normal Empyrean were beneath these clouds, let alone crossing this heavenly tribulation, they wouldn’t even be able to stand!

Lin Ming was their spiritual leader. In terms of prestige amongst the human race, he even surpassed Divine Dream.

If any accident were to happen to Lin Ming the consequences would be unbelievable.

In Demon Fairy Palace, Xiao Moxian’s heart was gripped. Standing beside her, Mu Qianyu and Qin Xingxuan also had worried expressions on their faces. This pressure was far too horrifying. Even though they were within the Empyrean force field set up by Xiao Moxian, they still felt it suffocating to breathe…

Chi-la!

Another bolt of thunder came chopping down!

Lin Ming stood still. At this time, the starlight gathered unto his body reached an unprecedented peak. He looked up, staring at the increasingly strong heavenly tribulation that approached.

Firming his mind, Lin Ming grasped the Black Dragon Spear and hurtled into the crimson tribulation clouds!

“Lin Ming!”

Xiao Moxian cried out in alarm. The human martial artists were also shocked!

From far away, everyone saw Lin Ming’s tiny figure rushing into those terrifying and roiling tribulation clouds that represented the might of the heavens and earth. This scene became something that eternally fixed itself into the hearts of those present!

The more one approached tribulation clouds, the more powerful the heavenly tribulation was. This was tantamount to provoking the Heavenly Dao itself!

“He is using heavenly tribulation to temper his body and force out the limit of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace within his body!” Soaring Feather said, her eyes shining with brilliance. And beside her, Astral Vault had an ugly complexion; this method was simply far too crazy!

Piki paka!

In that instant, endless arcs of thunder fell down upon Lin Ming!

Blinding beams of divine light lit up the world. From afar, Lin Ming seemed to have become the only existence within the heavens and earth!

Beneath the brutal barrage of thunder, Lin Ming’s body was covered in blood. He roared out, “Martial Sovereign Dao Palace, open again!”

Even though he was interrupted by heavenly tribulation the first time he tried to open the Martial Sovereign Dao Palace, Lin Ming paid little heed to this. He ignored the heavenly tribulation and impacted upwards a second time.

Since heavenly tribulation had entered his body, Lin Ming would simply use the power of this heavenly tribulation to further temper his body, allowing the Martial Sovereign Dao Palace to open even more thoroughly.

Kacha!

Lin Ming’s mortal body seemed as if it would explode in that instant. Beneath the limit of strength, Lin Ming felt a terrifying power of thunder gather into his already burning arms and legs. In these places it was like four doors were rumbling as they were being pushed open.

The power of starlight was compressed in his limbs, interweaving into an eternally glorious Dao Palace. This Dao Palace was the Martial Sovereign Dao Palace!

As this Dao Palace that represented the ultimate martial strength appeared, it was soaked in that violent and fierce thunder!

Thunder smashed into the temple, hardening it and making it shine even more radiantly!

Divine thunder could be used to refine weapons. Now, Lin Ming was using the thunder of this heavenly tribulation to hammer upon his newly formed Dao Palace!

In that moment the strength within Lin Ming’s body reached a new peak.

With a punch, he could crush the void. With a kick, a river of stars would tremble.

He had finally opened the sixth Dao Palace!

In that moment, the power of divinity and demons born within Lin Ming’s inner world began flow out, surrounding the six Dao Palaces like a rising tide.

The six Dao Palaces released a mystical strength. Dao patterns floated atop the chaotic energy surrounding the Dao Palaces and joined together like continuous mountain ranges, forming a marvelous fused state.

The two yin yang powers of divinity and demons represented the most extreme origins and had no conflict at all with these six Dao Palaces that represented the strength of the Heavenly Dao.

With this strength as a medium, the six Dao Palaces began to swirl around in the yin yang tide covered with dao patterns.

At this time, Lin Ming suddenly reached out his hand! The power of Laws converged. High in the skies, the chains that imprisoned the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace were grasped in his hand.

These divine chains were already cut apart by Lin Ming. The spirit mark of Famine’s soul had already been refined by Lin Ming but the source Laws still existed within, incredibly powerful.

For the last 3.6 billion years, these divine chains had imprisoned the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace and had undergone a baptism of infinite starlight. They gathered the essence of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace Heavenly Dao.

Without hesitation, Lin Ming smashed these divine chains apart and directly fused them into his body. The crushed chains turned into countless tiny Law fragments that gushed into the six Dao Palaces.

These divine chains had been able to imprison the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace. Now, they turned into silk threads that connected the six Dao Palaces within Lin Ming’s body.

For a time, it was like a similar bloodline was forged into the six Dao Palaces within Lin Ming’s body. These six Dao Palaces originally resonated with each other and now they began exchanging energy, rapidly merging together.

The Nine Star dao patterns of these six Dao Palaces wove together, overlapping against each other, embedding into each other.

This sort of fusion was a true fusion of the Great Dao. Divine spiritual power harmonized as one.

But at the same time, they still maintained a kind of independence, retaining their true source strength of the Great Dao.

It could be said that this was a transformation of the Great Dao’s strength, a sublimation.

Rumble rumble rumble –

As these six Dao Palaces sublimated, Lin Ming opened his daevic eye. He thought that his acupoints were opened like gates and immortals lived within them, reciting chants of the Great Dao.

All of these feelings allowed his heart of martial arts to climb to new heights.

Some obscure things he encountered in his road of cultivation also seemed to open up, as if the fog in front of them started to clear away…

Climbing, climbing, Lin Ming’s momentum soared into the skies, continuing to climb.

As he blinked, infinite galaxies seemed to be destroyed in his pupils, and worlds seemed to form and evolve.

This sort of scene already surpassed that of an Empyrean; it was an evolution of the highest Great Dao.

As these six Dao Palaces fused together without a single gap between them, blood began to burn like divine flames, shooting up into the heavens, transforming into True Dragons and True Phoenixes that cried and roared.

The Great Dao Laws hummed as if they were all submitting themselves to Lin Ming.

Seeing this sight, the low level martial artists were unsure what was occurring. But as for the Empyreans and God Kings present, they were stunned speechless!

Then, before they could tell what changes were occurring within Lin Ming’s body, Lin Ming’s figure suddenly flickered. He grabbed the Black Dragon Spear and fired himself into the 33 Heavens tribulation clouds once more!

This time, Lin Ming pushed forwards with unstoppable momentum, as if he would break through the heavens!

After being provoked by Lin Ming again and again, that raging heavenly tribulation was like fire with oil poured onto it. It became increasingly murderous and ferocious as it swept down!

This was no longer arcs of thunder, but a golden sea woven together by endless divine thunder!

Lin Ming roared out loud and the Black Dragon viciously slashed out!

Chi-la!

The vault of the heavens seemed to be torn asunder. This spear chopped that golden sea of thunder in half!

One split into two!

Lin Ming devoured this vast power of thunder in great gulps and continued rushing forwards with irresistible force. This time, Lin Ming’s goal was the 33 Heavens tribulation clouds!

Tribulation clouds were the most concentrated form of heavenly retribution as well as the most terrifying existence. Since ancient times, when Empyreans crossed their heavenly tribulations they had no choice but to dread these tribulation clouds. But at this time, Lin Ming was rushing towards these tribulation clouds.

Lin Ming didn’t hesitate; he slashed out his spear once more!

This spear was wrapped in the great strength of the six Dao Palaces as well as an unsurpassed heart of martial arts that seemed as if it would step above the 33 Heavenly Daos!

Chi-la!

It was like a universe-tearing strength erupted. In everyone’s shocked gaze, the 33 Heavens tribulation clouds that represented the highest rules of the Heavenly Dao were actually split apart by Lin Ming!

“His spear broke through the tribulation clouds!”

A human Empyrean cried out in awe.

And, Soaring Feather and Astral Vault were even more shocked. As peerless powerhouses who had withstood the baptism of heavenly tribulation before, they were profoundly aware of how terrifying these 33 Heavens tribulation clouds were!

But such tribulation clouds were forcefully shorn apart by Lin Ming!

This strength was simply far too horrifying!

Chapter 2059 – Battling the Heavenly Dao

The moment the tribulation clouds were torn apart by Lin Ming’s great strength, the deep golden lake emitted a vast and bass roar. This was the thundering of heaven. A gap appeared in the golden lake and a divine sword seemed to chop out, overflowing with the golden light of the Great Dao!

As this golden Great Dao appeared, it aimed straight at Lin Ming.

The golden lake began to shine with a blinding light. War chariots drawn by golden thunder dragons seemed to gallop out from the river of time, hurtling their way towards Lin Ming.

Standing on each war chariot was a divine god in golden armor. Their faces were without expression and their bodies flooded out with boundless killing intent, as if this entire part of the universe had turned into a bloody battlefield, filled with slaughter and death.

Each chariot was marked with countless scars. Every trace exuded a shockingly violent and brutal aura, as if they bore testimony to every war since ancient times.

“This… could this also be heavenly tribulation? How come there is no thunder but legions of golden war chariots?”

Many human martial artists were shocked. They had never seen nor heard of such heavenly tribulation before.

“Amitabha… these are war chariots manifested from the power of heavenly retribution…” Great Limitless Buddha looked up towards the heavens, his complexion earnest. His long white eyebrows trembled. “Those atop the war chariots should be… ancient divine spirits! In the legends there are peerless characters of the 33 Heavens that went to war for endless years. Afterwards, although they eventually died in the endless river of time, when they crossed their heavenly tribulation they were remembered by the Heavenly Dao. Now, even after they died and their mortal bodies turned to dust, they have cast down an immortal dao foundation that was not destroyed but instead kept within the Heavenly Dao…

“If I’m not wrong, then those golden war chariots and those golden divine spirits should be phantoms of those ancient peerless characters… and they are now being brought into reality by this heavenly tribulation.”

Hearing the words of Great Limitless Buddha, many human Empyreans’ complexions changed. After these ancient peerless characters died, their phantoms were left behind in the Heavenly Dao?

Although they didn’t know who these phantoms once were, what they knew without a doubt was that out of all them present, besides Divine Dream, none of them had the qualifications to leave behind their phantoms in the Heavenly Dao.

Although these Heavenly Dao phantoms were not the true bodies and perhaps they only contained a tenth of their strength from before they died, or maybe even only a twentieth, but these were all once dreadful characters capable of flipping over the 33 Heavens. With so many gathered here, this was truly terrifying!

Many of them had likely killed True Divinities before!

Facing these Heavenly Dao phantoms, Lin Ming didn’t hesitate nor did he feel fear. He stepped forwards, the Black Dragon Spear grasped in his hands. Behind him, the six fused Dao Palaces of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace began to fill Lin Ming with infinite strength. A boiling fighting spirit burned through his blood. Even if an ancient peerless powerhouse were to truly stand before him, he would still remain fearless in his desire to fight them!

As he rapidly flew upwards, his back split open. A fierce suit of bone armor like that of an abyssal emerged from his body, piercing through his black clothes.

He stepped through space, shooting upwards like a bolt of thunder, his entire body from head to toe emitting an overwhelming momentum. The Black Dragon Spear emitted an excited cry, howling like a black dragon as he flew to the heavens!

The golden-armored divine spirits remained without expression. They drew out golden halberds and rushed towards Lin Ming!

The moment the Black Dragon Spear clashed with those war halberds, beams of spear light shot out, swallowing the surrounding vastness of space!

Space seemed to solidify. In the boundless world, it was like only the black spear remained, blocking out the entire space.

Kacha!

The golden war halberd was directly smashed to pieces!

Even that golden-armored giant’s arms fractured. After the black spear broke through the golden war halberd, it pounded down upon the ancient divine spirit’s armor.

In that moment, the armor blew apart. The golden-armored giant was crushed into an endless rain of light by the Black Dragon Spear!

Bang!

Bang!

Lin Ming broke into the group of golden war chariots, his Black Dragon Spear singing its own epic!

With each spear strike, with each clash with the golden weapons of the ancient divine spirits, a heavy sound would echo through the heavens and earth.

It was hard to imagine just how much strength was behind these collisions!

Peng!

Another golden-armored divine spirit was shattered to pieces!

Lin Ming was an incomparably fierce war god, treading forwards with unstoppable force!

However, there were simply far too many ancient divine spirits surrounding Lin Ming, still over 20 of them. When Lin Ming killed two of them, a golden-armored divine spirit managed to stab its halberd into his back.

Black scales broke and blood sprinkled down.

The human martial artists felt their hearts skip a beat. However, before they could cry out in alarm, they discovered that the spear of this ancient divine spirit was only able to pierce halfway through to the halberd head.

Lin Ming’s mortal body was like a piece of the toughest divine iron, unable to be shaken!

Peng!

Lin Ming turned his hand and smashed the head of this golden armored divine spirit!

The golden-armored divine spirit shook and fell downwards.

At the same time, the flesh on Lin Ming’s back began to wriggle, regenerating at a speed visible to the naked eye. In just a few breaths of time the wound had already stopped bleeding.

Lin Ming had opened six Dao Palaces of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, and one of them was responsible for managing the recovery and restoration of flesh and blood – the Natal Life Dao Palace. After opening the Natal Life Dao Palace, even if he were to sever an arm or a leg he would still be able to grow another one. Even if a three foot long gash were to be torn open in his skin, rapidly regenerating wouldn’t be a problem either.

“His wound recovered!”

“Even after being sneak attacked by a halberd, he managed to turn and smash the other’s head!”

Seeing this scene, all of the martial artists were left dumbfounded. This method was simply far too fierce, it scared one silly.

While being attacked, he forcefully withstood it without problem and then struck back with a life-reaping attack!

Lin Ming was powerful to begin with, and coupled with such a fighting method where he didn’t even seem to care about his own safety, just who could fight against him?

But at this time, Lin Ming started his battle with the golden-armored divine spirits once more!

Rumble rumble rumble!

Golden ripples spread out, carrying with them the boundlessly mighty force of Laws. Another golden-armored warrior was destroyed by Lin Ming!

Lin Ming brutally killed a path open in the numerous ancient divine spirit phantoms and rushed into the golden tribulation clouds.

Bang!

Lin Ming slashed out his spear once more, chopping down on the surface of that golden lake and causing giant golden waves to rise up. The monstrous slaughter energy accompanied the boundless Great Dao Laws, condensing around Lin Ming.

In the tidal waves of thunder, every bolt was as thick as a mountain, tearing open the world without end.

The true sounds of the Great Dao rose up, as if they were the sounds from the origin of the universe. They rang like bells from the primordial chaos, awakening the mind to unknown truths.

“Ancient divine spirits, pond of heavenly thunder… true sounds of the Great Dao…”

Divine Dream muttered to herself as she watched Lin Ming submerge himself in lightning.

All sorts of heavenly tribulation phenomena manifested around Lin Ming. To other martial artists this would have been a fatal judgment of the Heavenly Dao, but to Lin Ming this was a great stroke of good fortune!

Nearly half of the golden-armored divine spirits had already been cut down by Lin Ming. But at this time, Lin Ming barraged the golden lake without end!

Strike after strike, the Black Dragon Spear became a dancing dark dragon that tore through the tribulation clouds.

With every explosion of golden waves, they turned into countless Law fragments. Most of these Law fragments sprinkled into the endless starry space, but a great deal was still absorbed by Lin Ming!

During this continued onslaught, the golden tribulation clouds became increasingly pale. The highly concentrated energy no longer took the form of a lake, but turned into layers of fog. This fog continued to disperse. As Lin Ming soaked within it, it became dimmer with each passing second.

He recklessly swallowed and absorbed the Heavenly Dao Laws. Around him, divine spirits of the Heavenly Dao were slain one after another. In the midst of this slaughter, Lin Ming’s scales were shattered and his entire body drenched in blood!

His flesh continued to regenerate and the power of the Heavenly Dao continued to weaken.

These ancient divine spirits had nearly all been killed off by Lin Ming!

Seeing this, the Empyreans and God Kings present were speechless.

They had also once experienced heavenly tribulation, but the way in which they crossed their heavenly tribulations was to wait for the heavenly tribulation to cast down its energy while they passively withstood it and underwent their baptism of heavenly thunder.

But Lin Ming had killed his way into the highest heavens, waging war against the Heavenly Dao!

Such a crazy procedure was nearly suicidal. But, Lin Ming relied on his inestimable war strength to succeed!

After he crushed apart all of the ancient divine spirits and the thunder of heavenly retribution, he absorbed the power of the Heavenly Dao.

Everyone knew that at this moment, Lin Ming had already perfectly crossed his heavenly tribulation.

This was the moment he truly became an Empyrean!

Chapter 2062 – Talks Collapse

“You want us, along with you, to withdraw from the war between humanity and the saints?”

Astral Vault frowned. He didn’t like being led along by others. This feeling was like he was simply following whatever decision Lin Ming chose, like he were taking orders. Wasn’t this just disgraceful?

“And Divine Dream?”

Soaring Feather’s eyes flashed to the side of Lin Ming.

At this time, Divine Dream was standing not too far away from Lin Ming. She remained silent, a vision of white, waiting for Lin Ming to answer for her.

“Senior Divine Dream will continue to remain involved in the war between humanity and the saints in order to make up for the difference in strength. The ones withdrawing will be you, me, and Astral Vault, three people altogether.”

Lin Ming confidently stated. The saints had far more Empyreans than humanity. Without Divine Dream here to keep the balance, humanity would be unable to engage the saints on the battlefield.

However, as these words fell into the ears of Soaring Feather and Astral Vault it actually grated upon their ears!

“What did you just say?” Astral Vault’s tone suddenly turned cold.

Originally, Astral Vault wasn’t particularly willing to accept Lin Ming’s proposition to withdraw from the war because he didn’t like being led along by a junior. But now that he heard the deal wouldn’t be equal, he was even angrier!

Could they really allow Divine Dream, a True Divinity powerhouse, to freely slaughter their saint Empyreans!?

Lin Ming said, “In this world there always exists the principle of equal exchange. In a war between races, however much war strength humanity takes out will also be the same that the saints take out. This is a fair concept.”

It would probably have been better if Lin Ming didn’t explain himself because once he did, Astral Vault began to emit a dense killing intent.

Astral Vault’s complexion was dark as he grimly said, “So you are saying that you alone are equal to me and Soaring Feather, so the three of us withdrawing together is an equal exchange?”

Lin Ming glanced at Astral Vault. “You can also understand the situation like this. In this deal, my withdrawal also means the withdrawal of Famine’s avatar. Moreover… just I alone may not necessarily make up for the loss of war strength created by the withdrawal of you and Soaring Feather from the war. At this moment I certainly cannot fight one against two, but with enough time, I believe that will be possible.”

Lin Ming provoked again and again. Astral Vault finally couldn’t withstand it; he was like a powder keg ready to explode. His face twisted into a fierce visage, his expression as if he were about to step forward and strangle Lin Ming.

“You are courting death!”

Astral Vault finally reached his limit. With a loud crackling sound his mortal body began to grow. From between his eyebrows, a mysterious nine dragon design appeared. With it, ancient runes appeared all over his body and his crystalline skin began to turn a faint blood red.

Astral Vault God King had already activated the strength of his bloodline and had begun the saint race’s body metamorphosis!

A great battle was ready to erupt at any moment!

Lin Ming’s eyes shined bright. In truth he had long expected that battle was inevitable!

Words could be a sharp weapon, but in negotiations between martial artists, strength was always what decided victory and defeat. If words weren’t enough to convince others then they could only overpower each other by force!

Lin Ming wanted to use the price of his withdrawal to exchange for the withdrawal of Soaring Feather and Astral Vault. If they didn’t fight then this deal would be impossible, because whether it was Soaring Feather or Astral Vault, their prideful hearts would not allow them to agree to such a deal.

And at this time, Soaring Feather also stepped forwards. Her white clothes fluttered about her and her long hair danced in the wind. Thick feathers fell around her; it was clear that she wouldn’t agree to these conditions.

She didn’t want to involve herself in this war between the saints and humanity to begin with. She understood that this war was in truth nothing more than the ambitions of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign.

But in the end, she was also a saint martial artist. She didn’t wish to see the saints be defeated by humanity.

She wouldn’t stand by idly as Divine Dream suppressed her people with a superiority in absolute strength.

As Soaring Feather displayed her force field, Divine Dream also drew out her sword. Beneath the starlight her appearance was sharp and fierce, just like a 10,000 year old shard of glacial ice.

A four person battle between three True Divinities and Lin Ming was about to explode at any moment!

But at this time, Lin Ming actually stopped Divine Dream. “Senior Divine Dream, allow me to handle this. These conditions were originally between me and two saint True Divinities. If you involve yourself in this then it will be impossible to convince them. Even if we win, it will only be the same as you and me as well as Astral Vault and Soaring Feather all withdrawing from the great calamity.”

Lin Ming calmly said. Astral Vault sneered, “So what if you join forces? Do you think that you two joining forces will be able to defeat us joining forces?”

“Whoever is weaker, we will only know upon fighting!” Lin Ming indifferently replied. He looked towards Astral Vault, his eyes blazing with fighting spirit. “I alone will fight you two. Of course, it will be one at a time. I won’t use Famine’s avatar as the price for fighting me one at a time!”

Famine’s avatar contained a dreadful war potential. In the hands of the Good Fortune Saint Son, it had a strength close or even near that of a middle True Divinity.

But in Lin Ming’s hands, he had already drawn out a massive amount of the avatar’s flesh and blood essence energy. The avatar’s strength had fallen precipitously but even so it could still be considered a formidable existence amongst lower True Divinities.

Although Famine’s avatar had weakened, Lin Ming was far stronger than the Good Fortune Saint Son. Whether it was in soul force or fusion compatibility, he was leagues ahead of the Good Fortune Saint Son.

In Lin Ming’s hands, lower True Divinity Famine would be able to display a war strength far higher than what the Good Fortune Saint Son displayed!

If Lin Ming were able to fight Astral Vault or Soaring Feather, then with Famine’s avatar added on he might be able to use its immense strength and massive size to fight one against two.

“Good! Very good! Then I will fight you! As long as you have strength that can match mine then I will withdraw from the war between humanity and the saints! Not just that, but I will also make a vow that in the future, if I attack any human influence that doesn’t have ill intent towards me or provokes me then my foundation will crack and my cultivation will be crippled!

“In addition, if I cannot defeat you then my two useless disciples will also withdraw from the war and return to honestly cultivate in earnest, never coming back out to disgrace themselves lest they are captured and used to threaten me again!”

Astral Vault God King was finally moved to true anger.

Lin Ming said, “Very well! A promise is a promise! Since that’s the case then I will promise that if you keep up your end of the bargain I will have the Legion of Famine withdraw too, no longer joining the great battle between humanity and the saints and only using them to protect my family.”

Since Lin Ming said he would withdraw from the war between humanity and the saints, he would do so thoroughly. In this regard, the Legion of Famine could also be considered a part of his strength, and he wouldn’t play word games concerning this.

As he spoke, Lin Ming turned to Soaring Feather. Soaring Feather remained silent; this was the same as agreeing to these conditions.

As for things like contracts, there was no need to sign them. Whether it was Lin Ming or these two True Divinities, they were all prideful individuals in their hearts and their word was more precious than stars; they wouldn’t renege on their promises.

Taking a step back, even if one side went back on their word then the other side could tear apart the agreement and rejoin the war; there wouldn’t be any losses.

Lin Ming silently drew out the Black Dragon Spear. His figure flashed and he had already crossed through the starry skies, flying thousands of miles away.

A True Divinity level battle was no trifling matter. He didn’t want the human juniors to be drawn in, otherwise the energy shockwaves would reduce them to ashes.

Divine Dream was easily able to create a force field a hundred miles wide around the battlefield to shelter the human martial artists.

Astral Vault narrowed his eyes. Looking at Lin Ming a hundred miles away, he quietly drew out a dark gold heavy sword. This heavy sword was a True Divinity spirit treasure!

Astral Vault was someone who had reached the limits of the body transformation system!

“Be careful, he isn’t simple!”

Soaring Feather said with a sound transmission.

“I know! Although I don’t want to acknowledge it, I can see from the phenomena that occurred during this boy’s Empyrean heavenly tribulation that he has some measure of skill. But, so what? If we don’t fight then we’ll never know who is weaker and who is stronger.

“At least, in the last tens of millions of years I have never truly engaged in brutal battle with someone! That woman Divine Dream simply never fought me at all. She only used those damned illusions to play with me, and now my belly’s long been full of fire!”

Astral Vault God King’s fighting intent was already boiling over. He lifted his golden heavy sword and slowly flew towards Lin Ming.

At this time, all the human martial artists looked upon Astral Vault God King’s back and held their breath. They had naturally clearly heard the negotiations between Lin Ming and the two saint True Divinities, and they knew that this battle concerned the future of the human race!

Chapter 2063 – Fighting Astral Vault

In a sea of stars, Lin Ming and Astral Vault stood a mere 10 miles apart from each other.

The starlight was misty and the killing intent was solemn. Because of the invisible energy it was as if this entire space had become denser.

Everyone was focused on this fight. Divine Dream had already released her force field to protect the human elites.

Lin Ming was the spiritual leader of humanity. Just after breaking into the Empyrean realm, he now welcomed a battle against a God King!

At this time, Astral Vault God King had his great arms crossed against his chest, his massive golden sword pressed against his body. This action wasn’t because he looked down on Lin Ming, but because this was the initial battle stance of the True Divinity cultivation method that Astral Vault God King trained in – the Astral Vault Saint Body. When his arms were crossed together, while it didn’t seem that his movements could be fast, the truth was that this stance unified the astral essence within his body and formed a type of potential.

As for Lin Ming, his battle stance was much more common. He flew high in the air, his hand extended diagonally, pointing the spear point down towards the void. His eyes were closed as he locked onto the surrounding space with his divine sense. To a martial artist on the level of Lin Ming, there was no difference between opening and closes their eyes. However, closing his eyes allowed him to better calm his mind, forming a more perfect union within the universe of his body and the universe of the world.

This was a stance of becoming one with the heavens and earth, also a peak manifestation of the Asura Laws and Holy Scripture Laws!

The world seemed to come to a standstill for this single frame of time.

Bang!

Astral Vault God King was the first to act. His movements were sudden and his speed immediately reached the peak!

Astral Vault God King was someone who had reached the peak in the body transformation system. In terms of Laws and force fields he might be at a disadvantage, but in terms of physique, he nearly reached the peak of the universe.

A powerful body brought him not just terrifying strength but also unparalleled speed!

No one could see just how Astral Vault God King had launched an attack when his arms were crossed against his chest. The Empyreans present also saw a flash as Astral Vault God King turned into a beam of light that hurtled forwards!

The potential that Astral Vault God King had gathered with the initial battle stance of the Astral Vault Saint Body was completely poured into this strike. And, what he attacked Lin Ming with was not the golden sword in his hand, but his fist!

In fact, for someone like Astral Vault God King, his mortal body could already compare favorably with a True Divinity spirit treasure. There was no difference in striking power between his fist and sword!

The void collapsed. Space storms swept out and rolled forwards. These storms gathered together, merging with Astral Vault God King’s potential. At this moment it was like Lin Ming wasn’t facing a fist, but a falling star!

Everyone held their breath. This was the disparity between a True Divinity and an Empyrean. Facing Astral Vault God King’s fist, nearly all of the Empyreans couldn’t help but think that his strike would be impossible to resist. This feeling was no different from a mortal facing landslides and tsunamis; it was impossible to struggle!

And at this time, Lin Ming also moved. Like a Divine Dragon awaked from its slumber, his eyes flashed open!

Lin Ming thrust out his spear, his strike colliding with Astral Vault God King’s fist.

In that terrifying impact, endless space and time storms shattered. All that was left over was the great momentum formed within Astral Vault God King’s fist, smashing into Lin Ming’s Black Dragon Spear.

A clash of fist and spear!

Chi –

A powerful pressure caused the Black Dragon Spear to distort; it bent like a drawn bow.

But at the same time, Astral Vault God King’s protective astral essence was also pierced through, leaving behind golden bloodstains on his hand.

These bloodstains burned in astral essence like a mass of divine flame, emitting an all-powerful light as if suns were exploding.

Bang!

The two separated. The Black Dragon Spear whipped back to its straight form. Astral Vault God King and Lin Ming flew back several hundred miles before pausing in the void!

In this one strike, no one had been able to harm the other. But, many human martial artists had cold beads of sweat dripping down their foreheads. This Astral Vault God King was simply too terrifying. Although they didn’t know what rank Lin Ming’s black spear was, they faintly knew that it must be a True Divinity spirit treasure of the highest caliber. But, Astral Vault God King had actually used his fist to contend with this spear; just how powerful was his mortal body!?

Although Astral Vault God King’s fist had been injured, what followed was…

Everyone looked towards Astral Vault God King and saw him wave his right hand. The bloodstains on his fist had solidified and the golden blood was being absorbed back through his skin. The wound on his hand regenerated at a visible speed and soon it disappeared altogether.

Seeing such a frightening bodily recovery ability, the human martial artists present all felt weak at heart. This person possessed a mortal body with a dreadful defensive capability that could resist a True Divinity spirit treasure and also had a formidable regeneration ability; this was simply the perfect defense! For the human Empyreans present, even if this type of enemy were to stand still and allow them to strike him, they still wouldn’t be able to do anything to him.

Was this Astral Vault God King’s strength?

Indeed, there were no weaklings amongst those that were able to become a True Divinity.

Lin Ming narrowed his eyes and looked at Astral Vault God King’s right hand. He said in a soft voice, “So that’s how it is. In terms of mortal body intensity, you already far surpass the rank of a lower True Divinity…”

Every True Divinity had their own special skills. For instance, the spiritas’ Great Brahmic God King excelled in the aspect of the mind and spiritual sea. Empyrean Divine Dream had balanced her development of the essence gathering system and soul forging system and was able to show countless variations of styles, making it impossible for Astral Vault God King to do anything. Soaring Feather God King was also similar to Divine Dream. She was skilled in spiritual sea and illusions, and even had high attainments of the body.

As for Astral Vault God King, he cultivated his body only. To become a True Divinity with his body alone, he used a single cultivation system to resist the other two. From this, it could be seen just how great Astral Vault God King’s mortal bodily strength was. This sort of person had peerless talent in the body transformation system and he was someone who displayed this talent to the extreme!

“My mortal body intensity actually goes beyond that of a True Divinity spirit treasure. But, True Divinity spirit treasures are simply objects. Destroying them, while not easy, can still be achieved. As for me, I am skilled in all sorts of cultivation methods and different skills. With my mortal body, once I pour in astral essence and revolve the Astral Vault Saint Body, the intensity of my body will increase by ten times! Your attacks are strong, but if you cannot break through my defenses then everything you try will be futile!”

Astral Vault God King sneered. Even the human True Divinity Divine Dream wasn’t able to harm him and had only trapped him in her illusions.

“I see…” Lin Ming didn’t have any expression. So what if Astral Vault’s mortal body was strong? His mortal body was also strong and it was also incredibly formidable. In particular, after opening another Dao Palace, what Lin Ming desired was to engage in frontal battle with a body transformation master!

At that moment, six Dao Palaces opened within Lin Ming’s body! Behind him, nine brilliant stars appeared. Endless starlight poured into Lin Ming, merging into those six Dao Palaces!

Even Lin Ming’s Black Dragon Spear started to shine with blinding starlight, scattering a luminous silvery brilliance all around. The Black Dragon Spear was a peak True Divinity spirit treasure, but if he couldn’t pour enough strength into it then its power would be greatly reduced.

Now, after pouring in starlight, the Black Dragon Spear seemed to come alive. Ringing cries of a dragon howled out from the spear, resounding through the void into the vastness of space.

Astral Vault God King narrowed his eyes. “You want to compete with me using body transformation? Haha, then bring it on!”

As Astral Vault God King spoke, he bellowed out and smashed his fist down at Lin Ming!

Lin Ming slashed out his spear in response!

Bang!

This was the second time the two clashed. Golden astral essence and silver starlight turned into a horrifying energy storm that swept outwards!

This time, the Black Dragon Spear didn’t bend. It seemed as if it truly had become an unrivalled Divine Dragon, capable of shattering stars!

Astral Vault God King was a body transformation God King and his speed neared the limits of possibility. But Lin Ming was actually no worse, completely able to keep up with Astral Vault God King’s speed!

The two of them engaged in a brutal melee of speed. However, their striking power wasn’t exchanged as a price for this speed. In fact, every time they clashed, their strikes would cause an energy storm to sweep outwards. Each time a storm was born it would persist for a long time. From far away, it seemed as if the entire distant skies were covered with giant gold and silver vortexes!

A nearly thousand mile large meteor was sucked into this gold and silver vortex and immediately burst into fragments before being reduced to dust.

This boggled the mind. How could the attacks of these two be so terrifying? If some of the weaker Empyreans present were drawn in, they wouldn’t even have their bones left!

With such high speed attacks and every attack having so much power behind it, just how could anyone fight them!?

“Hahaha! Great! Wonderful!” Astral Vault God King wildly roared. For him to laugh so recklessly in the midst of such fierce combat proved that he still had ample strength remaining.

Amid this great laughter, Astral Vault God King’s body emitted crackling from all over. His body started to grow and a faint red glow covered his body. The mystical symbol that appeared between his eyebrows before showed once again; he had completed his bloodline body metamorphosis!

Bang!

The void exploded. After transforming, Astral Vault God King was able to punch open a black hole in the void with his strikes. Lin Ming rapidly drew backwards!

Lin Ming grasped his spear, his eyes blazing brilliantly at Astral Vault God King!

This was the first time that Astral Vault God King had used the heavy sword in his hands!

This heavy sword seemed no different from a door and the blade was even longer than a man’s height. But, as Astral Vault God King held this heavy sword, this incredible length seemed just right.

This heavy sword was dark gold in color and didn’t seem different from an ordinary sword. However, Lin Ming discovered that when light flowed over this sword, it actually seemed to curve as if it were being drawn in by it.

Or, perhaps the space surrounding the sword itself was distorted.

“This sword’s name is – Dark Star!” Astral Vault God King had a proud smile as he saw Lin Ming looking at his sword.

“When I was stepping into True Divinity, I once went into seclusion on a dark star. Using the dark star’s terrifying gravity I tempered my own mortal body. After I truly broke into the realm of True Divinity, before I left, I used all of my strength to pull out a piece of matter from this dark star, a piece that was three inches wide, a foot long, and considerably thick. After I returned, I went into seclusion for another thousand years to use this dark star material to create a thin and long sword form. Using this sword form as the base, I cast an immense amount of golden gem demonic steel atop it, finally forging it into a heavy sword! I did not refine it nor did I carve any demonic runes on its surface. While this is a True Divinity spirit treasure it actually doesn’t have any supernatural abilities or array formations within. But, with its terrifying weight alone as well as its incredible hardness, it is the best weapon for me!”

As Astral Vault spoke, many people were bewildered.

Dark star? What was that?

Chapter 2065 – Reverse

Bang!

The sea of stars collided with the sword light. The sea of stars was torn apart and the sword light was also devoured. At this time, a black light shrouded over everything. The sword net that Astral Vault God King formed began to violently sway beneath this tremendous impact, and the attached sword potential also seemed as if it would soon fall apart!

In this instant, Astral Vault God King was submerged within the sea of stars.

In the endless starlight of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, Astral Vault God King felt like a mortal soaking in heavy mercury, his flesh and blood burning away!

His sword potential was diminished and his sense was also blocked by the starlight!

Divine sense was not Astral Vault God King’s specialty. But even without using his sense, he could still feel Lin Ming rapidly approaching, because he could feel a dense killing intent rushing towards him!

Astral Vault God King roared out loud. He stepped forward, his Dark Star Sword slashing down!

Kacha!

That sword seemed as if it could cut apart the sun and moon. By relying on the Dark Star Sword’s horrifying weight, Astral Vault God King was able to directly shear apart the sea of stars!

The Dark Star Sword collided with the black spear. The tremendous weight brought with it an overwhelming momentum. The endless power of the Nine Stars was swept up by this sword, exploding in the air!

Bang!

The black spear was smashed into a bent bow by the Dark Star Sword! The powerful backlash sent Lin Ming soaring backwards, and that overweeningly domineering astral essence struck his chest, causing him to spit out blood.

“Die!”

Astral Vault God King diabolically grinned. He knew that in that last attack his astral sword light has swept through Lin Ming!

Astral Vault God King was well aware of just how terrifying his astral sword light was; it wasn’t something that a human’s mortal body could withstand!

His body emitted explosive crackling sounds. He hurtled forwards, chasing after the victory!

Astral Vault God King slashed out his sword several times. Endless sword potential contracted, forming a special sword potential space that blocked all possible routes to evade in!

“This is bad!”

On the human side an Empyrean cried out in alarm. This sword potential space was like a giant meat grinder. Within it, sword potential cut throughout. Once one was sealed inside they would be torn into fragments by the sword potential.

Even if Lin Ming was incomparably fierce, this protective true essence would still be compressed by the sword potential and he would be restrained everywhere. If he wanted to break through the sword potential space he would need to spend a considerable amount of effort and time, but how would Astral Vault God King give him such a chance? In this sword potential space Astral Vault God King’s striking power reached the zenith of his capabilities; it was fundamentally impossible for Lin Ming to avoid Astral Vault God King’s attacks!

“Your blood shall be a sacrifice to my sword!”

Astral Vault God King’s voice was loud and clear, like billowing waves of heavenly thunder, vast and merciless. He blazed forwards, his sword slashing down and annihilating all Laws!

But in this moment, Astral Vault God King’s condensed sword potential space suddenly shook. Somehow, Lin Ming, who he had thought was trapped inside his sword potential space, suddenly used some unknown method to break free, gripping a black spear and sweeping out!

“What!?”

Astral Vault God King was simply unable to respond for a time. Although his sword potential space had trembled just then, it hadn’t shattered so how had Lin Ming managed to free himself?

In the fleeting instant there was no time for him to figure out what occurred. He lifted his Dark Star Sword and astral essence burnt all over his body as he lit up like a scorching sun!

Bang!

In that wild collision, a great black wheel appeared in Lin Ming’s hand. A great Asura demon that was several hundred feet tall appeared behind that wheel, slowly pushing it forwards.

The black wheel was like a grinding pan that swallowed everything before it; it constantly swallowed up the golden light emitted by Astral Vault God King!

This was Lin Ming’s Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel.

The all-annihilating Asura Heavenly Dao constantly grinded down the golden runes.

Astral Vault God King roared out loud and chopped down on the black wheel.

Kacha!

The Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel shivered, however, Astral Vault God King was also struck by a backlash of the Laws. His mortal body lit up with a macabre red color and his blood vitality started to tumble about!

Astral Vault God King drew back. Beneath the tremendous impact of the Laws, his mortal body was inevitably sent flying backwards. But at this time, another killing intent appeared behind him like gods and ghosts.

“What!?”

In that instant, Astral Vault God King felt a shiver run down his back, his entire body turning ice cold!

He had been struck backwards by Lin Ming’s attack, but Lin Ming must not have felt any better. His energy was too fierce, like a star exploding; it was impossible for Lin Ming to easily block it. However, he had attacked and in a short period of time it was impossible for him to launch another move!

And at this time, from behind Astral Vault God King, Lin Ming had already grasped his spear and was rushing straight towards him. Another Asura phantom appeared behind Lin Ming, another great wheel spinning between its arms.

The difference was that this wheel was not black, but purple.

The purple wheel seemed like a soul vortex, capable of twisting everything to pieces within.

“Avatar!?”

Astral Vault God King’s thoughts raced. He realized that in that great collision just then when he had smashed into the sea of stars, Lin Ming had used the moment that his sense had been restrained to scatter out his three avatars, and Astral Vault God King hadn’t discovered this!

Lin Ming was simply far too fast. Not to mention Astral Vault God King who was submerged in the sea of stars, even those peak Empyreans that watched from far away weren’t able to see a single one of Lin Ming’s avatars.

And what was most terrifying was that Lin Ming’s avatars originated from the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws. The strength of the three avatars was directly linked to the strength of his main body. The stronger Lin Ming was, the stronger his avatars became!

Astral Vault God King straightened himself with effort and suppressed the tumbling blood vitality within him himself. Then, he struggled to launch a counterattack.

His sword slashed atop the purple wheel. This purple wheel also came from the Asura Heavenly Dao – it was the Myriad Essence Reincarnation Wheel!

Bang!

A horrifying energy erupted. Astral Vault God King’s sword was unable to force back this giant wheel, but only managed to force back Lin Ming’s avatar.

The Asura phantom grabbed hold of the wheel and smashed into Astral Vault God King’s chest!

Puff!

Astral Vault God King spat out a mouthful of blood, his body hurtling away like a meteor!

Astral Vault God King, someone with incredible bodily strength and a mortal body that far surpassed a God Beast in intensity, had actually suffered heavy losses!

And in this moment, the fourth Lin Ming appeared!

“There’s more!?”

Astral Vault God King’s eyes turned blood red. Before this, Astral Vault God King had fought side-by-side with Soaring Feather God King and had engaged Empyrean Divine Dream in an exasperating guerilla war; he simply hadn’t had much communication with the saints. All he knew was that after Lin Ming returned, humanity had been able to win a number of victories. However, he hadn’t returned long enough to hear that Lin Ming had three avatars. And in truth, even if he knew this he still wouldn’t necessarily have been able to come up with a plan to deal with them. This was because while Astral Vault God King was formidable, his fighting technique was extremely singular in both offense and defensive, and lacked the variety needed.

But Lin Ming had learned a broad depth of skills and his fighting techniques were ever-changing, making it impossible to defend against!

Astral Vault God King was no longer able to tell whether this fourth Lin Ming was an avatar or his main body. All he felt was that this approaching enemy seemed to melt into the starry skies, his body reaching the peak of speed and his attack trajectory nearly impossible to predict.

This Lin Ming didn’t use a weapon, but simply used a palm to crash into Astral Vault God King!

At this moment, Astral Vault God King bit down on the tip of his tongue and forced out a drop of blood essence!

This drop of blood essence didn’t instantly burn like the blood essence of an ordinary martial artist. Rather, it turned into a golden fog of blood that covered Astral Vault God King’s body.

“Ahh!”

Astral Vault God King summoned his astral essence, attacking for the fourth time in a short period!

This sword would soon chop down on Lin Ming’s palm!

This sudden change bewildered everyone watching. They had all seen how terrifying this Dark Star Sword was. With the sword’s horrifying weight and Astral Vault God King’s all-out strength, even a royal God Beast would have all its joints and muscles broken apart, smashed into liquid mush!

A flesh and blood body was just unable to withstand this!

The moment that Lin Ming’s palm intersected with the heavy sword, a black and white yin yang diagram appeared above his palm. This yin yang diagram contained a vast aura, leaving one gasping for breath.

This was the manifestation of Lin Ming’s power of divinity and demons. Astral Vault God King’s sword crashed into the yin yang diagram.

Puff!

Astral Vault God King spat out a mouthful of blood; this was the backlash he suffered from summoning his astral essence while disregarding the roiling blood in his body.

This Lin Ming was once again sent soaring backwards from the tremendous impact force. But, before Astral Vault God King could catch his breath, his complexion changed once more!

He could feel a cunning and slippery strength pass through his Dark Star Sword, drilling into his flesh and blood!

“Mm!?”

Astral Vault God King froze. He discovered that in that attack just now, Lin Ming had poured a dark demonic strength into the yin yang diagram. That strength had broken into his body, carrying with it an all-destroying demonic force that actually began corroding away at his flesh and blood!

His mortal body began to lose its vitality!

This was the fusion of Lin Ming’s power of demons and the Holy Scripture Laws’ book of death. The power of death covered Astral Vault God King.

What was going on!?

Astral Vault God King was panic-stricken.

In normal times, he could transfer all the astral essence in his body and use absolute strength and his scorching sun-like blood energy to suppress this corrosive strength and burn it away.

However, because Astral Vault God King had repeatedly summoned his astral essence and even used a drop of blood essence to make four attacks, he had exceeded his limit. This caused Astral Vault God King to suffer a deficit in his blood vitality for a brief moment.

And this demonic strength took advantage of this chance to enter his body, directly attacking his life source!

Astral Vault God King’s mortal body defenses were incredibly formidable. But beneath this continuous attack of Laws, he was unable to use his powerful mortal body to resist it.

Once a deficit appeared in his blood vitality, then it wouldn’t be strong enough and every time he tried to restore some it would be corrupted and devoured by this demonic strength, becoming a part of that demonic strength. Like this, the demonic strength would continue to expand, forming a vicious cycle.

Astral Vault God King’s complexion changed!

He never imagined that this battle where he had the superiority would be reversed because of a moment of negligence!

Or it could even be said that this wasn’t a moment of negligence at all, but a trap intentionally laid down by Lin Ming!

Chapter 2069 – Lin Ming Battles Soaring Feather

“Famine!?”

Hearing this word, the Ancient Elysium Seal was stunned. Could this mysterious book originate from Famine, thus Famine’s name was placed atop it?

“This character ‘Famine’ seems to correspond to an abyssal word… a kind of foundational Demon Law…”

Lin Ming quietly said as he looked at the mysterious abyssal characters on the cover.

“What are the next characters?”

“Deep. Eon.”

Lin Ming pronounced. These words were based on Famine’s memories. In truth, there was no word that could be found in the human language which corresponded to these characters.

‘Deep’ and ‘Eon’, without a doubt, these were also characters that corresponded to foundational Demon Laws.

When these three characters joined together, Lin Ming formed a strange association.

“I feel that… Deep and Eon perhaps stand alongside Famine…”

“Mm?” The Ancient Elysium Seal’s thoughts stirred.

Lin Ming thought for a moment. “I have a feeling that each of the most foundational Demon Law marks in the abyssal language corresponds to a powerful abyssal demon. And Famine is only one of them! This cover has two other characters – Deep and Eon, and these should also correspond to extremely terrifying existences similar to Famine. They are abyssal ‘totems’, but I wonder just where these other two totems are. They might be hiding in the Dark Abyss or maybe they already died…”

As Lin Ming spoke, the Ancient Elysium Seal froze. Lin Ming’s speculations were not without reason, but if these speculations were true, this was disastrous news. Just Famine itself was already so terrifying! Moreover, Famine’s divine soul had been sealed by Empyrean Divine Seal 3.6 billion years ago, and that was the only reason Lin Ming had been able to use the Magic Cube to subdue it. Otherwise, if Lin Ming were to face Famine in its peak state, he would have died!

“Such powerful abyssal demons, how many could there be?”

The Ancient Elysium Seal’s voice was heavy.

“I don’t know, but there shouldn’t be many. At the very least, not more than can be counted on a hand, or maybe just a bit more than that. And this book cover only records three of them.”

Lin Ming continued sifting through the other characters on the cover. He believed that as he further unraveled Famine’s memories, he would eventually be able to open this mysterious ancient abyssal book and explore the secrets inside.

This was highly important to the future development of the 33 Heavens for all intelligent life. The abyssals were like fierce tigers perched just outside the 33 Heavens, making it so that Lin Ming found it difficult to feel at ease.

……

After this, Lin Ming entered seclusion. He explored Famine’s memories every day. Slowly, he was able to read more and more things.

But his time was too limited. As Lin Ming was in seclusion, although he managed to decipher some contents he still wasn’t able to open the mysterious ancient book.

This left Lin Ming puzzled. Just what was this ancient book? It didn’t seem like some cultivation method, so could it be only a book that recorded the history of the abyssals?

If a history book was written, it was written for the future generations to see. Was it necessary to use the most complex and difficult to understand abyssal characters to write it?

Perhaps only high-level abyssal figures would be able to read this type of Law writing.

Lin Ming had all sorts of doubts swirling in his heart. He faintly felt that there was some important secret recorded in this ancient demon book, and to himself, it was inestimably valuable.

…….

Time passed day after day. After the tenth day passed, the time approached for Lin Ming to face his second battle.

In this battle he would fight Soaring Feather God King!

This was a critical battle. Lin Ming had a premonition that Soaring Feather God King was far more powerful than Astral Vault God King. This battle would not be easy!

On the last day, Lin Ming no longer probed Famine’s soul. Rather, he adjusted his condition to its peak state.

On the day of the battle, the human martial artists within the Hidden Dragon Galaxy gathered outside the star territory where Lin Ming and Soaring Feather God King would fight.

Divine Dream, Emperor Shakya, Skyrend Godlord, everyone stood at the front of the battlefield, waiting to witness this historical moment.

Force fields were already arranged behind them. Besides Empyrean Divine Dream helping, the other Empyreans also contributed in forming great array formations.

These array formations were divided into dozens of different regions. The human fleets and the millions of human elites were dispersed throughout these regions. From there, they would be protected by the array formations and it would be much safer for them.

All of the human martial artists were seething with excitement.

To watch a battle between True Divinity level opponents was an incredible lucky chance. For those with amazing talent, they would be able to comprehend many things.

Humanity only had a single True Divinity in Divine Dream. Yet, within a short period of 10 days they were able to witness two continuous True Divinity level battles. This was simply unthinkable for the young elites.

At this time, hundreds of miles in front of Divine Dream, Lin Ming was floating high in the void. The Black Dragon Spear was carried on his back, its sharp point reflecting a cold starlight!

“Brother Lin…”

From afar, Xiao Moxian could see Lin Ming’s figure. Although they were separated by a great distance, Xiao Moxian could see every minute detail on Lin Ming’s face. This battle against Soaring Feather placed a tremendous pressure upon Xiao Moxian. Since she cared about Lin Ming it was naturally hard for her to feel at ease.

Nearby Xiao Moxian, Mu Qianyu, Qin Xingxuan, and the others also watched with tightened hearts.

As Lin Ming felt the gazes of these women on him, he turned and glanced at them, revealing a faint smile.

“I’m fine.”

Lin Ming lightly said. If he didn’t fight against Soaring Feather then no one knew what the result would be. However, no matter what happened, he would not perish here today. Even if he lost, it would only mean a greater burden for humanity and a delay on their plans to retake the Divine Realm.

Xiao Moxian nodded. Everyone waited.

Soaring Feather was a punctual individual. Just a brief moment before the agreed time, a thick pall of feathers rained down from the starry skies. These feathers fluttered in front of Lin Ming, reflecting the vast starlight, as beautiful as a dream…

Lin Ming quietly drew out the Black Dragon Spear, his gaze much sharper.

Soaring Feather had arrived. She came like a ghost deep in the night, emerging from thin air in front of Lin Ming. All the feathers gathered around her, condensing and forming rainbow-hued energies. Soaring Feather reached out a hand and stroked this energy before pulling out a long sword.

This sword was only two inches wide but the blade was extremely long, a full six feet in length. Moreover, the blade was supple and soft, as if it wasn’t solid at all. When Soaring Feather pulled out this sword, the blade didn’t swing, but writhed about like flowing blue water.

It was clear this sword represented the extremities of soft flexibility.

Lin Ming narrowed his eyes and looked at this sword. There was no True Divinity whose weapon could be underestimated. Astral Vault’s Dark Star Sword had also startled Lin Ming.

In particular, the saints guarded the Primeval Realm Ruins, so how could the saint True Divinities not have obtained some fierce spirit treasures from those ruins?

The atmosphere became stagnant. Several hundred miles away, the millions of human elites watched without uttering a single sound. As they gazed upon this True Divinity level battle that was about to begin, all of them held their breath.

This was a battle that concerned the destiny of humanity; it was natural for them to be nervous.

“In today’s battle, I will lay witness to your future. Come, make your move…” Soaring Feather lightly said.

Lin Ming didn’t delay. He focused his aura and the energy within his body began to surge. Behind Lin Ming, the faint phantom of a Supreme appeared. This Supreme stood tall and proud with no expression on its face. A vast and boundless aura gushed out from its entire being, as if it looked down upon the world with cold indifference.

After this Supreme phantom appeared, Lin Ming’s aura changed, becoming incredibly deep and gargantuan, as if his Laws stood evenly with the Heavenly Dao.

He stepped forwards, treading upon the stars. The Black Dragon Spear seemed to turn into a Divine Dragon as it howled outwards!

The distance between the two could be crossed in less than an instant. Lin Ming’s spear pierced through the impediment of space, seeming to instantly appear in front of Soaring Feather God King thrusting straight towards her head!

Feeling this cold spear light, Soaring Feather didn’t even bat an eyelash. She gently waved her sword, the wave-like sword rolling towards the Black Dragon Spear.

Compared to the overwhelmingly tyrannical Black Dragon Spear, Soaring Feather God King’s soft sword seemed far too weak and underwhelming. But when the spear and sword intersected, a brilliant rainbow-hued divine light erupted.

Bang!

Energy blasted outwards as a terrifying impact spread out from the divine light, as if countless golden swords were shooting out in all directions!

Space was recklessly torn apart like decrepit paintings beneath the aftershocks of energy. Divine light dazzled the world, blinding those who watched. And at this time, Lin Ming and Soaring Feather hurtled towards each other. Like this, the great True Divinity level battle had begun!

Chapter 2070 – To Wear Away Rock With Water

Waves of energy soared into the air, as if the galaxy were collapsing. Lin Ming grasped the Black Dragon Spear, a profile of epic daring!

Lin Ming had poured a terrifying amount of his bodily strength into every spear strike. With loud crackling noises, Lin Ming began to grow. Black scales and bone armor started covering his body.

He had activated the Asura blood.

After Lin Ming broke into the Empyrean realm, galvanizing the power of the Asura blood wouldn’t create too much of a burden on his body. In the past he only used the power of the Asura blood when he was going all-out.

Hu - !

Lin Ming waved his spear, the sight like a heaven-supporting pillar falling down. This wild strength was accompanied by endless black thunder, carrying with it starlight of the highest heavens and the momentum of the strike seeming as if it could cleave apart rivers of stars!

Soaring Feather wasn’t flustered. She released the sword in her hands and welcomed Lin Ming’s strike!

The Black Dragon Spear against the soft sword!

No matter who was watching, this seemed like a completely disproportionate collision!

Due to the disadvantage of her weapon, everyone thought that Soaring Feather God King would avoid Lin Ming’s strike. However, she didn’t do so!

“Be careful of a spiritual attack!”

Someone shouted out from the human forces.

This was also what many other human martial artists were thinking. No one believed that Soaring Feather’s soft sword would be able to occupy any advantage when colliding with the Black Dragon Spear.

Everyone knew that Soaring Feather God King was extremely strong. However, in their thoughts, Soaring Feather was someone who cultivated essence and divine. From the different forms of combat she had revealed and her form of weapon, they all assumed that she had extremely high attainments in the aspect of souls, illusions, and mental strength. However, when it came to body transformation, she was simply a slender and delicate woman, and people didn’t believe that she excelled much in this domain. At the very least, she wouldn’t be able to compare with Lin Ming.

In particular, the current Lin Ming had activated the Asura blood and was utilizing the strength of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace!

But even so, Soaring Feather God King was meeting Lin Ming head-on. The only possible explanation for this was that there were profound and complex principles hidden within Soaring Feather God King’s attack!

Even Lin Ming also instantly made defense preparations for his spiritual sea. He wouldn’t allow his enemy any openings!

However, when the soft sword clashed with the Black Dragon Spear, Lin Ming’s complexion changed!

Soaring Feather simply didn’t attach any soul attack to her sword. Rather, she used absolute strength and skill to frontally collide with him!

If the strength of the Black Dragon Spear was a meteor that crashed into the earth, capable of easily annihilating mountains and puncturing through the world, then the strength of Soaring Feather’s soft sword was like a profoundly deep sea, capable of unparalleled accommodation of force. Even if a meteor were to strike the sea, although it would create wild explosions and summon great tsunamis, it would still be extremely difficult to truly blow up a sea. As long as the explosion of the meteor finished then the sea waves would draw back and the sea would be the same as before.

Now, Soaring Feather God King’s astral essence gave Lin Ming such a feeling!

The moment the Black Dragon Spear clashed with the soft sword, Soaring Feather’s astral essence was shaken away by Lin Ming’s violent and limitless strength. The Black Dragon Spear continued driving forwards, smashing into the soft sword until it curved. However, the soft sword gave but did not break, and Soaring Feather was also like a piece of cotton in the wind, blown away by the fierce energy storm of the Black Dragon Spear!

However, the moment Lin Ming’s strength pushed in and was about to strike Soaring Feather, her astral essence returned. Not only did it return, but it carried with it a portion of Lin Ming’s strength and instantly submerged the power of divinity carried by the Black Dragon Spear. This was just like the sea water submerging the meteor that crashed into the sea.

Bang!

A brutal and crazy eruption exploded outwards. Lin Ming’s strength rapidly shattered away, creating a dazzling brilliance. However Soaring Feather wasn’t wounded at all. Instead, the moment Lin Ming’s strength scattered away, Soaring Feather’s six foot long soft sword seemed to turn into a spirit snake that slithered up the Black Dragon Spear and cut towards Lin Ming’s hand!

Lin Ming’s palm was as hard as divine iron. But, he didn’t doubt that as long as he was cut by this sword, then perhaps even his hand would be severed!

Soaring Feather’s strength contained a sort of opportunistic and unyielding strength, the kind of Laws that allowed water to wear away rock!

Without hesitation, Lin Ming held the spear in his right hand and used his left to smash at the soft sword that was crawling up the Black Dragon Spear.

Kacha!

Lin Ming’s fist smashed into the ridge of the soft sword; this was where a sword was most fragile and where it had the least striking power. But even so, the ridge of Soaring Feather’s soft sword couldn’t be underestimated.

The moment Lin Ming’s fist struck the sword ridge, trillions of motes of the power of divinity rushed in before exploding with the power of vibration.

Such powerful vibrations could turn any True Divinity spirit treasure that didn’t have energy poured into it into powder; it directly blasted away Soaring Feather’s six foot long soft sword.

Lin Ming pulled his spear and flew backwards. His left fist was covered in blood.

The vibration just now was called Flow like Silk. It was a technique that Lin Ming had learned at the start of his road of martial arts, from a Divine Realm body transformation cultivation method.

In the past, Lin Ming’s Body Tearing Bone Shattering Fist had similar effects from different methods with that strike just then.

The Great Dao was limitless. The Vibration Laws might not be some profound Law, but if used correctly, it could still play a role even in a True Divinity level battle.

When a person had a blood-sucking leech attached to their leg, it was difficult to pull off. Even after ripping off the leech its fangs would still be sucking blood. But, using vibration to free it was easier. With enough correct slaps on the leg the leech would fall off.

In that moment, Lin Ming had used the powerful force of vibrations to push off the soft sword that had wrapped around his Black Dragon Spear. Otherwise he would have been forced to abandon his spear.

Lin Ming and Soaring Feather drew back from each other, thousands of feet away.

Soaring Feather held her soft sword, her expression indifferent. The sword still swung about like a reed in a river, not suffering any stress at all. But, the combat strength it could display left one frightened.

Depending on how Soaring Feather used her astral essence, it could become soft, it could become sharp, it could become hard, all sorts of changes were possible with just a thought.

Seeing this, the human martial artists were worried.

This battle was too important and the strength Soaring Feather showed so far was too great. She hadn’t even used her divine feather force field nor had she revealed her soul force combat methods.

If Soaring Feather used all of her strength to fight, then her combat methods would change without end, making it nearly impossible to guard against!

In this sort of situation it was unknown whether or not Lin Ming could win!

Soaring Feather was clearly much more formidable than Astral Vault.

Ten days ago when Lin Ming defeated Astral Vault, it hadn’t been a suspenseful victory. However, when considering it carefully, it was related to Lin Ming’s planning and Astral Vault’s mistakes.

This was because Astral Vault had lacked information on his opponent before the battle began. In the most crucial moment, Astral Vault hadn’t recognized Lin Ming’s avatar and had used the majority of his strength to deal with Lin Ming’s Essence Spirit Embryo Stone.

A single wrong chess move and the entire game falls apart. Lin Ming had seized this chance to push forwards. He gathered all his avatars and struck again and again, leaving Astral Vault God King no chance to catch his breath. Finally, the result of all these attacks was that Astral Vault God King had momentarily used up the power of his blood energy and he was eventually defeated because of this.

But Soaring Feather clearly wouldn’t make such a mistake.

She was a calm and intelligent fighter. If Lin Ming wanted to defeat her he would have to rely on absolute strength to directly suppress her!

How could he accomplish this?

“Lin Ming…”

Xiao Moxian looked towards Lin Ming and bit her lips.

Not too far away, Empyrean Vast Universe clenched his fists, worried.

Hundreds of miles away, everyone’s eyes were fixed upon a single figure.

At this time, in the starry skies, Lin Ming took a deep breath. He slowly undid the body transformation of the Asura blood. The nine stars behind him also dimmed a great deal.

Seeing this, the audience was shocked.

After undergoing body metamorphosis Lin Ming still wasn’t able to obtain the advantage. Then, wouldn’t his situation be much worse after undoing his body metamorphosis?

“What is Lin Ming doing?”

“I have no idea!”

No one thought that Lin Ming would give up; he wasn’t such a person. Then, this could only mean that he had some other plan.

Soaring Feather looked at Lin Ming, a smile on the corners of her lips. “Saving your strength?”

It was hard to tell whether Soaring Feather’s words were praising or mocking.

Lin Ming indifferently said, “You are borrowing strength to fight strength. I naturally wouldn’t be so idiotic as to give you more strength to borrow. You truly have extraordinary achievements in the body transformation technique and have surpassed my expectations. But, there is something that I am sure of. In truth, your body transformation technique walks the road of Law. In terms of absolute cultivation of body transformation, you are inferior to Astral Vault God King!”

The saint race’s body transformation was also one of the 33 Heavenly Daos. However, the change of Laws involved in it were far inferior to humanity’s Nine Divine Shifts. Thus, in terms of Laws, humanity always felt superior and believed that the saints were nothing but brutish and simple-minded fellows whose only advantage was well developed bodies.

As for the saints, they took pride in their body transformation technique that allowed them to engage others in honest and straightforward combat, frontally colliding with each other. At the same time, the saints also felt that human martial artists only had flowery fists and fancy footwork, all show and no true strength, a bunch of little women in disguise.

But today, beneath Soaring Feather’s hands, the saint race’s body transformation technique was clearly not such an example.

She had introduced far more variation and Laws into the saint race’s body transformation technique, forging her own road.

To wear away rock with water, to take all opportune chances with the least effort, these things didn’t seem to involve the most profound of Laws, but if utilized in a True Divinity level fight by a True Divinity to a high degree, then everything became different.

This was like using simple lever principles to tilt a planet.

Lin Ming was surprised, but he still maintained his original judgment. In the end, Soaring Feather God King was still a delicate woman, and it was exactly because she was weak in the aspect of body transformation that she had to walk the road of wearing away rock with water, to borrow strength to fight strength. If she had absolute strength herself, why would she need to borrow strength from others?

Facing such a Soaring Feather, Lin Ming no longer went all-out with his strength. Rather, he chose to use skill to win. If he wanted to use strength alone to win, he could only rely on an overwhelmingly massive eruption to do so. But if he used a smaller portion of his strength then he could better control his abilities and reach the peak of his skill.

At this time, three avatars appeared behind Lin Ming.

These avatars each held spears. The spears were all peak Empyrean spirit treasures obtained from saint Empyreans that Lin Ming had killed.

Since Soaring Feather already knew of the existences of these three avatars, it was impossible to hide them. If using these avatars in a sneak attack was meaningless, then he might as well openly and honestly take them out.

These three avatars and Lin Ming’s main body spread out around Soaring Feather God King.

Soaring Feather God King’s slender eyes suddenly narrowed.

Chapter 2073 – Suppressing a God King

“This… how can anyone still defend against this!?”

Some human Empyreans cried out in pure shock. After Soaring Feather became the incarnation of a seven-colored divine luan, not only did she unveil her horrifying body transformation technique but her strikes even contained divine soul attacks!

This was the last level of the Feather Conversion Art and Soaring Feather’s ultimate fighting method!

And to any enemy, this sort of fighting ability was undoubtedly a nightmare! After Soaring Feather underwent her transformation there were already few people capable of resisting her tremendous strength. Even if they managed to do it, they still had to endure the soul energy impact of the Feather Conversion Art, and there simply weren’t many martial artists that could withstand this.

Divine Dream’s guess was correct. The moment that Soaring Feather God King’s claws struck Lin Ming’s arms, he felt an incomparably insidious energy hurtle towards his spiritual sea.

Even for Lin Ming, his face paled at this moment. An incredibly overbearing strength pierced into his spiritual sea, turning into a giant feather that thrust down like a spear.

As long as this spear struck, Lin Ming’s spiritual sea would absolutely be injured!

Even if there weren’t any lingering side effects left over, this would be the same as losing this battle.

In an instant, Lin Ming’s soul form appeared within his spiritual sea.

“Famine’s soul!”

He bellowed out loud. Behind him, the titanic soul of Famine that was submerged in his spiritual sea was stirred into a frenzy. Countless tentacles stretched out, rolling out like an army of blood dragons.

Rumble rumble rumble!

The blood dragon tentacles violently collided with Soaring Feather God King’s heaven-shattering feathers countless times. Every explosion caused Lin Ming to turn that much paler.

Lin Ming knew that if he used the Magic Cube it would be easy to defend his spiritual sea. But, he didn’t want to let Soaring Feather know about the Magic Cube; the time was not yet ripe to reveal such a secret.

Time and time again, powerful feathers were struck into powder.

Finally, the moment the feathers were about to touch Lin Ming’s spiritual sea, ten blood dragons rushed out together, shredding apart the final feathers!

Peng!

The feathers turned into countless motes of light; Lin Ming’s spiritual sea was unscathed.

However, with Lin Ming’s current strength he was unable to completely control Famine’s soul. To forcibly call upon the power of Famine’s soul just now consumed a great deal of Lin Ming’s strength.

The battle over Lin Ming’s spiritual sea had occurred in just a moment. When he opened his eyes Soaring Feather had flown right in front of him, her claws grasping down!

This strike came towards Lin Ming’s head; it was nearly impossible to avoid!

And Lin Ming had already let go of his Black Dragon Spear. If he were to use his flesh and blood to resist this strike, he would need to discard an arm to do so, and if he did that then this battle would be as good as settled.

In this critical moment, the black-clothed Lin Ming, purple-clothed Lin Ming, and blue-clothed Lin Ming rushed towards Soaring Feather God King from three different directions. One of them chopped down at her claws and the other two thrust their spears towards her eyes!

Lin Ming’s three avatars all possessed the ability of independent thought. Even though they were controlled by Lin Ming they could move on their own. In this moment, the avatars came to rescue him, saving him from this crisis. Soaring Feather God King’s figure flickered and her wings swept out, sweeping the three avatars away. As for Lin Ming’s true self, he also took this chance to extricate himself from Soaring Feather God King’s attack.

Bzz!

The Black Dragon Spear emitted an excited cry as it returned to Lin Ming’s hand.

Lin Ming smashed the spear downwards. In this strike, Lin Ming had used his complete strength, even opening the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace to the limit and pouring the power of divinity and demons into the Black Dragon Spear without reserve. For a time, black and white yin yang colors swirled on the surface of the Black Dragon Spear.

The spear broke through the endless skies, unstoppable! The power of divinity and demons kindled, burning like sacred flames and scorching down the vastness of space!

Soaring Feather God King emitted a keening cry. She had just repelled Lin Ming’s avatars with her wings so she was only able to resist Lin Ming’s strike with her claws.

Kacha!

In that moment, all sound was swallowed. A blinding divine light swept through the void. For the surrounding several hundred miles, the human martial artists bore the brunt of the aftermath as they were covered by this divine light. Everyone watched as a large asteroid started to melt away and disintegrate beneath the illumination of this divine light!

“Be careful!”

Many human martial artists cried out in alarm, all of them summoning their protective true essence to resist the energy that snuck through the array formations.

“How horrifying. Even with protective shields prepared ahead of time, so much energy leaked through that we have to use all our energy to resist it.”

A young Holy Lord level elite said, his complexion changing. Facing such a dreadful strength, even if an Empyrean were to stand exposed in space it was likely they would be severely wounded.

Everyone instinctively wanted to retreat further away. But at this time, Divine Dream moved. She formed a seven-colored divine light that fused into the protective array, stabilizing it so that no energy leaked through anymore.

Seeing this, everyone let out a sigh of relief. As they looked at Divine Dream, awe was in their eyes.

This massive asteroid had disintegrated beneath the impact of energy yet Divine Dream was able to easily resist it. This showed just how terrifying True Divinity level masters were.

At this time, the explosive divine light had dissipated. Everyone looked towards the center of the battlefield and saw that Soaring Feather God King’s two claws were stained with blood and the feathers on her stomach were also drenched red. From a single glance, one could see that this blood didn’t originate from Lin Ming because its color was strange and although it was red, it shined with a rainbow luster.

Soaring Feather was injured, moreover her injuries were heavy!

As for Lin Ming, his wounds were even greater. His arm was twisted at a strange angle; it was clear he had broken his bones.

His other arm was also covered in blood. It was obvious that he took heavy losses in that collision just now.

Not just that, but his complexion was deathly pale, as if in that explosion just now the two of them had also undergone a contest of soul force!

Looking at Lin Ming’s bloodstained body, Xiao Moxian trembled. Mu Qianyu, Qin Xingxuan, Lin Xiaoge, and the others were also shaking with worry.

For the fight to reach this point, it was simply too brutal.

“Father…”

Lin Huang looked at Lin Ming from afar, his thoughts complex.

To him, Lin Ming would forever be the one he worshipped and the goal he aimed for in his heart. Lin Ming’s back had always been driving Lin Huang forwards.

Compared to the nervous human side, Soaring Feather was staring at Lin Ming, her complexion dignified. She had used the final level of the Feather Conversion Art, revealed her true form, combined her soul attack and material attack, and even utilized the saint race’s body transformation technique to the limit. It could be said that she had gone all out this battle.

Although she had suppressed Lin Ming, she actually didn’t manage to defeat him!

And at this time, something occurred that caused Soaring Feather’s eyes to leap up.

Lin Ming stretched out his left hand. He held onto his fractured and twisted right arm, clenched his teeth, and pulled.

Kacha!

With a cracking sound the broken bones joined back together. Lin Ming slowly moved his right hand. Although his arm trembled, it was clear that there was no problem with his joints.

By activating the Natal Life Dao Palace of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, a martial artist could obtain an unequalled restorative ability. They could regenerate severed arms and even rejoin their body if they were cut in half.

Lin Ming held his spear in his left hand. He didn’t move his right hand, but instead wrapped it with energy. It started to regenerate at a speed visible to the naked eye.

Lin Ming’s eyes were profound. His three avatars gathered around him, clearly planning to delay for time.

If he consumed a massive amount of blood vitality on his arm, he could definitely repair it in 20 some breaths of time. But during this time, he would need his avatars to divert his opponent.

Soaring Feather’s eyes were cold. She rushed forwards!

She used her extreme speed once more. She clearly didn’t plan on giving Lin Ming time to heal, or, perhaps it could be said she wanted to test Lin Ming’s limits.

Hu - !

Hu - !

Strong gales stirred up. Soaring Feather and the four Lin Mings moved together.

Energy wildly blazed outwards, forming a horrifying storm in the cosmos. The speed of the five figures neared the pinnacle, and even Empyreans found it difficult to clearly see what was occurring. As for the common martial artists, all they saw were series of afterimages!

Although they couldn’t clearly see the movements, the energy shockwaves that were capable of disintegrating asteroids reminded everyone just how terrifying this battle was!

If it wasn’t for the force field released by Divine Dream, then besides the several peak Empyreans there would be no one capable of standing still. Everyone below the Empyrean realm would also be instantly turned to ash. This was the disparity of absolute strength!

Chi!

Lin Ming gripped his spear in his left hand, drawing a crescent moon through the air as he aimed at Soaring Feather’s abdomen. Soaring Feather blocked with her right wing and grasped out a claw at Lin Ming. However, at this time, Lin Ming’s avatars attacked from behind Soaring Feather, forcing her to draw back her attack. Lin Ming’s body flickered. Space shrank beneath his feet and he instantly appeared thousands of feet away.

“You fight just to delay for time? Your arm should already be fine by now!”

Soaring Feather’s face was cold and decisive. Lin Ming’s avatars were simply too annoying. Although their individual strength was less than the main body, they still possessed formidable defensive powers. And with each one coordinating with the others, it was hard to damage them.

“I just recovered!” Lin Ming suddenly shouted. He stretched out his right hand and the Black Dragon Spear landed in its grasp.

“You dare to engage me in frontal battle!?”

Soaring Feather asked, her aura erupting.

“As you wish!”

Lin Ming roared into the heavens. He grabbed his spear with both hands and hurtled forwards once more. A massive Asura phantom appeared behind him. At this time, Lin Ming was covered in blood, small and large wounds crisscrossing his entire body. He was like a blood red meteor as he impacted towards Soaring Feather God King.

Bang!

An explosion no smaller than the previous one blew out once more. Even from trillions of miles away, one could see a blazing light ignite in the distant skies.

The protective barriers that were several hundred miles away began to violently shake. Besides Divine Dream, everyone else, including Emperor Shakya, Dark Demon Monarch, and the others, all had changed complexions. Just how horrifying was this battle?

In this collision, Lin Ming’s arm didn’t break. By using the power of vibration he dispersed a great deal of the impact force. Taking advantage of this chance, Lin Ming flipped around. He actually… rode on top of Soaring Feather’s back!

This was a weakness of Soaring Feather God King’s defenses that he had long since been eyeing! With Soaring Feather God King having become the incarnation of a divine bird, he could avoid many of her attacks by riding on her back.

Chapter 2078 – Retaking the Divine Realm

In these past years, Lin Ming felt a great pressure on his shoulders and he had experienced far too many tribulations. After arriving at an absolutely safe place like Tragic Death Valley, he immediately relaxed.

This was an array formation that the Asura Road Master had personally laid down in the past. Even someone on the level of Soaring Feather God King would have a hard time freely entering and leaving as they pleased.

And, no one could expect that he would hide here.

While inside he was absolutely safe.

Lin Ming began his seclusion.

There were too many matters he had to complete; just absorbing the memories in Famine’s soul would take an extremely long time.

Lin Ming needed to go to the Dark Abyss, and without Famine’s memories as a guide, then a single human entering was no different from a sheep wandering into a wolf den.

He had to protect himself, and the greatest measure with which to do so was Famine.

The years passed without sense of time.

Lin Ming fell into an absorbed state. He didn’t know how much time passed, only that his hair constantly grew longer, brushing against the ground and still growing.

Dust rose and fell on his body. At certain intervals, waves of demonic energy would rise up and the dust on Lin Ming would fly away. However, he steadfastly sat there like a rock.

When Lin Ming first entered the Asura Road he was already just barely able to deal with the demonic energy tides in Tragic Death Valley. Now, he was like a reef in front of a breeze, simply not feeling it at all.

But Lin Ming’s clothes slowly tore apart. As several demonic energy tides rose, they wore away at his clothes. Soon, he became utterly naked.

Every now and then his exposed skin would glow red; he was absorbing Famine’s essence!

To Lin Ming, Famine’s avatar was powerful, but it was only slightly more powerful than himself. With sufficient time Lin Ming would surpass Famine’s avatar in strength, and by that time the avatar would be weak.

Thus, the most effective method for Lin Ming to use the avatar of Famine was to absorb its essence to further develop himself.

As time passed, Lin Ming absorbed more and more of Famine’s energy into his body. Not only did he absorb a massive amount of pure demon energy, but he also absorbed the Laws within it.

Faintly, Lin Ming seemed to arrive in a chaotic space. Deep within this chaotic space, a massive black hole of space-time slowly revolved. As energy neared this black hole it would be sucked in.

Seeing this, Lin Ming froze. This was…

Laws of Swallowing!?

Lin Ming sucked in a deep breath. Famine’s flesh and blood and even its soul contained the secrets to the Laws of Swallowing. After absorbing Famine’s soul and now absorbing Famine’s flesh and blood, all of Famine’s essence was being transferred to his body.

Then…

Perhaps he could also peek into the deepest secrets of the Laws of Swallowing and begin plundering talent like Famine could.

Of course, it was impossible for Lin Ming to do this to a such a heaven-defying degree like Famine could. But, it would be good enough if he could inherit a tiny portion of the talent in the Laws of Swallowing.

Disregarding everything else, just his speed in absorbing world energy in the future would be incomparable to the present.

To swallow. In Lin Ming’s mind, these weren’t the methods of the enemy, but a new shortcut that would allow him to grow faster!

With these intentions in mind, Lin Ming no longer hesitated. He composed his mind and poured all of his mental strength into Famine’s flesh and blood, greedily absorbing nutrition from its essence.

Unknowingly and unwittingly, 100 years passed. Outside this was only ten years.

In these ten years, Lin Ming’s two children were born. One was a boy and one was a girl. Mu Qianyu gave birth to a boy named Lin Yu, and Qin Xingxuan gave birth to a girl named Lin Xuan.

The names of these two children came from both their mother and father.

Lin Yu and Lin Xuan’s talents were slightly worse than Lin Huang’s. But, they had inherited Lin Ming’s Asura bloodline, and if they cultivated in the future they were sure to become extraordinary individuals.

Another ten years passed.

In the Divine Realm, the war between humanity and the saints raged like a blazing conflagration. Because Soaring Feather and Astral Vault withdrew from the war, humanity’s ability to face their opponents on the battlefield was no less than the saints’. Many territories in the Divine Realm had already been reclaimed by humanity.

As the human refugees scattered throughout the Divine Realm saw the return of their fellow comrades, all of them sobbed in joy.

No one could understand what they felt after waiting for this moment for more than 6000 years.

They were happy, so happy that even if they died they could die in peace…

In terms of the great war between humanity and the saints, a mere 20 years of fighting was in truth only a short period of time. It would take much longer to reclaim the Divine Realm.

After all, the Divine Realm itself had 3000 great worlds.

The battles in the wild universe alone had continued for several hundred years.

Now, the great effort to retake the Divine Realm would require at least several hundred years before they could truly reclaim their land.

But, during the third decade of the effort to retake the Divine Realm, the saint armies began to retreat.

They relinquished Divine Realm great worlds they had seized on their own initiative, riding on spirit ships to flee back to Saint Convocation Heaven.

Soldiers receded like a falling tide. With the saints retreating, the human armies were able to push in without facing any obstacles.

The human warriors were incomparably excited. However, the several human Empyreans leading the war were startled; they hadn’t expected such a result to occur.

“The saints are retreating. What should we do?”

Emperor Shakya asked Divine Dream. He was asking whether or not they should chase down the armies of the saints.

Without a doubt, the saints were retreating because the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was in seclusion. Because the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign couldn’t be interrupted midway, the saints had decided to return to Saint Convocation Heaven where they could regroup and maintain their strength.

With the death of the Good Fortune Saint Son, the withdrawal of Soaring Feather God King, Astral Vault God King, as well as their subordinates such as Blue Lotus and the others, that meant the saints had no highest leader to turn to. To return to Saint Convocation Heaven was an intelligent move in these circumstances.

When humanity took back the Divine Realm, it hadn’t been easy for them even though this was territory they were profoundly aware of. If they were to march into Saint Convocation Heaven and face the unknown breadth of the saint armies from the seven Heavens of the saints, then this would be far too risky a move.

It was unwise to pursue a hard-pressed enemy too far, much less an army that was deep in enemy territory.

However, Divine Dream still issued the order to give pursuit. This was because with her presence, she could maintain the integrity of the human fleets.

Divine Dream knew that it was impossible for humanity to seize the Saint Convocation Heaven no matter how much they chased after their enemies. She knew that besides annihilating some of the saints’ overall war strength, there weren’t any advantages to be had. But, she would still continue the pursuit.

Even if this was only a tribute to the countless martyrs who had died bravely in battle in the wild universe!

The blood of humanity couldn’t be bled in vain. She needed to give those heroic martyrs an answer to their deeds!

This battle continued for another 30 years.

Humanity’s war in the Saint Convocation Heaven was even more difficult.

Humanity had yet to recover their energy. In terms of Empyrean level characters, they only had a bit more than 100 and only 2000 some Great World Kings.

Although Divine Dream was powerful, she was only a single person. This would be the same if the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign went to the wild universe to fight. The human Empyreans would immediately hide away, making it so that the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign wouldn’t be able to kill many of them.

And now, with Divine Dream battling in the Saint Convocation Heaven, the saint Empyreans naturally wouldn’t line up so that Divine Dream could slaughter them.

Thus, Divine Dream’s greatest function was to protect the main force of humanity and threaten. With Divine Dream, the human armies did not fear frontally facing the saints, nor did they fear being surrounded. However Divine Dream couldn’t replace the human armies in fighting. To annihilate the armies of the saints, what humanity truly relied on were their Empyreans, World Kings, and Holy Lords.

The size of the human armies was far too small. It was simply impossible for them to wage war throughout the seven Heavens of the saint race.

Soon, the fight reached an impasse.

The saints actively avoided battle. In this situation, humanity wasn’t able to achieve much.

To further expand their war victories, they could only destroy planets of saints and wipe out massive amounts of low level saint martial artists. But if they did this then they would be no different from the saints, and perhaps might even be worse.

Thus, on the fiftieth year, the human armies returned to the Divine Realm.

The moment that the armies withdrew, the Divine Realm wildly cheered in revelry and celebration!

Countless people cried out hot tears. They had paid a deep price for over 6000 years, putting in generations of effort, and now they finally had their homeland back!

They had preserved their dignity, had preserved the bravery of their bloodline.

Although this was only temporary, they had all firmed their resolve. No matter how the saints counterattacked in the future, they would continue fighting on to the last person.

With humanity’s victory, two names shined ever brighter in human history.

These two names were – Human Sovereign Lin Ming and Heavenly Empress Divine Dream.

No one referred to Divine Dream as Empyrean Divine Dream anymore, but started to call her the Heavenly Empress.

This corresponded to Lin Ming. Within the heavens and earth, Lin Ming was the Human Sovereign and Divine Dream was the Heavenly Empress.

One Sovereign one Empress, these were similar to the names of the spiritas’ Soul Emperor and Soul Empress.

‘Emperor’, ‘Sovereign’, ‘Empress’, these were some of the highest titles give to men and women in humanity; they were unrelated to whether or not one was married.

While the Divine Realm was being rebuilt, Lin Ming was still deep in seclusion. 70 years had passed outside, meaning 700 years within Tragic Death Valley.

During these 700 years Lin Ming had already started the seventh cycle of the Grand Reincarnation Art.

The energy needed to recultivate from the start of a reincarnation came from the avatar of Famine. And during the process of fusing with this energy, Lin Ming started to slowly touch upon Famine’s Laws of Swallowing. Bit by bit he imprinted Famine’s talent to swallow into himself.

By now, Lin Ming was completely able to control the power of demons. If he camouflaged himself as an abyssal then no one would suspect him, and they would even think he was a high-level existence amongst abyssals.

This paved the way for Lin Ming to enter the Dark Abyss. Otherwise, a human entering the abyss was no different from suicide.

After 700 years of cultivation, Lin Ming’s foundation had consolidated. This gave him the ambition to attack the middle Empyrean realm while in Tragic Death Valley.

Another 500 years passed. Lin Ming had reached the peak of the lower Empyrean realm. Strength gathered crazily within him. The planet-sized avatar of Famine gave him strength without end.

In addition to the talent of swallowing he had now, absorbing the flesh and blood essence of Famine came as easily as drinking water to Lin Ming. Lin Ming’s cultivation speed couldn’t even be described as travelling 10,000 miles in a day.

After staying in Tragic Death Valley for 1500 years, he finally felt he had accumulated sufficient strength.

The conditions were ripe. It was time to break into the middle Empyrean realm.

Chapter 2080 – Goal: Dark Abyss

There were naturally calendars in the Asura Road. But, these calendars didn’t start from the day the Asura Road was created.

In fact, a calendar that counted a mind-boggling number like billions of years was a nearly impossible matter.

Different areas in the Asura Road had different calendars. Moreover, in history, when a large influence unified a massive territory within the Asura Road, they would often create their own calendar and set the first year as the day they were established.

For instance, Divine Void Divine Kingdom and Heaven Union Divine Kingdom both used different calendars.

As for the Great Desolate, it used the Great Desolate Calendar. This calendar had already been in use for several million years.

As the middle-aged man suddenly said the number 1768, Lin Ming thought for a moment and asked, “Do you mean Year 121,768?”

Lin Ming added in two more digits, leaving the middle-aged man startled.

The middle-aged man immediately guessed that this young man in front of him hadn’t come out into the world for a long time, at least several thousand years, thus he asked them to confirm the calendar year for him.

Just who was this person? Why would so many evil beings be awed by him and submit to him?

These methods were something that not even an Empyrean would possess, right?

Had they managed to bump into some hundred million year old monster that had been in seclusion all this time?

Thinking of this, everyone felt a cold chill crawl down their backs. In particular, that black beam of light just then had clearly emerged from Tragic Death Valley. Could it be that… this man had come from Tragic Death Valley?

Realizing this possibility, the group was left speechless.

The middle-aged man still managed to keep his wits about him. He respectfully replied to Lin Ming, “Yes, Senior.”

He used the honorific of senior to refer to Lin Ming, and in truth this honorific wasn’t wrong. The only difference was that Lin Ming’s age was far from being as high as he imagined.

“Great Calendar Year 121,768. If so, then… this period of seclusion has already gone on for more than 5000 years. I thought that I broke into the Empyrean realm one or two thousand years ago, but perhaps it might have been even longer than that. It’s just that because I fused the 33 Heavenly Dao Laws together, time passed too quickly and in my entranced state I wasn’t able to clearly tell how much time I spent in there.”

5000 some years within Tragic Death Valley corresponded to 500 some years in the outside world.

According to the information provided by the Good Fortune Saint Son, over 500 years shouldn’t be enough time for the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign to finish his seclusion. But, the moment was rapidly approaching.

The truth was that even if the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign left seclusion, Lin Ming wasn’t afraid. He had Divine Dream helping him. Although Divine Dream couldn’t defeat the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, it shouldn’t be a problem for her to protect them and hide them away somewhere.

Currently, the Divine Realm was open and connected to other universes. With the wild universe and its convoluted terrain as well as a third universe, humanity had three universes they could hide in. To use the phrase that a crafty rabbit has more than three burrows and a cunning man has more than one backup plan was about right for this situation.

Like this, if the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign wanted to dig out human elites and kill them then this wouldn’t be easy. But, Lin Ming had to make haste. He didn’t want to leave his destiny to the heavens.

“Thank you.”

Lin Ming faintly smiled. He passed through the crowd of martial artists and continued walking out of God Burying Ridge.

He seemed to walk at a slow pace, as if he were casually idling his way through fog. But in the blink of an eye he had vanished from sight.

As for the evil beings of God Burying Ridge, they still lay sprawled out on the ground.

Seeing the motionless evil beings all around them, the squad of trial challengers had cold sweat dripping down their palms. They nervously said, “Let’s hurry and leave!”

They wanted to take this chance to quickly leave God Burying Ridge. But even though they were scared and apprehensive the entire way, they weren’t attacked by any evil beings as they left.

It was only when this squad emerged that they learned that what occurred around Tragic Death Valley happened in a much wider range than they thought.

This marvelous sight within God Burying Ridge was spread in numerous tales and exaggerated in different ways.

However, because there were too many guesses and too many versions of the story, even if some people had stories close to the truth, no one believed them. After all, their stories were far too unbelievable, and since they were only a minority, they didn’t have much persuasive power.

Slowly, what occurred in Tragic Death Valley morphed into a pure legend…

……….

Asura Sea, final trial –

Lin Ming stood in a broad starry space. Two old men were in front of him; they were the guardians of the final trial and also the servants who had served the Asura Road Master for generations – Clear and Ink.

“You want to go to the Dark Abyss?”

Hearing Lin Ming’s decision, Clear was bewildered. The Dark Abyss was simply far too dangerous.

“Two Seniors, I have decided that I must go to the Dark Abyss and this is a decision that came after a long period of deliberation. Since I dare to go, I naturally have methods to protect myself and no one should be able to recognize me. The reason I came here today was in truth to confirm something, a secret related to the Dark Abyss and the abyssal demons…”

As Lin Ming spoke, the two old men fell silent, not speaking for a long time.

Lin Ming continued, “I originally thought that the Dark Abyss and Primeval Realm Ruins might be entrances to a whole different world and that the 33 Heavens weren’t the only world there is. But afterwards, I obtained some information. It seems that the Dark Abyss comes from an ancient era of ancient eras. That it could be a place which existed a hundred billion years ago or even further back than that? I wonder if this is right?”

Hearing Lin Ming’s question, the expressions of the two old men changed. They glanced at each other, then Clear said, “Concerning the Dark Abyss, we only know some speculations and these are descriptions that the High Lord left in his letters in the past. Indeed, the Dark Abyss might have already existed for a hundred billion years…”

“Mm… so it really was like that. And, the great calamity of the universe 10 billion years ago was the ancient races fighting with the abyssals?”

Lin Ming asked. But concerning this assumption, many clues already confirmed that it was correct, and it wasn’t too difficult to guess anyways. Moreover, Famine’s memories proved this.

“That’s right. In the great war 10 billion years ago, countless God Kings perished and innumerable races were wiped from existence. Some universes were even left in tatters and devolved into wilderness. Compared to the great calamity of 10 billion years ago, the war between humanity and the saints isn’t anything at all.”

“I see… then, it seems that 100 billion years ago, an even greater calamity erupted in this universe? Compared to it, even the great war 10 billion years ago between the abyssals and the intelligent life forms of the 33 Heavens seems to be a minor matter?” Lin Ming suddenly said after a period of contemplation. This was only something he extrapolated from Famine’s memories.

But because he couldn’t be absolutely sure, he asked these two old men.

The two old men were stunned, seeming as if they didn’t expect Lin Ming to ask such a question.

They looked at each other. Then, Clear said, “The events of 100 billion years ago are far too distant, so distant that it is horrifying and nearly impossible to discover. The High Lord also managed to extrapolate some speculations. He believed that the Primeval Realm Ruins and the Dark Abyss were formed in that great calamity… the High Lord called this great calamity – the Shattering!”

“The Shattering…” Lin Ming sucked in a deep breath.

In truth, he had already heard the arguments people made against eternal life. To them, eternal life went against the Heavenly Dao Laws, and the reason for this was that all things in existence had to be born and had to die. Mountains could collapse, rivers could dry up, stars could fall, and even a boundless world would collapse and be destroyed.

There was nothing that could withstand the erosion of time.

Then what about the 33 Heavens?

Would there be a day when this world was destroyed?

If this were really to occur, then this would be the true horrifyingly great calamity.

All order, all rules, all life, nothing would exist anymore.

Lin Ming knew that the three divine treasures of the Magic Cube, Purple Card, and Grandmist Spirit Bead were possibly seeds of universes.

Since a universe could have such a seed, then that implied a universe could be born.

And with birth naturally came death. This was cause and effect, the cycle of samsara.

At this time, Ink said, “The High Lord suspected that the Dark Abyss and Primeval Realm Ruins are a piece of the world left behind after the previous 33 Heavens underwent the Shattering. As for why this part of that world wasn’t destroyed along with everything else, that is an unknown.

“And the abyssal demons are life forms that might have existed 100 billion years ago. They always lived in the Dark Abyss, and the Dark Abyss was originally isolated from the 33 Heavens. But because of some unknown reason, the two worlds connected, thus the great calamity of 10 billion years ago erupted.

“Of course, all of these things are merely guesses that the High Lord made…” Ink quietly said.

In fact, regardless of what the origins of the abyssals were, there was one thing that no one needed to doubt.

That was that the abyssal demons were the mortal enemies of all intelligent life in the 33 Heavens.

Chapter 2081 – Secret of the Black Book

Through speaking with Clear and Ink, Lin Ming was able to verify the memories of Famine. He was able to confirm all sorts of information about the great abyssal calamity 10 billion years ago.

10 billion years ago, the calamity of the 33 Heavens had finally been ended by the Eternal Wall.

The Asura Road Master and Immortal Sovereign joined forces, using their transcendent methods to forge the Eternal Wall and block off the Dark Abyss. After cutting off the source of these abyssals they proceeded to kill the other ones that remained.

Thus ended this great calamity.

The Eternal Wall was a barrier that only intelligent life forms of the 33 Heavens could pass. As for abyssal demons, they were sealed outside the Eternal Wall.

But the Eternal Wall wasn’t perfect and impregnable. As the wearing of time passed, many space-time cracks would appear. Some abyssals were able to pass through these space-time cracks and bypass the Eternal Wall.

The more powerful an abyssal was, the lower the chances of them passing through these space-time cracks.

Like this, even if those abyssals that passed through the cracks possessed a peak Empyrean level strength, they still wouldn’t be able to harm the 33 Heavens to any large degree.

But history was never without accidents. Billions of years ago, an incomparably terrifying abyssal demon somehow managed to pass through the Eternal Wall, bringing down a catastrophe unto all races of the 33 Heavens.

This catastrophe even continued until now.

This abyssal was ‘Famine’.

As for how Famine was able to pass through the Eternal Wall, Lin Ming wasn’t able to find this out from Famine’s soul. Many of Famine’s memories should have been kept in its main body, and some parts were also sealed away.

Lin Ming continued to explore Famine’s memories. Within the starry space he sat in the void.

At this time, an ancient pitch black book floated before him. This black book was left behind by Imperial Prince Xishen.

Lin Ming reached out a hand and gently traced its cover. Strange abyssal runes lit up, like the eyes of an abyssal demon flashing in the dark of night.

After absorbing a massive amount of Famine’s memories and furthering his understanding of the abyssal Laws, Lin Ming was now able to open the black book.

He silently flipped open the cover. The thick black cover seemed to be sealed by some force field, making it incomparably heavy.

This was not the first time he had opened this mysterious ancient book. But each time he did, he discovered new things.

The reason was that these abyssal texts were too difficult to understand. Trying to decipher them with the limited fragments of information he had wasn’t easy at all.

“The source of darkness, the abyssal ritual…”

Lin Ming read these words out loud and fell into a long period of contemplation.

In front of him, the black book shimmered with a mystical light, like the book of fate in the hands of the king of hell.

Lin Ming had already determined that this black book wasn’t some rare cultivation method manual nor was it some ancient secret technique, and it definitely wasn’t a True Divinity spirit treasure.

It was a book of abyssal rituals, and what was written inside were all texts of abyssal rites, texts that contained profound symbolic meanings.

These recitations of abyssal rites were completely unrelated to cultivation. They weren’t able to directly enhance a martial artist’s strength, but their value was still extraordinary.

Within the ranks of the abyssals, there were six super abyssals similar to ‘Famine’.

When they were at their peak strength, they were situated somewhere between peak True Divinity and Beyond Divinity. They were existences only inferior to the Asura Road Master!

They were the totems of the countless devils in the Dark Abyss, incredibly horrifying existences.

Underneath the command of each of these super abyssals was an influence of their own lineage. These influences were extremely powerful and contained countless abyssal demons. Many of these abyssals were comparable to middle True Divinity realm or even upper True Divinity realm characters.

If it were 10 billion years ago and each one of these influences turned out in full strength, then they would be able to easily overwhelm the current 33 Heavens, destroying all life within the universe.

Compared to these super influences, even the Good Fortune Saint Palace wasn’t anything at all.

However, in the great calamity 10 billion years ago, the ancient races also inflicted heavy losses on the Dark Abyss. The six great influences were the main forces of the war effort against the 33 Heavens, and they had suffered the greatest losses. Even many of the six great abyssals died, and the forces beneath them nearly fell apart.

Of these six great influences, each lineage possessed such a black book.

The six black books were ceremonial rites, and the ceremony they were related to was concerned with the deepest and most mysterious place of the Dark Abyss – The Demon God’s Tomb.

The Demon God’s Tomb was the foundation of the Dark Abyss and also the most enigmatic place in the Dark Abyss.

Lin Ming originally wanted to find out more information about this Demon God’s Tomb, but there wasn’t much within Famine’s soul. If this information was kept in Famine’s main body then there was nothing he could do to look for it.

Of the six great influences, Lin Ming’s black book belonged to the one named ‘Eon’!

Just like Famine, Eon was the name of the super abyssal that led one of these great influences. When Eon was at its peak strength, it was equal to Famine.

To hold the black book was tantamount to Eon being personally present.

But Eon’s true self had died in that great war 10 billion years ago…

Lin Ming now suspected that when he entered the Asura Road’s final trial for the second time and wrested away the demon relic from the Good Fortune Saint Son’s hands, this had been from a super abyssal that was killed by the Asura Road Master.

If it had truly been a super abyssal as horrifying as Famine then it was naturally impossible for it to leave behind such a small relic. Lin Ming guessed that the abyssal’s main body had been used by the Asura Road Master for other purposes, and the demon relic left behind was only a tiny portion of that super abyssal’s essence.

After finding explanations for all these questions, Lin Ming slowly closed the black book.

He stood up and flew towards the entrance of the final trial.

“You are leaving?”

Clear and Ink appeared behind Lin Ming.

Lin Ming nodded. “Yes.”

“Very well...”

Seeing Lin Ming’s decisive appearance, Clear and Ink no longer said anything.

On this day, Lin Ming left the Asura Road. He entered the Saint Convocation Heaven from the Divine Realm, and then flew straight towards the Primeval Realm Ruins…

As early as his life or death battle with the Good Fortune Saint Son, Lin Ming had already heard news about the Primeval Realm Ruins. This was an incomparably broad land that existed independently from the 33 Heavens. Countless lucky chances and treasures were buried here.

A great reason why the saints were able to accumulate so much strength was highly related to the Primeval Realm Ruins.

And today, Lin Ming finally came to this land.

Taking a broad look out, this was a dead and listless world. The skies were shrouded in gray as if an eternal dusk had settled upon this land.

There was an inexplicable divine pressure like the pall of hell covering this world, making one feel almost suffocated.

Of course, this sort of deathly aura and pressure couldn’t affect Lin Ming at all. But if a low level martial artist were to come here, perhaps they might not even be able to take a single step forwards no matter how hard they tried.

Lin Ming galvanized the strength within his inner world. The power of yin and yang wove together with the endless power of Laws, forming sparkling divine runes. Like rainbow-hued marks being carved into space, they emitted infinite light that shattered this deathly aura.

Lin Ming walked forwards one step at a time. Along the way, he saw bleached bones all around him.

There were many bones; most of them decayed. Shattered bones littered the ground, covered in the mottled traces of endless years. The reason for these marks to appear was because of the thick deathly aura that covered this land. This sort of deathly aura was able to draw out all life force. If one’s blood vitality was unstable and they walked through this land then they would soon turn into a dried corpse. As for the speed at which their corpse decayed, it would be astonishingly fast.

“This really is a nearly dead world…”

Lin Ming recalled Famine’s memories. He pondered for a moment. Because if a world died, all life within would gradually break down and come to an end. This was the Shattering that the Asura Road Master spoke of.

But according to his intuition, with this world having reached such a degree of decay it should have long since been destroyed. But, why had it continued to exist until now?

Somehow, somewhere, could there be some Laws supporting it so that not even the Shattering was able to destroy this world?

Lin Ming walked through this land, tasting the Law fragments left behind by the endless years. This sort of silent aura faintly resonated with the Death Laws in his body.

Death, was silence.

When a person died, they would return to dust. When a universe died, it would be annihilated into nothingness.

In the end, all things in existence only left behind one thing in the end – that was, ‘Nothing’.

On the distant horizon, one could see collapsed temples. Mountains of divine stone were piled up together. It was easy to imagine just how grand and magnificent they were in the past.

There were many of these great temples but not a single one was complete. All of them had become dilapidated ruins. These were structures created by powerhouses of the past, yet all of them had been corroded and damaged by the inexhaustible flow of time.

With every step he took, Lin Ming could feel ripples of powerful auras all around him.

These were auras left behind by ancient God Kings. They remained even after billions of years, reminding all who came here just how prosperous and mighty they had once been.

Lin Ming passed by a lake. The surface of it was like a mirror. Inside was a goddess bathing, her appearance beautiful and her charm devilish, captivating the heart, beckoning the soul.

Seeing this scene, Lin Ming was startled. For such a scene to appear in this deathly still world was surprising.

However, he immediately understood what this scene before him was. A pupil opened up between his eyebrows and a brilliant beam of divine light shot out, chopping onto the surface of the lake. The goddess shattered to pieces, turning into a wisp of strange Law fragments that slowly vanished.

These were the great world Law fragments that had condensed and then manifested into reality.

Lin Ming passed over a high mountain. Up above, endless divine demons beat upon drums, lightning wrapping around them as they all seethed like a rising tide.

Lin Ming’s inner world opened. Chaotic energy burst out, swallowing all of this divine demon aura.

In the Primeval Realm Ruins there was no ancient aura that could hinder Lin Ming’s steps. He walked forwards without stopping. Although his pace appeared slow, the truth was that space had lost meaning beneath his feet.

He walked for seven days.

During this time period, he once saw many saint martial artists enter into some underground ruins.

These ruins were buried all throughout the Primeval Realm Ruins. Countless dangers were hidden within, and many saint martial artists that entered were not able to leave.

But, there were always some people that went into these underground ruins and emerged with heaven-shocking lucky chances.

Chapter 2084 – Identity of the Divine Skeleton

Between the eyebrows of the crystal divine skeleton, flower petals of light appeared. These petals were like dots of cinnabar. As they formed they gathered around a center, forming a strange flower.

There were nine flower petals in total. Each one seemed to condense the most beautiful sights in the world, causing one’s mind to fall into reverie.

As this deep red flower reflected in Lin Ming’s pupils, he stood there transfixed for a long time.

A long time ago, 7000 years in the past – almost 12,000 years when he counted his time in Tragic Death Valley – Lin Ming had entered the primal god race’s Asura forbidden zone. In his trial within the Cold Ice Mirror, he had once seen a peerless woman dressed in black.

This woman had an appearance completely the same as Sheng Mei. Their temperament, their attitude, their appearance, everything was similar.

It was impossible that this was a mere coincidence.

And between that woman’s eyebrows, there was a mark composed of nine flower petals.

The only difference between that woman in the Cold Ice Mirror and this skeleton before him was that within the Cold Ice Mirror, that mysterious woman only had eight flower petals fully unfurled on her mark; the final flower petal was small, not fully stretched out.

But now in front of Lin Ming, nine flower petals were in full bloom. Their light was sharp and brilliant, leaving one intoxicated with their beauty.

“This is…”

Sheng Mei’s unrivalled appearance flashed in Lin Ming’s mind.

There were two possibilities. One of them was that this sort of flower petal mark belonged to a certain type of person, and this crystalline divine skeleton and the mysterious woman in the Cold Ice Mirror were both this type of person.

However this was an extremely unlikely possibility. After all, this type of peerless woman was simply far too rare 10 billion years ago.

Thus, the more likely explanation was that this crystalline divine skeleton belonged to the woman in the Cold Ice Mirror. She had died here and her bones were preserved for 10 billion years.

Could it really be that Sheng Mei was the reincarnation of a super powerhouse from 10 billion years past?

Thinking of this possibility, Lin Ming felt it was far too ridiculous.

10 billion years was simply far too long ago. What sort of peerless powerhouse could pass the river of 10 billion years after death to reincarnate?

Moreover, although Sheng Mei was fierce, the truth was that she was suppressed by the Soul Emperor. There was not just a simple disagreement between Sheng Mei and the Soul Emperor; the two could be described as sharing a deep grudge.

From this point, if Sheng Mei was truly the reincarnation of a peerless character from 10 billion years ago, how could she be restrained by the Soul Emperor?

All sorts of ideas raced through Lin Ming’s mind. He looked at the flower petals. With his sense, he couldn’t be wrong. The flower petals he saw right now were identical to the ones that the mysterious woman in the Cold Ice Mirror possessed. Not only were they similar in shape but their aura was also the same.

As for why there was a difference in the ninth flower petal, this might be because these flower petals were a manifestation of the cultivation method that the mysterious woman in the Cold Ice Mirror trained in.

For instance – the Grand Reincarnation Art.

With every reincarnation, an additional flower petal would appear between the woman’s eyebrows. With nine reincarnations, the flower petals would be complete, reaching perfection.

When Lin Ming had seen the black-clothed woman in the Cold Ice Mirror, she had just finished her eighth reincarnation and had yet to complete the ninth revolution!

And now it was obvious that before this mysterious woman perished, she had reached perfection in the Grand Reincarnation Art.

Upon realizing this, Lin Ming wasn’t sure what he felt.

The Great Dao was boundless and the heavens and earth were heartless. An ancient beauty that could bring the downfall of the worlds, a goddess of peerless grace and talent, even someone like this couldn’t escape the fate of becoming nothing but bones. As for those ancient rulers of a hundred races, those peerless proud sons of heaven, in the end they too turned to dust, their bones scattered in the wind.

This was destiny, the final fate that no one could avoid…

Lin Ming deeply bowed towards the remains of this goddess. And after he bowed, the soul fires in the goddess’ eye sockets slowly extinguished. All that remained were the runes on the surface of the bones. The runes glittered, allowing Lin Ming to clearly see the Laws within.

These runes were all slowly cultivated by this ancient peerless woman. What they contained included the universe of the body and the samsara of life and death recorded within the Holy Scripture!

Compared to the Holy Scripture, the runes on the goddess’ remains gave no hints. There was no beginning and no end; all there was were endless runes, each one more mysterious and complex than the last.

These runes originated from the Holy Scripture. But after fusing together with the mysterious woman’s own understandings and comprehensions, they were no longer the same as the Holy Scripture.

If one didn’t understand the Holy Scripture, if one didn’t have a deep martial arts foundation, then it would be completely impossible to understand just what these runes were.

Even for Lin Ming, wanting to understand these numerous convoluted bone runes wasn’t easy at all. He rapidly browsed through them, and then recorded them all in his mind using his formidable memory.

In the past Lin Ming had only seen the pages of life of the Holy Scripture. As for the pages of death, they were in memories left behind to him by Sheng Mei in that tiny part of her soul source; they were in truth extremely incomplete.

Lin Ming had relied on his own comprehensions and personally understood samsara through death to continue the pages of death.

In this state, as Lin Ming saw these bone runes left behind by this peerless woman from 10 billion years ago, it was equal to making up many missing places in his own Holy Scripture Laws.

Lin Ming slowly verified these bone runes with his own comprehensions, one at a time. He felt his mind open and new realizations pour in.

The martial arts civilization was a process of accumulation. Although there were proud children of heaven with outstanding talent capable of producing their own self-created cultivation methods, all these self-created cultivation methods had foundations based on the inheritances of their predecessors. It was impossible for anyone to create a cultivation method that far surpassed the current level of the martial arts civilization.

No matter how many reincarnations Lin Ming underwent, no matter how many samsaras of life and death he observed in the world, no matter how profound his comprehensions were, it was impossible for his Laws in the pages of death to be as complete as that of the Immortal Sovereign from 10 billion years ago, who had focused his lifetime of energy on the Holy Scripture.

And now, with the true Holy Scripture’s pages of death before him, Lin Ming was undoubtedly able to further his Holy Scripture Laws.

Lin Ming greedily remembered all he saw. A quarter hour passed. The shimmering runes of the divine skeleton began to darken; it was clear that the runes could only manifest for a short period of time. Lin Ming’s pupils widened and he sped up his reading pace.

These incomparably complex runes swiftly passed through Lin Ming’s mind and were recorded deep in his memory, marked into his spiritual sea.

This continued until the light of the bones faded away. By now, Lin Ming had memorized all of the bone runes.

Hu - !

The last wisp of light vanished and darkness returned to the altar temple. The divine skeleton also became tranquil once more.

Lin Ming faced the skeleton and bowed a final time.

When his mental strength probed the crystalline divine skeleton, the bone runes had lit up. This was clearly not a coincidence.

Could it be that the Holy Scripture Laws in his body had activated the bone runes somehow?

Or could it be that there was some wisp of residual consciousness in this divine skeleton, that managed to be preserved due to the array formation in this altar?

If this were true then these bone runes were intentionally revealed to him by this wisp of consciousness.

As Lin Ming thought of this, he became increasingly puzzled and uncertain as to the events of the great calamity 10 billion years ago. Just what connection did this mysterious woman who looked like Sheng Mei have with the Immortal Sovereign?

The cultivation method came from the same lineage – the Holy Scripture Laws. It was clear that they were closely related to each other, and at the time when Lin Ming entered the Asura forbidden zone’s Cold Ice Mirror, the hostility that the mysterious woman showed to the lineage of the Asura Road Master proved this point.

He didn’t know what level of strength this mysterious woman reached. Even if she hadn’t stepped Beyond Divinity, she was likely extremely close!

“Could this mysterious person be the same as Immortal Sovereign?”

As soon as Lin Ming thought of this he shook his head. In the planet-sized heavenly palace and the galactic battlefield in the Akashic Dream Universe, he had seen the phantom left behind by Immortal Sovereign more than once. He had obviously been a man, completely different from this mysterious woman.

But for this mysterious woman to be Immortal Sovereign’s relative, such as his daughter or little sister, just didn’t seem too likely. It was true that a family with an outstanding bloodline would have a higher chance of producing powerhouses, but to produce two people who neared or stepped Beyond Divinity, this was a bit too exaggerated.

Lin Ming didn’t understand any of this nor did he spend more time thinking about it. At this time, he spread his sense outwards into the bronze temple. Within it was a slowly spinning purple vortex.

This purple vortex was a part of the Eternal Wall and also the channel leading from the Eternal Wall to the Dark Abyss.

After passing through this purple vortex, what awaited underneath was the Dark Abyss!

In the abyss there were endless numbers of abyssal demons!

And this purple vortex was a channel that only intelligent life forms of the 33 Heavens could pass. In addition to the killing array of the dark altar, with these two insurances, there would be no abyssals that dared to come here to die.

Lin Ming let out a deep breath. Then, he leapt into the purple vortex!

Chapter 2085 – Dark Abyss

The moment Lin Ming passed through the Eternal Wall, he felt as if he were swimming through a river of time that flowed on for billions upon billions of years. He didn’t know how much time passed, perhaps thousands of years, perhaps just a mere instant, but during this time all sorts of chaotic scenes raced through his mind.

Then, he suddenly arrived on a black land.

This land was incomparably desolate. Everywhere he looked there were bare rocks that stretched out to infinity. Floating above this land, he could feel a deep and heavy permanence.

Nine suns hung high in the skies. Without exception, each one of these nine suns was blood red, and the sunlight they emitted caused one’s blood vitality to faintly resonate with it.

“This is the abyss!”

Lin Ming took a deep breath. The air here was burning hot and carried with it the faint smell of blood. This sort of air could subtly affect a person’s mind, slowly turning them violent and crazy.

Lin Ming felt his surroundings. Then, his figure flickered and he flew to a distant black mountain.

Hiding in this remote mountain, Lin Ming’s body started to change. His joints emitted crackling explosive sounds. Layers of scales and bone armor appeared on him and his limbs became thicker and more stout. Hideous bone spikes jutted out from his elbows, and curved horns grew out of his head. On his back, a fearsome tail extended downwards.

His eyes turned blood red and his aura became vicious and dangerous. He had completely taken the appearance of an abyssal demon, and not just that, but layers of demon power covered him, forming a faint black mist around him.

At this moment, Lin Ming had thoroughly become an abyssal.

After cultivating the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace to the sixth star and absorbing all sorts of top quality bloodlines, Lin Ming had already gained the ability to easily manipulate his bones and muscles, allowing him to transfigure his appearance however he wished.

In the past Lin Ming had absorbed the essence of Famine’s flesh and blood. Not just that, but in the Asura Road’s final trial he had also absorbed the demon relic, and during the process there was a period of time where his body had taken the appearance of an abyssal.

The power of demons and the demon bloodline had tried to invade Lin Ming’s body and possess him, but in the end he had subdued and digested it.

Now, Lin Ming could branch out this strength to easily manifest the aura of an abyssal.

His essence was that of a human, but if he were to disguise himself as an abyssal, then with his True Divinity level strength it would be difficult for any abyssal to see through him. This was because Lin Ming had absorbed the essence of Famine and also the demon relic. Since each of them was one of the six great totem rank abyssals, their abyssal bloodlines could not be any more pure!

Using a quarter hour of time, Lin Ming constantly adjusted the frequency of the demon power in his body and also checked over himself again and again to prevent there being any flaws in his disguise. He continued this until he felt it was perfect.

Lin Ming believed that even if Xiao Moxian were to stand in front of him, she would find it difficult to recognize him. That boiling demon power had covered all of his original aura.

He stretched a finger. This finger ended with a black and terrifying nail. On the end of Lin Ming’s fingertip, layers of black lines appeared, dancing in the air. These lines condensed together, turning into different shapes. Sometimes it was a sphere, sometimes it was a cube.

Finally, these figures completely collapsed, leaving behind a single point and becoming a mini black hole. The mini black hole greedily swallowed all the surrounding energy, and even light vanished when it entered.

This strange phenomenon belonged to Famine – it was the Laws of Swallowing!

Within Tragic Death Valley, Lin Ming had used a thousand years to absorb Famine’s essence and unlock its memories. Now, not only could he simulate an abyssal aura but he could even replicate the Laws of Swallowing!

It could be said that Lin Ming truly controlled a portion of Famine’s abilities. Although his Laws of Swallowing weren’t as strong as Famine’s, it was more than enough for him to use for absorbing energy for his own cultivation.

With the Swallowing Laws supporting him, Lin Ming’s cultivation speed and ability to accumulate energy would rise by a mind-boggling amount.

Woosh –

The black sphere vanished. He subconsciously cracked his wrists, a loud crackling sound coming from them. What he wanted to do now was to find a high level abyssal demon and see if it would recognize him.

A human had come to the world of the abyssals and had disguised himself as an abyssal to probe their secrets and steal their lucky chances. This strange feeling left a playful smile tugging at Lin Ming’s lips.

When this smile was joined with his current appearance, it gave off a fierce and bizarrely macabre feeling. This seemed like the vivid image of a sinister and cruel demon and if martial artists of the 33 Heavens were to see him, they would desperately try to kill him with everything they had.

Lin Ming’s figure flashed. His tall and strong body tore through the void, rapidly flying away!

In an instant he flew thousands of miles. Then, he fell down into a wild forest.

In Famine’s memories the Dark Abyss was like a pagoda; it was divided into different layers.

Each layer of the abyss was vast and boundless; it was hard to find where its edges were.

Every layer of the abyss had nine suns hanging high in the skies, forming a complete world.

From one layer to another, trillions of space channels connected them. These space channels overflowed with violent space storms. If an abyssal whose body wasn’t strong enough entered one of these space channels then it was possible they would be torn to shreds by the space storms.

The deeper one went into the abyss, the more intense the space storms became. Thus, generally speaking, low level abyssals were gathered in the first few layers of the Dark Abyss. As for the high level abyssals, they lurked in the lower layers.

They were like beasts hiding in the dark, waiting for the day they could run out of the abyss and swallow all living beings in the 33 Heavens!

Lin Ming didn’t plan to stay in the first several layers. It was impossible for these low level abyssals to see through his disguise. Moreover, if he stayed in the upper levels it would be impossible for him to find lucky chances.

The reason Lin Ming came to this forested mountain was because after probing the area with his sense, he discovered that there was a space channel hidden here, one that led to the next layer of the abyss.

However, as Lin Ming was looking for the space channel in accordance with what he sensed earlier, his footsteps paused.

He heard a rustling sound from the forest and also a faint killing intent.

It was clear that some sort of aggressive being was approaching.

Although Lin Ming didn’t have any interest in killing the low level abyssals at the first layer of the Dark Abyss, since he didn’t have any relation to them he might as well use this chance to test his Laws of Swallowing.

Lin Ming stood still, waiting for the abyssal to approach. Or, perhaps there was more than one, because there were four or five dangerous auras locked onto him.

However, when Lin Ming spread out his own sense and locked onto these abyssals, he actually stiffened!

This… just what was this!?

Lin Ming looked at a corner of the wild forest with disbelief thick on his face. He subconsciously gripped his fists.

Shua –

Shua –

The bushes of the wild forest were separated, and a few aggressive beings with fierce and distorted expressions emerged from the shadows.

Seeing these beings, Lin Ming sucked in a breath of cold air.

He would never have dreamed that after arriving at the Dark Abyss, the first attack against him would not be from abyssals, but by…

Humans of the 33 Heavens!

No… these weren’t humans, but some sort of ancient race that possessed a shape and appearance similar to that of humans.

However, from their distorted complexions and fierce features, their curved knees and spines and their arms that nearly hung to the ground, Lin Ming could clearly feel that these beings in front of him were not the usually-seen intelligent life forms of the 33 Heavens, but some sort of primitive and savage being without much intelligence of their own.

There were five people; four men and one woman, all of them stark naked. Their limbs brushed against the ground and bloodthirsty hope filled their eyes. These were eyes that only wild beasts would have.

The ancient race man in the lead emitted a deep and bass roar. He opened his mouth, revealing fangs like those of a blood-sucking vampire.

It was clear that this ancient race man considered Lin Ming an enemy, and even food.

“How could… this be?”

Lin Ming found this situation hard to accept. And at this time, the ancient race man roared and led the several people behind him to rush towards Lin Ming.

Their movements were like those of vicious beasts, but to Lin Ming who had reached a True Divinity level of strength, they were nothing but slow and clumsy, unable to harm him at all.

As long as Lin Ming wished it then the heads of these five wild ancient race savages would fall to the ground. However, Lin Ming’s mind was in a mess and he simply didn’t want to kill these savages. His figure flashed and he drew backwards like a ghost, instantly appearing a mile away.

The five savages emerged empty-handed. They were immediately enraged.

And at this time, Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred once more. He looked up in a direction. There, he could see four or five other living beings rapidly flying over.

These beings were covered in black armor. Their bodies were tall and thick and they held large axes in their hands. Their eyes were blood red and black energy tumbled around their bodies. They were clearly abyssal demons!

Whoosh!

An axe was hurled out by the leading abyssal. It tore through the air, howling in an arc as it circled around towards those five savages.

Blood shot into the air. Two savages were decapitated by the axe, their blood splashing out!

“Hehe! We caught another five prey! Although their cultivation is a bit lower, it's good enough. All of them are mine!”

The abyssal in the lead spoke in the abyssal language. Thanks to Famine’s memories, Lin Ming was able to understand him.

These words left Lin Ming dazed.

He seemed to realize a possibility. In the Dark Abyss, these ancient race people were considered the same as vicious beasts; all of them were regarded as prey.

And the abyssals were hunters. They captured and killed their prey in the open land, and this was how they gained experience!

Similar to when humanity developed the wild universe.

In the Dark Abyss, everything was reversed. The intelligent life forms of the 33 Heavens had become the prey instead!

Lin Ming had no idea what had occurred in the abyss. In the memories of Famine, the Dark Abyss originally wasn’t like this.

Chapter 2086 – Fate of the Ancient Races

“Hahahaha! How fun!”

The abyssal demon slashed out his axe once more. Another ancient race man had his neck sliced off. After a moment, only two of the five savages remained.

These two savages could clearly feel fear. They began to run in different directions, but how could the abyssal demon chasing them let them go?

The abyssal demon hurled two axes, each flying in a different direction and aimed at the back of an ancient race savage!

With the abyssal demon’s strength, accomplishing this was easy. However, just as those two savages were about to die, the axes seemed to strike upon some sort of invisible energy wall. With two loud cracking sounds, the axes fell to the ground.

Taking advantage of this moment, the two savages wildly fled deep into the forest.

“What!?”

The abyssal demon that shot out the axes was stunned. Then, he frowned, his complexion darkening.

He slowly turned to Lin Ming, derisively sneering as he said, “Are you the one that blocked me?”

Lin Ming was silent.

Killing intent erupted from the abyssal demon. He didn’t know why Lin Ming would rescue those two pathetic creatures, but at this time, Lin Ming’s lack of explanation and his contemptuous expression caused the abyssal demon to become even more furious.

He felt that Lin Ming was intentionally trying to pick a fight and was taunting him.

“You are courting death!”

The abyssal demon spat out.

Hua-la!

With a light sound, the five abyssals surrounded Lin Ming.

These abyssal demons were all iron claw demons; they were one of the relatively low level abyssals of the Dark Abyss. Their limbs were sturdy and powerful and they were extremely fast. Their claws could freely extend in and out of their bodies and were also sinisterly sharp.

At this time, the head abyssal demon no longer used axes. Rather, from between the spaces of his fingers, three foot long claws suddenly popped out.

These claws were like icy cold sabers. If an iron claw demon could cultivate to the level of an Empyrean, their claws would be equal to an Empyrean spirit treasure.

An iron claw demon that used their claws could display their greatest combat strength.

“Kill him.”

One of the iron claw demons shouted out loud. However, the head of the iron claw demons waved his hand, motioning for the others not to act rashly. The abyssal demon squinted his eyes and looked Lin Ming up and down, a cold light flashing in his eyes.

The abyssal demon was motionless and his followers didn’t move either.

The head iron claw demon stared at Lin Ming for a full ten breaths of time. Then, he stretched out his tongue and lightly licked his claws.

“Royalty?”

The iron claw demon asked Lin Ming. As this question fell into the ears of the other iron claw demons, all of them were startled.

From within Lin Ming’s body, this iron claw demon was able to feel a pure demon bloodline. The aura of this kind of demon bloodline would only appear in the bodies of high rank abyssals.

Now, the feeling that Lin Ming exuded was like that of a royal abyssal. This was no minor matter.

Royal abyssals possessed an extraordinary and lofty status. To kill them for no reason was a capital crime.

Moreover, generally speaking, royal abyssals weren’t weak. Wanting to kill one wouldn’t be easy at all.

But even so, there were numerous royal abyssals slaughtered every year. The reason for this was that abyssals could devour each other. If an abyssal demon swallowed a royal abyssal, they could obtain a part of that royal abyssal’s bloodline, improving their own body and greatly enhancing their strength!

The abyssals were a ruthless and tyrannical race. There was often slaughter within their own race, and in this sort of endless slaughter the abyssals would constantly evolve and transform.

Now, facing Lin Ming, this iron claw demon fell into a conundrum.

On one hand, he wanted to kill Lin Ming and steal away his royal bloodline. But on the other hand, he feared Lin Ming’s strength. He didn’t know Lin Ming’s background either. If he rashly acted and kicked an iron sheet then that would be stupid of him.

The several iron claw demons rapidly spoke with sound transmissions. The opportunity was placed right in front of their eyes and they didn’t want to let it go, but they didn’t think this was safe either.

As the iron claw demons discussed the situation amongst themselves, Lin Ming casually lifted his hand.

The several abyssals were startled. They didn’t know just what Lin Ming was doing. All they saw was Lin Ming simply cut a finger through the air, and then their eyes blurred as the world turned upside down.

Puff! Puff! Puff!

Five sharp slicing sounds filled the air. The heads of the five iron claw demons were instantly separated from their bodies. As their giant heads fell onto the ground, they bounced like rubber balls. In their final moments of death, all that filled their faces was utter disbelief.

“How… could this…”

The head of the iron claw demons could see his own body standing still and growing farther and farther away. His consciousness turned blurry; even now he had no idea how Lin Ming had killed them.

But the moment the iron claw demon was about to die, he felt an irresistible strength cover his spiritual sea. Then, a soul-tearing pain wracked his entire being as his spirit mark was forcefully erased by Lin Ming.

Lin Ming began using the Magic Cube to read through the memories of these abyssals.

He wanted to know everything about why they were hunting the ancient races.

These iron claw demons were of a very low level. As Lin Ming read through their memories it was the same as a mortal scholar reading through the well-known texts of the nation. It was rapid and easily understood at a glance.

Soon, Lin Ming obtained the information he wanted.

The situation was close to what he had guessed, and in truth was even worse than what he had thought!

The Dark Abyss had always had people of the ancient races. This even included the number one ancient race of the 33 Heavens – the primal god race.

And, these ancient race people came from the great calamity 10 billion years ago, when they were captured and brought here by the abyssals.

In the past when the Asura Road Master and Immortal Sovereign laid down the Eternal Wall to isolate the Dark Abyss from the 33 Heavens, these ancient race captives had inevitably been trapped in the Dark Abyss.

For all this time, the abyssals raised these ancient race people and transformed these captives. They left behind demon brands in their bodies, turning them into slaves, living furnaces, food, alchemy materials, experimental materials, and so forth.

In the great war 10 billion years ago, the destiny of the 33 Heavens’ ancient races had been shattered. Beneath the terrifying existence of the abyssals’ curse, the ancient races began to slowly decline. For instance, even an incredibly powerful race like the primal god race found it increasingly difficult to reproduce.

However, within the Dark Abyss, these ancient race captives weren’t affected by this curse. They retained their original ability to reproduce.

10 billion years was enough time for these ancient race captives to multiply and expand. Their population increased by countless times, until they covered every layer of the Dark Abyss.

Due to the careful efforts of the abyssals, the bloodlines of these ancient race captives had slowly merged together as one. The abyssals used curse arts, subjugation techniques, slave seals, and so forth to constantly enslave the ancient race descendants. At the same time, the abyssals even planted abyssal control factors in the bloodlines of the ancient races.

Slowly, the ancient races became no different than cattle, raised in captivity in large numbers by the abyssals.

The abyssals sealed away the intelligence of these ancient race descendants. Then they picked the best among them and let them loose in the wild, turning them into prey.

The ancient races had outstanding talent. Even after becoming savages they still retained a formidable combat strength. They were used as hunting targets for low level abyssals. Through killing these ancient race captives, the low level abyssals were able to hone their combat skills.

And deeper in the Dark Abyss, there were even some ancient race savages that hadn’t had their intelligence sealed away. They still retained their cultivation ability and even had some crude inheritances. As life forms with intelligence, they were even stronger.

But their fate was to be released into the wild mountains and plains to be hunted down by higher level abyssals.

Many abyssal influences would organize hunting parties to kill these ancient race descendants. There were even abyssal armies that marched directly into the wilderness and slaughtered massive numbers of ancient race members.

To the abyssals, the ancient races were their grinding stone. This was like mortals raising a tiger in a cage. They would throw live chickens to the tiger to eat in order to maintain its wild and fierce nature.

And so upon being born, the ancient race descendants who retained their intelligence faced the fate of being hunted down and slaughtered. But with their martial arts civilization ruined it was impossible for them to truly organize to resist the abyssals.

In the depths of the Dark Abyss, over these billions of years, many proud children of heaven had emerged from the ranks of the ancient races. They were outstanding individuals with amazing talent and formidable strength. They weren’t willing to accept the fate of being hunted down by abyssals for generation after generation, and organized large influences to resist them.

But in the end, all of them were mercilessly suppressed!

Ultimately the fate of these proud children of heaven was to be eaten up by the abyssals.

After understanding all of this, Lin Ming sighed. He never thought there would be a day when the intelligent life forms of the 33 Heavens would devolve into prey and be recklessly hunted down by others.

Chapter 2088 – Demon Association

The restaurant Lin Ming was in was called Blood Moon Hall. In Demon Snake City, although this restaurant wasn’t considered too expensive, it still charged a price of 100-200 demon crystals for a meal. It absolutely wasn’t an amount that a low level abyssal could afford.

Counting today, Lin Ming had stayed in Blood Moon Hall for 20 days.

At the start some beautiful succubus maids approached Lin Ming with their own thoughts in mind. But after being refused several times, they no longer bothered him. Like this, Lin Ming finally obtained peace and quiet.

He knew that these succubus maids were not amateur weaklings. In truth, the reason they flirted and enticed him was because they had thoughts of obtaining his royal bloodline.

Every day Lin Ming would come to Blood Moon Hall and order the most ordinary wine. Besides that, he didn’t order anything else. There was food and although the food was also expensive, it didn’t arouse any appetite in him. Rather, it even made one feel nauseous to the stomach.

What abyssal demons usually ate were: live insects, bloody meat, living beasts, parts of ancient race descendants, such as their brains, flesh, bones…

Every time Lin Ming saw some abyssals gather together to eat the flesh and blood of ancient race clansmen, he had the sudden urge to wipe every single one of them from existence.

“Have you heard? The Demon Association is planning to sell 10,000 high quality slaves. Of these high quality slaves, 8000 are young girls especially selected for their beauty. They have angelic appearances and their talent is also good. Moreover, all of them are virgins. They make the best possible living furnaces! As for the 2000 male slaves, they make decent slave guards. With slave seals planted in them, they will be absolutely loyal.”

In a corner of the restaurant, several abyssal demons began speaking as they tore away at chunks of blood beast meat. As they spoke their words slurred together and drops of blood leaked out from the corners of their mouths.

The Demon Association that these abyssals spoke of was one of the six totem level influences in the Dark Abyss.

Their leader was… Evil.

Evil was a super abyssal on the same level as Famine. After the ancient great war, Evil had gone missing. Some people said Evil had perished but there were also some who said Evil was lurking in the darkness. The reason for this was that although Evil went missing, the Demon Association didn’t fall apart. Rather, over these years, it developed more and more, growing with each year.

Billions of years ago it was the Demon Association that raised a massive amount of ancient race slaves and then constantly screened out these slaves and bred them. Then, they released them into the open wilderness, turning them into prey that was to be hunted down by abyssals.

In addition to that, the Demon Association also controlled over 90% of the ancient race slave business. Whether it was living furnaces, guards, experimental materials, alchemy materials, or anything else, all sorts of slaves could be bought from the Demon Association.

The slaves of the Demon Association were far more outstanding than slaves produced by other influences.

Over all these years, the Demon Association had accumulated an unknown amount of wealth. The reach of the Demon Association was spread throughout the entire Dark Abyss. Their headquarters were located in the 17th layer of the abyss, but they also had countless strongholds both large and small in the other layers.

In order to resist the Demon Association, the ancient race clansmen had stirred up countless revolves in these past billions of years. These were also the slave uprisings that the abyssals spoke of.

The ancient race rebel armies had once killed innumerable abyssals. But compared to a massive abyssal influence, an uprising of slaves was not worth mentioning at all. These rebel armies were nothing more than tiny splashes in an ocean, soon subsiding. Their only use was to help abyssals in training.

This was the sorrow of the ancient races.

In the past thousand years, a large-scale slave revolt had erupted in the abyss. The waves of the uprising swept through the abyss’ 11th, 12th, 13th, and 14th level – it was on a vast scale.

However, this so-called ‘vast scale’ was only relative to slave uprisings that occurred in the past several tens of millions of years. The truth was that to the abyssals, these rebel armies could be crushed to death with a single foot, no different from someone stepping on a cockroach or ant: simply unworthy of mentioning.

In the face of the slave uprising on the 12th layer, the bashe serpent continued sleeping. As for the Demon Association, they still continued selling slaves. None of them placed the rebel army in their eyes. At this time, the sale of 10,000 slaves was considerable business for Demon Snake City. The main reason was that the quality of these slaves was high, and whether it was men or women, they all had cultivations at the Divine Lord realm or above.

Lin Ming quietly listened in on this news. Then, he laid down a demon crystal to pay his bill and walked outside.

And when Lin Ming stood up, the several abyssals in the corner of Blood Moon Hall glanced at each other and quietly followed him.

Lin Ming seemed to not have noticed this.

He carried a pot of wine with one hand and drank it while he strolled through the city.

Abyssals favored wine brewed with blood and didn’t have any interest in spirit wines brewed from heavenly materials. Thus, the level of these spirit wines couldn’t be compared to those brewed in the 33 Heavens.

Lin Ming continued to drink a mouthful at a time as he walked to a remote location outside the city.

This was a good place to kill someone and steal away their possessions.

The abyssals that followed Lin Ming looked at each other, excitement growing in their eyes.

They were long-tail demons. They had crocodile-like heads and crocodile-like tails. They were inherently cruel and bloodthirsty and loved to rip their prey apart. As soon as they came to Demon Snake City they had locked onto Lin Ming.

To them, Lin Ming’s bloodline was extremely tempting.

In these past days Lin Ming had come across many similar events. The world of abyssals originally followed the laws of the jungle where they strong ate the weak. After Lin Ming suppressed his cultivation he also blatantly walked around in public with his royal bloodline; this was no different from a little child carrying gold bars and walking round the city streets.

The further Lin Ming walked, the more desolate and bleak the surroundings became. But the abyssals didn’t develop any suspicions at all. Rather, they grew even more excited. At this time Lin Ming stopped and slowly turned around.

The several abyssals feverishly grinned. In their eyes, Lin Ming was a dead man walking.

“Brat, be a good little boy and give us your bloodline and we’ll let you die in peace! Hahaha!” The several abyssals laughed, looking at Lin Ming with mockery in their eyes.

Lin Ming sighed. “How stupid. Even at the precipice of death you still keep laughing. Haven’t you realized by now that I intentionally led you here?”

As Lin Ming spoke, the abyssals were stunned.

“What?”

They no longer had the time to think. Lin Ming’s sharp claws slashed through their throats and blood sprayed out!

Peng! Peng! Peng!

Lin Ming punched out his fists. Billions and trillions of threads of demon power surged outwards, directly breaking into the bodies of these abyssals. This was Lin Ming’s Body Tearing Bone Shattering Fist.

Then, Lin Ming waved a hand and a black vortex swirled into existence.

Swallowing Laws!

After absorbing the flesh and blood essence of Famine and carving the Law runes of Famine into his body, Lin Ming had inherited its swallowing ability.

The truth was that for Famine, it was no longer accurate to describe its swallowing ability with Laws. Rather, this was a type of talent, a talent that turned another’s strength into one’s own!

Now, what Lin Ming displayed was this sort of talent. The abyssals he just killed were mostly at the Holy Lord realm, and the strongest of them was at the peak Holy Lord realm.

The strength of these abyssals was also drawn out by Lin Ming, turned into the purest strength where it converged within him and nourished his demon body.

Now, Lin Ming was still training this swallowing ability. He couldn’t be as freakish as Famine and swallow the strength of others without leaking out any bit at all.

Lin Ming could swallow at most 70-80% of another’s strength. And as the other party’s cultivation got higher, there was a proportionately smaller amount of strength that Lin Ming could absorb.

However, this was still several times faster than Lin Ming’s previous cultivation speed.

A low absorption ratio didn’t matter; he would simply need to kill more abyssals in exchange. The abyssal demons were mortal enemies with the intelligent life forms of the 33 Heavens to begin with, and Lin Ming showed no mercy in slaughtering them.

For the last 20 some days, as Lin Ming practiced Famine’s swallowing talent he was able to swallow an increasingly high level of strength. Lin Ming felt he could now attempt hunting down World King level abyssals, and after several more months, he could even pursue Empyrean level abyssals.

At that time, Lin Ming’s cultivation speed would rise to even greater heights.

Thinking of this, Lin Ming coldly sneered.

Demon Association… this seemed to be a decent target!

After a period of thought, Lin Ming waved his hand and gathered the souls of the abyssals. By now, he didn’t even need to summon the Magic Cube. With another wave of his hand he directly erased the spirit marks of these souls and then used a short period of time to read through their memories.

For these last 20 some days, every time Lin Ming killed an abyssal he would read their memories. His understanding of the Demon Association became increasingly profound.

Know oneself, know your enemy, and be undefeated in a hundred battles. Since he had placed this Demon Association as one of his targets, he naturally had to seek out all the information he could on them.

Chapter 2093 – Abyssal Ritual

“She disappeared?”

Lin Ming was puzzled. How did Fishy suddenly go missing?

“Mm…” Mo Eversnow shook her head. “I have no idea where she went. When I passed through the Eternal Wall, she was still with me. But, the instant I was in the Eternal Wall, she seemed to be swept away by a spatial vortex and vanished. For all these years I’ve been looking for her but I haven’t found any news…”

Sorrow and guilt weighed down Mo Eversnow’s shoulders; she felt that she didn’t take good care of Fishy.

“Spatial vortex…” Lin Ming frowned. Fishy was an energy form and in truth she could attach herself to Mo Eversnow. But even in such a situation she was swept away by a turbulent space flow, and yet Mo Eversnow had remained fine. Something seemed unusual about this.

Just what had happened?

Seeing Mo Eversnow’s sad expression, Lin Ming comforted her. “Senior-apprentice Sister, you might not know this but Fishy is originally a life form produced from the Purple Card. If she was swept away by a spatial vortex then that might not necessarily mean something bad happened to her. It might even be a lucky chance, or perhaps she was even summoned by something…”

Lin Ming couldn’t think of a reason thus he could only remain optimistic.

Now, no one knew whether or not Fishy was in the abyss. And even if she was in the abyss, wanting to look for her was no different from looking for a needle in the sea. And in fact, if Fishy was taken away as she passed through the Eternal Wall, she might not have even entered the abyss…

“Purple Card…” Hearing Lin Ming mention the most mysterious of the three divine tools, a thoughtful light appeared in Mo Eversnow’s eyes. If it had been the Purple Card that summoned Fishy, that would be the best possible result. But, where was the Purple Card?

“Could it be in the Demon God’s Tomb?”

Mo Eversnow muttered to herself.

The Demon God’s Tomb located in the 18th layer of the Dark Abyss hid far too many secrets.

“What is in the Demon God’s Tomb? The middle-aged man I spoke to convinced me to come here with secrets of the Demon God’s Tomb. It’s lucky he had some sudden inspiration to mention this, otherwise we might have never met.”

Lin Ming attached great importance to the Demon God’s Tomb. It seemed to be the most mystical and most important location in the Dark Abyss.

“I don’t have a complete understanding of the Demon God’s Tomb. In my years in the Dark Abyss, I have killed some high level abyssals and obtained their abyssal records for myself. I studied the abyssal language by myself and was just barely able to understand it. It seems that the most powerful strength of the Dark Abyss is hidden within the Demon God’s Tomb. In truth, it is also the birthplace of totem level abyssals, the same place Famine, Deep, Eon, Evil, and those other super abyssals come from!”

“Birthplace of totem level abyssals?” Lin Ming asked, his mind shaking. This rank of abyssal was far too terrifying. At their peak strength they were existences only inferior to the Asura Road Master. There were no life forms in the 33 Heavens capable of contending with them!

The only thing worth celebrating was that 10 billion years ago, the Asura Road Master and Immortal Sovereign had joined forces to fight these totem level abyssals. Several of them had either died, been severely wounded, or gone missing.

But from what Mo Eversnow said, it seems that the Demon God’s Tomb could give birth to new totem level abyssal demons. Lin Ming felt ill at ease. If this were true and new totem level abyssals were to appear, then the 33 Heavens were in danger.

“Do totem level abyssals have parents? How are they born?”

Concerning secrets of the Demon God’s Tomb, Lin Ming was unable to obtain any from Famine’s soul. Those memories had been sealed away to an incredible degree. If a super abyssal and another super abyssal joined together and produced an inherently super abyssal, then that would be horrifying.

“They aren’t.” Mo Eversnow said, shaking her head. “Totem level abyssals weren’t born. Rather, when an abyssal with a top True Divinity level strength accepts the energy of the Demon God’s Tomb to enter their bodies, they are promoted to a higher realm! After this promotion is completed, this new abyssal can slowly cultivate to activate the energy within their body.

“This entire process is called the ‘abyssal ritual’. But, the burden it places on the body is far too great. There is an extremely high demand on the life potential and strength of the abyssal who accepts this ritual. If their body cannot withstand this energy then they will directly turn to ashes. Moreover, there is a condition in order to begin the ‘abyssal ritual’, and that is that… one requires mysterious ritual rites, a token required to open the Demon God’s Tomb. This is also the key to activate the ‘abyssal ritual’.”

As Mo Eversnow spoke, a strange color flashed over Lin Ming’s face.

“What is it?”

“The ritual rites you spoke of is likely this, right…”

Lin Ming traced his spatial ring and a mysterious black book appeared in his hand. This black book was wrapped in grandmist energy and seemed as if it had a life of its own. It pulsated, as if a heart was sealed within. And this wisp of grandmist energy suppressed these life fluctuations. Originally, Lin Ming had to rely on the Ancient Elysium Seal to accomplish this, but after reaching a True Divinity level strength he was able to use his grandmist energy to do the same.

Seeing this black book, Mo Eversnow was immensely shocked. In some texts she had seen descriptions and records concerning the ritual rites. They were supposed to be written in a black book, and that black book was similar to the one Lin Ming was holding!

“This… where did you get it from?”

“I obtained it from the hands of a saint race genius, and where he found it from was…the Primeval Realm Ruins.” Lin Ming casually stated.

Mo Eversnow was stunned speechless upon hearing this. “So something like that happened… there are a total of six of these black ceremonial books, each one corresponding to one of the six great totem level abyssals. Only when a totem level abyssal dies will the corresponding black book appear.

“Every time the Demon God’s Tomb is opened and the black book is used, and if the abyssal that withstands the ritual successfully passes the test, then the black book will vanish and no longer appear.

“On the other hand, if the abyssal that undergoes the ritual fails then they will disintegrate to ashes and the black book will disappear into the void, appearing in some far off and unknown place. Sometimes, the black book will even leave the Dark Abyss. Countless abyssals desire to obtain a black ritual tome and many high level abyssals will use all methods they have to search for one. However, to look for one cannot even be described as searching for a needle in an ocean. Thus there is a saying that an abyssal who obtains a black ritual tome is favored by the Demon God and is also an inborn Demon Envoy. A Demon Envoy has an extremely high status in the Dark Abyss, because they have been favored by the Demon God and also because their chances of passing the test and becoming a totem level abyssal are the highest!

“I never imagined that this black ritual tome in your hand would actually have been obtained by a saint genius. What a cruel joke. The intelligent beings of the 33 Heavens have actually received the favor of the Demon God…”

Mo Eversnow shook her head, clearly showing contempt towards these abyssal legends.

But Lin Ming hesitated for a moment, as if he were mulling over something.

“Mm? What are you thinking about?” Mo Eversnow asked.

“I was just thinking on what to do with this ritual rites tome…” Lin Ming rubbed his chin, opening the cover of the black book.

The first sentence of the black book’s title page was: “The Tomb is the end, and also the beginning!”

Then, what was written was, “The one who possesses this book is the embodiment of Eon!”

‘Eon’ was the name of a totem level abyssal. No matter which abyssal managed to withstand the baptism of the abyssal ritual, that demon would become Eon. And when Eon died, only then would this black book appear.

“What to do with the black ritual rites tome…” Mo Eversnow furrowed her eyebrows, “It doesn’t seem as if it can be destroyed. The safest method would be to hide it in some place where no abyssal can find it so that the Dark Abyss will forever be missing a totem level abyssal. Or, we can come up with a plan to use the black book to set up a trap and draw in high level abyssals and then kill them. But, this is extremely risky… it would need to be planned in great detail… otherwise, it would be the same as giving treasures to the abyssals…”

For a time, all sorts of thoughts raced through Mo Eversnow’s mind.

However, Lin Ming shook his head, “Senior-apprentice Sister, what I was thinking of just now… was to do something else… and it might even sound a bit crazy…”

“Mm?” Mo Eversnow was startled.

“Senior-apprentice Sister, please look at this first.”

As Lin Ming spoke, he roared from the bottom of his lungs. His voice became bass and low, sandy and loud, as if peals of thunder echoed out in the skies.

His entire body emitted explosive crackling sounds as he grew taller and his muscles bulged out. Fierce plates of bone armor and scales appeared on the surface of his skin and bone spikes jutted out from his knees and elbows.

In just an incense stick of time, Lin Ming had become an abyssal demon!

Mo Eversnow was utterly bewildered.

“You… how did you do this!?”

She knew that Lin Ming’s body transformation technique had reached an extremely high boundary, and one could use the body transformation to change the structure of their body. But to turn into an abyssal like Lin Ming did now was far too exaggerated. Moreover, she could feel the aura of an abyssal exuding from Lin Ming’s body, and it was impossible to fake this sort of aura.

“I cannot even… recognize you!”

If she hadn’t stared blankly on as Lin Ming completed this transformation in front of her, then she wouldn’t have recognized that the abyssal in front of her was a disguised human. Moreover, it would have been impossible for her to recognize Lin Ming.

This camouflage was far too perfect.

“Well… this is a long story. Senior-apprentice Sister, I have the power of demon in my body. What I was thinking of just now was whether or not it would be possible for me to withstand the abyssal ritual.”

Lin Ming’s words left Mo Eversnow panic-stricken.

A human to withstand the abyssal ritual?

This was too crazy!

“This is too dangerous, you simply don’t know what will occur when you withstand the abyssal ritual. Even high level abyssals can die when they withstand the abyssal ritual. And with your current strength…”

In truth, Mo Eversnow didn’t know what the limits of Lin Ming’s strength were. But, she shouldn’t be wrong that Lin Ming’s cultivation was at the middle Empyrean realm. Even if she considered that Lin Ming possessed heaven-defying potential, he still couldn’t be more formidable than a True Divinity level abyssal, right?

“Also, even if you managed to survive the abyssal ritual, this abyssal ritual is originally prepared for abyssal demons. If you withstand the ritual… will you even still be you?”

Mo Eversnow spoke her worries. Lin Ming said, “My soul is protected by the Magic Cube so there shouldn’t be a problem. Moreover, I also plan to open the seventh Dao Palace – the Twofold Dao Palace. Like this, it will be much safer for me…”

Chapter 2094 – Twofold Dao Palace

“Twofold Dao Palace… you have already reached the Twofold Dao Palace?”

Upon hearing that Lin Ming planned to open the Twofold Dao Palace in the near future, Mo Eversnow was startled. She never imagined that Lin Ming’s cultivation speed of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace would be so fast.

The Nine Stars of the Dao Palace – seven bright and two dark. As the seventh Dao Palace of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, the Twofold Dao Palace was the last of the seven bright Dao Palaces and also the most unusual Dao Palace.

Its unusualness was embodied in its position. Every Dao Palace had a specific position in a martial artist’s body. For instance, the Daevic Eye Dao Palace was in between the eyebrows, the Martial Sovereign Dao Palace was in the four limbs, the Purple Temple Dao Palace was in the dantian, and so forth.

As for the Twofold Dao Palace, it had a particularly unique position; it was located outside a cultivator’s body.

After the Twofold Dao Palace opened, it would condense into a star that appeared in the void not too far away from a martial artist. This star was named the Twofold Star.

Then, the Laws of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace would use this Twofold Star as the foundation, gathering infinite starlight and gradually taking the form of a person’s phantom.

This phantom would be completely similar to a cultivator in appearance.

Thus, this was where the name of the Twofold Dao Palace came from.

As the last of the seven bright Dao Palaces, the Twofold Dao Palace gathered the most strength of the nine stars, several times that of the previous Dao Palaces. This also meant that the Twofold Dao Palace was the mightiest of the seven bright Dao Palaces.

When this starlight phantom first appears it would have 50% of the true body’s combat strength. After that, as long as the cultivator poured in a part of his source blood vitality and source soul, concentrating it into this Twofold Star, then it would be able to have a flesh and blood avatar.

This avatar was named the Twofold Avatar.

The more blood essence the Twofold Avatar received, the more powerful it would become. In addition, with the starlight of the highest heavens that the Twofold Dao Palace gathered, it would eventually become an extremely powerful weapon.

Of course, because the cultivator branched out a part of their blood vitality, they would suffer some damage to their strength. But the degree to which they were injured would be far less than that increased strength brought about by the avatar.

In the martial world there were numerous techniques that allowed one to control avatars. For instance, the Asura Heavenly Dao had its own cultivation and fighting methods involving avatars.

However, in these cultivation methods, the avatar formed was usually refined.

For instance, the Asura Heavenly Dao’s three avatars. The Essence Spirit Embryo Stone, Soul Springs Divine Embryo, these were divine stones naturally bred through the world and didn’t originate from Lin Ming himself.

If Lin Ming were to lose his avatars, although it would decrease his strength, it wouldn’t cause any true damage to his body. But, the Twofold Dao Palace was different.

The avatar of the Twofold Dao Palace was created by a martial artist taking out a portion of his blood essence and casting it in starlight of the high heavens, transforming it into true flesh and blood.

One couldn’t afford to lose such an avatar.

Moreover, this avatar came from the same origins as the main body. It could separate from the main body and also fuse with the main body.

Once the avatar and main body merged together, it would cause one’s strength to erupt, doubling over.

This sort of ability was not something that a refined avatar could possess.

In normal situations, after a martial artist opened the Twofold Dao Palace, the main body and avatar were mostly fused together. With this one could display the greatest strength.

It was only in cultivation that they would separate. Like this, absorbing heaven and earth origin energy would be that much faster.

Lin Ming fervently wished to open the Twofold Dao Palace now, because after he opened it he could use its special characteristics to separate the power of divinity and demons in his body.

Lin Ming’s Twofold Dao Palace had a large difference from that of others who cultivated the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace.

Generally speaking, once a martial artist opened their Twofold Dao Palace and separated out their avatar, this avatar would be no different from their main body. If the avatar and main body were separated, this would make one’s fighting techniques more flexible and their cultivation speed faster. If the avatar and main body were fused together, then this would be the same as superimposing their strength together.

But Lin Ming was different. He planned to use the Twofold Dao Palace as the foundation, and after condensing the starlight phantom he would then pour all of the demon power in his body into this avatar, turning his Twofold Avatar into a complete demon avatar!

As for his true self, he would leave behind the power of divinity and the corresponding bloodlines.

By doing this Lin Ming would have a more flexible identity in the future. He could fuse with his avatar whenever he wished and also separate whenever he needed to.

As for this abyssal Twofold Avatar, it would be able to recklessly use the Swallowing Laws to swallow the power of demons while his main body absorbed the power of the world, allowing his cultivation to rise faster and faster.

If so, then Lin Ming wouldn’t need to worry that using such an evil and unorthodox cultivation method like the Swallowing Laws to rapidly increase his cultivation would make his foundation unsteady, nor would it cause a backlash.

After opening the Twofold Dao Palace and entering the Demon God’s Tomb, he could even use his avatar to transform into the shape of an abyssal and undergo the abyssal ritual. Like this, there shouldn’t be a problem…

Lin Ming spoke his ideas to Mo Eversnow.

As Mo Eversnow heard this, she was stunned for a long time. “You… you want to form a demon avatar?”

Mo Eversnow felt this was all too inconceivable. How could Lin Ming have approached the seventh Dao Palace so quickly, and where did he obtain Famine’s essence from?

“It should be possible. This avatar is myself and not something I seized. As long as I branch out a wisp of my source soul into my avatar, then it will be a second me.”

“This is… just what have you gone through these past years?” Mo Eversnow had long been wanting to ask this, but she didn’t have a chance since there were so many matters to discuss.

It should have been impossible for life forms of the 33 Heavens to seize the body of an abyssal. If Lin Ming were to form a demon avatar in the future, this would be an unbelievable event.

Lin Ming told everything he experienced in the last 7000 years to Mo Eversnow without holding anything back. He described being chased down by Soaring Feather, his own source soul force being taken by Sheng Mei, his tribulations in the lower realms, his seven reincarnations, his arrival in the wild universe, his absorbing of Famine’s soul and controlling Famine’s avatar, his overcoming two God Kings and making them withdraw from the war between humanity and the saints…

Towards Mo Eversnow, Lin Ming had no need or desire to conceal anything. She already knew about the secret of the Magic Cube so what else was there left to hide?

After listening to Lin Ming’s experiences Mo Eversnow fell silent for some time. For these past years, Lin Ming’s experiences were simply far too bizarre. From the verge of death, to the abyss of despair, to standing up tall once more, to entering the wild universe and turning the tides, to becoming a leader of humanity and being titled the Human Sovereign, it wouldn’t even be enough to describe Lin Ming’s life as one that experienced simple ups and downs.

She thought that with all the lucky chances and life-or-death slaughters she encountered in the Primeval Realm Ruins, her life had been considerably adventurous. But when compared to what Lin Ming had experienced, it seemed quite bland instead.

“So the reason you went missing in the past was because of Sheng Mei. She…”

Mo Eversnow was at a loss for words. She just couldn’t understand why Sheng Mei did what she did. “You said that Sheng Mei has a great enmity with the Soul Emperor and after she took away your strength she still left behind a wisp of her source soul in your body, and even sealed her primordial yin and Grand Reincarnation Art into it? But what is the meaning behind doing all of this? In that sort of situation, the chances of you overcoming the odds to rise once more were nearly zero. Sheng Mei didn’t know you had the Magic Cube either, so why would she think you could restore your strength?”

Lin Ming sighed and shook his head. “I am not sure either. Her methods at the time were probably the only choice she could make after she joined the Soul Emperor and found herself powerless to do anything. At that time, I truly would have died, but Sheng Mei relied on the faintest glimmer of her intuition to leave behind one last hope for me, as well as one last hope for her…”

Sheng Mei was a woman no different from a puzzle.

Thinking of her, Lin Ming once more recalled the mysterious peerless woman who had appeared in the Cold Ice Mirror and whose remains were left behind in the center of the Eternal Wall.

To surpass a river of time that flowed for 10 billion years, Sheng Mei and that mysterious woman were no different from a martial artist and their Twofold Avatar. Just how could they be related?

Sheng Mei and the Soul Emperor’s fate, all that she did to him, everything left Lin Ming with extremely complicated feelings towards Sheng Mei.

She was neither good nor evil. She seemed to have seen the limitless scenery of the world, and also seemed to be shouldering a pitiful and sorrowful story…

However, no matter what her life experiences were, no matter what it was she wanted, Lin Ming knew that seven thousand years ago when he was being hunted down by Soaring Feather God King without hope of escaping, when he was also being eyed by the Soul Emperor on another side, it was Sheng Mei who had saved him. This graciousness was not one that Lin Ming would forget, even if Sheng Mei’s methods had been filled with riddles…

The feeling she emitted was like a pearl shrouded in the darkest fog. 10 billion years ago a flower falls and 10 billion years later a flower opens. To overcome the samsara of 10,000 lives, unaffected by karma, fated for life and death…

Chapter 2097 – The Final Request

“What does sir think? If sir is satisfied then you may feel free to take a look. These slaves are all high quality goods with superior talents and they have also been trained since childhood in all manners of skills to please and pleasure you. Moreover, all of them are virgins!”

The succubus demon leaned in close to Lin Ming’s ears and blew out her steamy breath.

She didn’t believe that Lin Ming would be able to resist such temptation. Of course, if he wished to go down and recklessly play with them then he would need to pay the deposit money and also purchase the slaves too.

Lin Ming shook the jade slip in his hands, glancing over the prices. Although he already knew the approximate pricing of these female slaves, seeing the long line of numerals still left him slightly flabbergasted.

These slaves were far too expensive.

However, Lin Ming was also extremely wealthy. For the last year he had killed hundreds and thousands of abyssals, including even an Empyrean level abyssal. He was already wealthy to begin with, and when he came to Black Sand City he also brought the numerous demon crystals that Mo Eversnow had.

In these past years, the Ancient God rebel army had accumulated an astronomical level of wealth.

“The deposit money is here. I will buy them all!”

Lin Ming took out a spatial ring and flicked it towards the succubus demon. The succubus demon grabbed it and probed it with her sense. She was immediately shocked. Within this spatial ring were piles upon piles of demon crystals; it was simply hard to estimate how many there were. Let alone the dozen some young girls bathing in the spring below, even if there were hundreds of them this money would be more than enough.

And from what Lin Ming said just then, this was also only a deposit!

Deposit money…

This meant that Lin Ming would take out even more wealth and buy even more slaves. Thinking of this, the succubus demon was immediately excited.

“Sir, you are far too generous. Would you like to go down now to take a look?”

She thought that after Lin Ming bought the young girls in the valley he would certainly dive into that warm pond and enjoy himself in devouring those beautiful women. But, she never imagined that Lin Ming would issue a terse order, “Have those people put on clothes and follow me!”

“Put… put on clothes!”

The succubus demon was stunned. The Demon Association Branch Division had spent a considerable amount of effort to arrange the scene below, and yet this royal abyssal had no intention of doing anything with the young girls. To have such beautiful young girls put on clothes, wasn’t that just a waste of goods…?

Although she was puzzled in her heart, in Black Sand City a customer’s requests were everything. The succubus demon could only act accordingly.

All of the young girls in the valley were ordered to rise up, dry their bodies, and then put on clothes to follow Lin Ming.

Then, Lin Ming went to the high platform he saw before. The slaves here were all enclosed in iron cages.

In this giant slave market there were some slaves that showed a positive demeanor. But, there were even more young girls who were only giving performances in the iron cages to attract customers.

There was no young girl willing to be held in an iron cage as a commodity to be sold and bought.

Like this, whether they were ephemeral Saintesses or little girls that seemed to be treasures of families, they were only maintaining their outer appearance beneath the threats of the Demon Association. Lin Ming could actually see their bodies gently shaking. Some girls were pale with beads of tears at the corners of their eyes. They were nervous but also pitiful.

To the abyssals, the delicate and fragile appearances of these female slaves could arouse the beastly desires in their hearts.

There was even the rare kind-hearted abyssal who would feel a protective desire upon seeing these slaves. Even so, no matter who they were, they would still buy these slaves.

“Raise your head! Stand at the front of the iron cage for me!”

As Lin Ming stepped before an iron cage, two identical young girls shrank back into a corner, subconsciously lowering their heads. They didn’t dare to look at Lin Ming now because his appearance was simply far too fierce.

To these young girls who had just bloomed, it was hard to imagine just what sort of master Lin Ming was and what awaited them.

“I’m speaking to you two! Are you deaf!?”

Near the iron cage, an iron claw demon raised a whip, enraged at the disrespectful appearance they showed towards Lin Ming. He lashed out his whip and the two young girls panicked upon seeing this.

These iron claw demons were extremely skilled in using their whips to cross through the slits of the iron cage and strike the girls’ bodies. The strike would hurt but it wouldn’t break their skin, in order to avoid leaving behind scars.

The two young girls subconsciously closed their eyes. However, the pain didn’t arrive. They opened their eyes and saw that the iron claw demon’s whip had been grabbed by a towering abyssal before it fell.

Compared to this large abyssal, the iron claw demon seemed as small as a chicken.

The iron claw demon smiled apologetically. “I apologize for this shameful sight. These little girls only arrived a short time ago and are still a bit wild. Slashing them with a few whips will be enough.”

Lin Ming looked upon the iron claw demon, revealing a bit of killing intent in his eyes that caused the iron claw demon to shrink away, a cold chill running down his back.

“You… you…”

The iron claw demon gulped, not sure of what to say. He didn’t want to offend such a powerhouse.

Luckily for him, Lin Ming had already turned his head, giving the iron claw demon a chance to catch his breath.

“I’ll buy them.” Lin Ming coldly said to the succubus demon behind him.

The succubus demon was overjoyed. As for the two young girls in the cage, they were flustered, unaware of just what fate awaited them.

After becoming slaves they didn’t expect any brilliance or glory in their lives; just surviving would be enough.

However, although this abyssal before them seemed ferocious, he had still stopped the iron claw demon from striking their bodies. He shouldn’t be some cruel pervert, right…?

As the two young girls were thinking like this, they developed wild hopes of Lin Ming. They left the iron cage and followed behind him.

Lin Ming didn’t speak. As they walked forwards, every time he saw a young girl in a cage he would only ask what their price was and then buy them up.

Later, Lin Ming didn’t ask for their price. When he saw one he bought one, as the clear prices of these slaves were listed on their cages.

Soon, the several hundred young girls from the iron cages had been bought up by Lin Ming.

Many of these young girls had pink whip marks marring their skin and their clothes were torn in many places. With their appearance, it was easy to take pity on them.

The succubus demon behind Lin Ming was already ecstatic. She didn’t know why Lin Ming was in such a haughty mood to buy so many slaves at once. But, she didn’t have any interest in finding out the reason, as she would earn money all the same.

The commission she would earn from this customer today would be the same as what she earned in several years.

For all the slaves that Lin Ming bought, he would branch out a part of his soul force to enter their spiritual seas and refine the slave seals there.

Like this, these slaves were turned over to Lin Ming for him to control. As for the slave seals, the array formation spells that would cause the slaves to instantly die were also lifted.

The Demon Association was a merchant organization that heavily relied on word of mouth. They certainly wouldn’t add such spells on goods they sold that would make their customers feel ill.

Slave after slave was rescued. Afterwards, Lin Ming didn’t even speak. With a wave of his hand the succubus demon would cheerfully laugh and take away the slaves.

The several hundred ancient race slaves that were training on the celestial mountain, both men and women, were all bought by Lin Ming.

The flowery fairy maidens in the medicinal garden and the common slaves there were also bought by Lin Ming.

Following that, from the various halls, residences, pavilions, towers, alchemy rooms, all the male and female slaves that one could see were bought up by Lin Ming.

Lin Ming welcomed all without reserve. Sometimes, he didn’t even glance at them. Finally he waited in place and all the slaves in the slave market walked towards him, whereupon he received them all.

Such a bold approach even alarmed the City Lord of Black Sand City; he was a peak Empyrean of the Demon Association.

This Demon Association City Lord commanded Black Sand City. Now, he came to personally greet Lin Ming.

Lin Ming tossed out more and more demon crystals. Soon he started to lack funds.

Fortunately for him, by this time almost all the slaves had been bought up by him. He placed them all into Primordius Heavenly Palace.

At this time, Primordius Heavenly Palace had its appearance changed by the Ancient Elysium Seal and it now looked like one of the dark fortresses that abyssals liked to ride. It was covered all over in cruel and demonic bone spikes.

After a purchasing session of nearly eight hours, the last of the ancient race slaves were sent to Primordius Heavenly Palace by Lin Ming. Primordius Heavenly Palace then flew away. Lin Ming watched as it broke through the void and vanished into space. Slowly, his face turned cold.

He had already paid the abyssal crystals. These crystals were held in the hand of the Empyrean level abyssal before him, who was also the City Lord of Black Sand City.

The Black Sand City Lord also had a royal bloodline and he was much taller than Lin Ming. At this time, he was smiling as he looked at Lin Ming. “Sir is truly bold and refreshing. For all the slaves that sir bought, we have already accounted a 5% discount for you. Next time you can place an order and we can personally prepare your request to create suitable slaves!”

As the abyssal spoke, he clapped his hands and ordered a banquet to see off Lin Ming. Then, he looked at Lin Ming and said, “I wonder if you have any other requests you would like to make?”

Lin Ming looked at the Black Sand City Lord with indifference. He slowly said, “I have one more request, and that is that… I don’t want to pay anything.”

Lin Ming’s tone was casual, as if he were speaking of minor matters.

“Mm?” The Black Sand City Lord’s face stiffened, as if he hadn’t clearly heard what Lin Ming just said.

“I said that I want you to give me all your demon crystals.”

Lin Ming spoke, clearly and unhurriedly, his eyes blazing as he stared at the Black Sand City Lord.

The Black Sand City Lord’s complexion darkened. But, he still retained a friendly tone. “Are you making a joke here? This joke isn’t funny; the slaves have already been taken away by you.”

“My apologies, but this is not a joke…” As Lin Ming spoke, killing intent flashed in his eyes.

Chapter 2100 – Stormy Assault

The moment the waves broke, Lin Ming’s strength suddenly rose to a new level. Without a doubt, he had been hiding his strength all this time.

“You… just who are you?”

The abyssal Elder’s face lit up with murderous intent, his appearance becoming more ferocious. He faintly felt that Lin Ming had intentionally lured him here. Above the void sea, one of the greatest characteristics of this place was that time and space were mixed up in a chaotic jumble, and it was hard for the outside world to discover just what was occurring within. This also meant that if there was a fight here, it would be difficult for anyone outside to come to the rescue.

Shua –

A gray force field came shrouding down, completely covering the surrounding space.

It was Lin Ming’s grandmist space. This force field could easily prevent the abyssal Elder from activating a great void shift. In fact, beneath Lin Ming’s all-out onslaught, even if there was not a force field here it would basically be impossible for the abyssal Elder to find a moment of piece to lock onto new space coordinates and traverse the void sea with a great void shift.

The abyssal Elder’s complexion darkened as he felt Lin Ming’s force field. “What influence are you from? Since when have totem level influences become such sneaky cowards! Are there more abyssals here? Call them all out!”

The abyssal Elder radiated his sense outwards, watching for any possible sneak attack. Although Lin Ming had suddenly erupted with a great strength, he still didn’t think that Lin Ming would be the only one here in this trap that was set up for him.

The truth was that for the high level Elders of the Demon Association, being encircled and killed was nearly impossible. This was because even in the Dark Abyss there were only several influences capable of cutting down a True Divinity level Elder. As for the Demon Association, their relationships with these other influences weren’t antagonistic to the degree that these influences would decide to kill a True Divinity level Elder.

But if it wasn’t a trap set by a great influence, it coming from a personal grudge was even more impossible.

This abyssal Elder had long since killed off almost all his personal enemies. Even if there were a few fish that managed to escape his net, these simply weren’t characters that the abyssal Elder would bother to remember, much less be capable of encircling and killing him.

Thus, True Divinity level abyssals that attached themselves to large influences were nearly without any enemies in the Dark Abyss. This was also the reason why this abyssal Elder chased Lin Ming while throwing caution to the wind.

However, exceptions always existed in reality. The abyssal Elder began to understand that all the events that occurred in Black Sand City had been targeting him from the start, and the Black Sand City Lord that died was merely a cover for luring him out.

However, the abyssal Elder didn’t think that there wouldn’t be anyone rushing out from hiding spots. Instead it was only Lin Ming who would attack.

At this instant, the skies suddenly darkened. Nine sparkling stars appeared high in the air. They rose up from behind Lin Ming, six of them radiating infinite divine light as they shined upon his six Dao Palaces.

Bang!

The sea exploded, issuing a savage war song. Lin Ming’s spear swept up mountain-like waves as he thrust towards the abyssal Elder’s throat!

“This is…”

The abyssal Elder’s heart shook. He had an extraordinary level of experience and he could see that the moves Lin Ming used didn’t utilize the Laws of abyssals. Rather, this seemed to be… the 33 Heavenly Daos!

An abyssal demon could use the 33 Heavenly Daos? Was this even possible?

The abyssal Elder didn’t have any time to further think about this. By now, the Black Dragon Spear had already pierced right in front of him. The shining spear light was like a blazing divine light, blinding to the eyes!

The abyssal Elder emitted a guttural roar. His joints emitted explosive crackling sounds as he clenched his hand into a fist and punched out.

Bang!

This fist was like a collapsing world, pressing down upon the Black Dragon Spear!

Zi zi zi - !

The Black Dragon Spear bent like a full moon. A massive wave of energy gushed out, forming a monstrous tsunami that swept over the world!

The force of this blow left the abyssal Elder flustered. A corner of the scales on his fist had shattered and blood flowed out.

Whoosh!

The abyssal Elder was sent flying backwards like a meteor, his face one of stunned astonishment.

“Who are you!?”

He thought that Lin Ming was someone who came from another one of the six totem level influences and wanted to harm the Demon Association, but Lin Ming revealing the Laws of the 33 Heavens left him feeling shocked and fearful.

It was nearly impossible for an abyssal to study the 33 Heavenly Daos. Compared to a saint cultivating the Nine Divine Shifts or a human cultivating the saint race’s body transformation technique, the difficulty was over ten times greater!

But Lin Ming simply didn’t give this abyssal Elder any time to think. He rushed out once more, the Black Dragon Spear bravely blazing forwards, thrusting straight towards all the abyssal Elder’s vital points!

“Damn it!”

The abyssal Elder was incensed. He slashed out his claws and 10,000 claw lights wove into a giant net of light that split open the skies.

Rumble rumble rumble!

The abyssal Elder brutally collided with Lin Ming. As a True Divinity level abyssal, his mortal bodily strength approached that of Astral Vault God King and his scales granted him a defensive ability no worse!

However, Lin Ming’s strength was no longer what it was in the past. If he were to fight Astral Vault God King as he was now, he could easily defeat him in direct combat.

Bang!

In that moment, an Asura war god phantom appeared behind Lin Ming. The giant Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel came smashing down, grinding away the abyssal Elder’s claw lights.

Lin Ming took this chance to move forwards. Space lost all meaning beneath his Laws. The Black Dragon Spear snuck out like a viper, diagonally sweeping towards the abyssal Elder’s ribs at a tricky angle.

The lower rib was not a vital point on the abyssal Elder’s body, but it was an extremely deadly attack point. This was because the abyssal Elder’s defenses were mostly focused on his head, neck, and areas above his lungs and heart. It wasn’t easy to attack him under his ribs, but this was also the area where he was most vulnerable to injury.

Lin Ming’s angle of attack could be called extremely cunning, completely surpassing the abyssal Elder’s expectations.

This spear was fast and ruthless; there was no time to dodge!

Ka!

Protective demon power exploded. Scales were torn open and blood shot out!

A foot-long gash opened up on the abyssal Elder’s chest and his body was sent tumbling away!

Although the wound wasn’t deep, the moment that the Black Dragon Spear tore open the abyssal Elder, a dark and sinister energy broke into his body, hurtling straight towards the heart and lungs!

“Just who…”

The abyssal Elder was shocked beyond compare. He summoned demon power to forcefully diffuse Lin Ming’s energy strike, but as he looked at Lin Ming his face was still covered in disbelief. This enemy’s strength was clearly above his own and yet his cultivation was clearly only at the Empyrean realm!

Lin Ming didn’t give his opponent any chance to catch a breath. As his spear thrust out, another Lin Ming flew out from within his body!

This Lin Ming wore black clothes – he was Lin Ming’s essence energy avatar, the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone!

The black-clothed Lin Ming also grasped a spear. The beautiful spear drew a killing circle through the air, the spear point coming down in a deadly arc, the end point being the abyssal Elder’s neck!

What!?

The abyssal Elder’s pupils shrank. Lin Ming’s Essence Spirit Embryo Stone avatar had no ability to turn into the form of an abyssal, thus it retained Lin Ming’s original appearance: that of a human from the 33 Heavens!

Before this, the abyssal Elder simply didn’t understand why Lin Ming understood the Laws of the 33 Heavens, and Lin Ming’s onslaught of attacks was so fierce and wild that he didn’t have the time to think about this. But now that he saw a human of the 33 Heavens emerge from Lin Ming’s body, he suddenly realized what was occurring.

“You aren’t an abyssal demon at all!”

The abyssal Elder’s eyes turned blood red. Still, he couldn’t figure out why he sensed the purest abyssal bloodline pulsing from Lin Ming’s body.

But in a mere instant he no longer had the luxury to ponder this. The Essence Spirit Embryo Stone’s spear already came cutting toward his neck!

Kacha!

In this crucial moment, the abyssal Elder opened his alligator-wide jaws and bit down on the spear!

The grinding of metal against metal pained the ears.

However, Lin Ming’s attacks were like a storm, a barrage that came without end. At this time, a purple-clothed Lin Ming and a blue-clothed Lin Ming also rushed out from his body. These were Lin Ming’s soul forging avatar and essence gathering avatar!

A sharp spiritual sword shot out from between the purple-clothed Lin Ming’s eyebrows, shooting straight into the abyssal Elder’s spiritual sea.

And at this time, the blue-clothed Lin Ming grasped a short lance and swept towards the area beneath the abyssal Elder’s ribs. This attack point was exactly where the abyssal Elder had been wounded just a moment ago. This was an attack to add injury upon injuries!

“You!”

The abyssal Elder’s pupils shrank. These mighty and swift attacks rained down on him like hail and it was no longer possible for him to dodge. Against two attacks that came crashing down on him at the same time, he could only block one.

Without any consideration, the abyssal Elder instinctively formed a protective demon barrier in his spiritual sea to guard against the purple-clothed Lin Ming’s soul attack!

When it came to abyssals, their mental and spiritual defenses were their weakest, and their mortal bodily defenses were their strongest.

In such a situation he certainly had to defend his spiritual sea first. Otherwise, if his soul was shaken it would be difficult to deal with anything that followed.

Kacha!

The spiritual sword crashed into the protective demon barrier and broke apart.

But at this time, the short lance struck the abyssal Elder’s body, causing him to vomit out a mouthful of black blood and sending his body flying away like a broken kite.

But while he tumbled away, the abyssal Elder’s eyes flashed with a sharp light. He borrowed the momentum of the strike to plunge away, rushing far away from Lin Ming!

He wanted to flee!

He knew that this was a trap purposefully aimed at him and he also knew that he couldn’t win in a fight, thus he had no intention of tangling himself up here with Lin Ming. Rather, he first thought of fleeing into the void sea. Then he could go to the high level figures of the Demon Association and report this shocking news to them… that there was a being of the 33 Heavens capable of disguising himself as an abyssal demon, and even simulate the accompanying abyssal aura! This was a disguise that not even a True Divinity was able to see through. This was information that was absolutely capable of placing the abyssals on guard against the 33 Heavens!

Moreover, what was most notable was that Lin Ming’s aura didn’t seem to be that of the ancient race descendants born in the Dark Abyss, but from one of the current races of the 33 Heavens – this information was even more important!

Of all the abyssals capable of stepping into the True Divinity realm, none were weak. Even though this abyssal Elder had been seriously wounded, he could still erupt with an incomparably terrifying strength for a short period of time.

And at this time, what lay in front of the abyssal Elder was the grandmist force field that blocked off the surrounding space!

Chapter 2105 – Ancient Eon Sect

Although the Dark Abyss was said to have 18 layers, the truth was that very few people had ever set foot in the 18th layer.

This was a forbidden land of the Dark Abyss.

In normal situations, only a few ancient sects would decide to go into the 18th layer to undergo some dark rituals or establish large-scale array formations.

But sometimes there would be True Divinity level abyssals that would enter the 18th layer to go into seclusion and complete a breakthrough.

As for other situations, the Dark Abyss’s 18th layer was nearly sealed off.

The Demon God’s Tomb was located in the 18th layer of the abyss.

The day of the Demon God’s Tomb opening approached.

And at this moment, in the layer above the 18th layer – the 17th layer where all the various large influences of the Dark Abyss were headquartered – they had already started aggressively making preparations for the Demon God’s Tomb.

Now, in the entire Dark Abyss, there were only two ceremonial rites books; it was far too small a number.

Only when a totem level abyssal died would a new ceremonial rites book be born. Moreover, some of them had been long since lost to time.

When the Demon God’s Tomb opened, a massive number of higher abyssals would enter. Most of them ventured in for other lucky chances, but if a ceremonial rites book were to be placed in front of them, any single one of them would be tempted.

Like this, the struggle for a ceremonial rites book would stir up a storm of blood and fire. Thus those sects that possessed a book began to form unions.

As for whether or not there would be unrest in the unions due to the existence of benefits, this was something that was temporarily put aside for later consideration. This was because in a situation where there was a common enemy, the influences in a union would first annihilate this common enemy before going back to competing for internal interests.

Deep King Road was one of the influences capable of organizing such a union. The reason they were able to do this was because in the Dark Abyss, Deep King Road was one of the two strongest totem level influences. Its leader was a totem level abyssal – Deep.

Moreover, Deep King Road controlled a ceremonial rites book!

Any abyssal that held a ceremonial rites book would surely become the target of everyone else. If one lacked ability, no one would dare to hold something that was both a sweet and tempting treat and also a bomb at the same time. Thus, when the Demon God’s Tomb opened, the ceremonial rites books would be in the hands of the great influences with the deepest background and the books themselves would be given to the strongest abyssal demons and also the ones with the greatest potential.

There were many influences that wished to attach themselves to Deep King Road, of which two were even totem level influences.

Although they were totem level influences, the disparity between them was enormous. This was because some totem level abyssals had perished or gone missing while others were alive.

In fact, strictly speaking, only influences that had a totem level abyssal could be called true totem level influences.

And a totem level influence that didn’t have a totem level abyssal could only be called a false totem level influence.

The Ancient Eon Sect was one such false totem level influence.

The leader of the Ancient Eon Sect was Eon, but Eon had already died. Even the ceremonial rite book that belonged to Eon had gone missing. Because of this, the Ancient Eon Sect inevitably began to decline.

A billion years ago, several amazingly outstanding abyssals had appeared in the Ancient Eon Sect and this rejuvenated it. At its height the Ancient Eon Sect stood in the middle of the six great totem level influences. However, 200 million years ago, these outstanding abyssals began to perish one after another, and the Ancient Eon Sect declined once more.

It was as if their destiny had come to an end.

Moreover, this decline was even more dramatic than the last. Now the Ancient Eon Sect had internally split into several factions, and each faction was controlled by one to two True Divinity Elders.

These factions did not have peaceful relations with each other and they even struggled against one another. If the Ancient Eon Sect were to disintegrate, no one knew whether these factions would be annexed by other influences or if they would remain independent.

The current Ancient Eon Sect could be called an alliance, an alliance that was in great disarray and lacked any semblance of unity. After another long period of time, dissolution or destruction was a high possibility.

On this day, the Ancient Eon Sect was discussing matters of opening the Demon God’s Tomb.

The Ancient Eon Sect’s True Divinity level abyssal Elders were discussing the situation in the main hall. The reason the Ancient Eon Sect was able to persist until now and still maintain their reputation as one of the six totem level influences, no matter how precarious a situation they were in, was all because this group of True Divinity level abyssal Elders supported the sect.

However, if this group of Elders were to die of old age, it was unknown whether or not a new generation of True Divinity Elders could be formed. This was the most dangerous time for the Ancient Eon Sect.

Now, the Ancient Eon Sect was discussing whether they should attach themselves to Deep King Road, to what degree they should attach themselves, and how the benefits should be assigned.

Only in the face of something as important as the opening of the Demon God’s Tomb would the various Great Elders put down their prejudices and maintain a sense of unity.

And at this time, an abyssal disciple arrived in the meeting hall. He hurriedly said, “Reporting to the Elders, there is a royal abyssal that wishes… wishes to join the Council of Elders and become an Elder… moreover, they wish to obtain one of the spots to enter the Demon God’s Tomb from our Ancient Eon Sect…”

As the many Elders in the meeting hall heard this news, all of them were shocked. Strange and wonderful expressions crossed their faces. They never thought that something so absurd would still be reported to them.

In particular, this conference of Elders was convened to discuss important business, and outside disturbance wasn’t allowed.

Without waiting for these Elders to yell at him, the abyssal disciple hesitantly said, “The sect branch also reported something else. It seems that this royal abyssal… possesses… the long-missing ‘Book of Eon’.

In the minds of the abyssals, the six ceremonial rites books corresponded to the totem level abyssal they were associated with. For instance, the Book of Eon, the Book of Famine, the Book of Evil, and so forth.

“What did you say!?”

Hearing the name of the ‘Book of Eon’, the Elders in the meeting hall were suddenly excited. Some of them stood up where they were.

“Where is he? Is this information true?”

The Book of Eon had been missing for far too long and no one knew where it was. And today, it had suddenly appeared in the hands of a royal abyssal; how could the Ancient Eon Sect not be shocked?

It was the holy treasure of their Ancient Eon Sect! The Book of Eon was no different from Eon itself being present!

There were even some people that believed the reason the Ancient Eon Sect went into decline was because the Book of Eon had gone missing. With the holy treasure of their sect gone, it was natural for them to lose their destiny.

“He is currently waiting in the main hall of the branch sect. It also seems he has the strength of an upper Empyrean so the branch sect cannot do anything to him. He hasn’t taken out the Book of Eon, so we do not know whether or not this information is true…”

Several abyssal Elders glanced at each other as they heard this and then set out to leave.

“Which branch division is it? Let’s go take a look now!”

To the Ancient Eon Sect, an upper Empyrean level abyssal wasn’t anything at all. But, if they possessed the Book of Eon, that was a completely different matter.

Within the entire Ancient Eon Sect, there was not a single abyssal demon that dared to disrespect the Book of Eon in the least.

The person that possessed the Book of Eon was also the voice of Eon.

Now, the question was, once they confirmed the existence of the Book of Eon, what should they do then?

…..

At this time, tens of thousands of miles away from the Ancient Eon Sect’s headquarters at a branch division, Lin Ming stood in the main hall. He had become the incarnation of an abyssal demon. From the moment that he had opened the seventh Dao Palace, three years had passed.

In these three years Lin Ming had successfully consolidated his boundary of the Twofold Dao Palace. However, the late Empyrean realm continued to elude him.

During this time, Mo Eversnow also successfully launched a surprise attack against Black Sand City. After her rapid strike she quickly withdrew without any hesitation at all. She managed to kill some higher abyssals and also take away a massive amount of wealth that the Demon Association had accumulated in Black Sand City.

For some time afterwards, the Ancient God rebel army ceased all activities.

Mo Eversnow knew when to stop. This was because she knew that the surprise attack on Black Sand City had nearly touched the Demon Association’s bottom line.

If the Demon Association was truly serious then they would send out seven or eight True Divinity Elders to complete a full search of the entire 12th layer. Like this, they would certainly be able to find the Ancient God rebel army.

The day that happened would be the apocalypse of the Ancient God rebel army. Thus, the choice they could make was to rest up and build their strength. When the Demon God’s Tomb opened up the Demon Association would be too preoccupied to deal with the Ancient God rebel army. At that time, the resistance could go all-out once more.

Lin Ming paced around in the main hall, silently looking upon a sculpture situated in it. This was a statue of an incredibly fierce demon.

The abyssal demons took Demon as their god and religion. They all considered themselves faithful subjects of Demon.

In the high abyssal language, the character ‘Demon’ was written with the most mysterious and most source Law runes. It represented the meaning of unsurpassed reverence.

Lin Ming gazed at this statue and quietly waited for the Elders of the Ancient Eon Sect to arrive.

Chapter 2108 – Undercurrents

As Lin Ming followed the many Elders to the Ancient Eon Sect Headquarters, news that another Elder was joining the Council of Elders rapidly spread through the entire sect.

These people were all incredibly curious; just who was this new Elder and where had he come from?

However, they soon discovered that this new Elder was not a True Divinity level abyssal but an upper Empyrean.

For a time, the entire Ancient Eon Sect was thrown into an uproar.

It had to be known that within the Ancient Eon Sect, an Elder had extraordinary status. They possessed the authority to directly control the wealth of the sect, they could freely read through any rare cultivation methods, and they could even perceive the abyssal Laws and demon crystal left behind by Eon.

Such privileges left one simmering with envy!

In particular, when it came to perceiving the Laws left behind by Eon, there were simply far too many disciples in the Ancient Eon Sect that wished to do so. Because of this, it was nearly impossible to obtain the chance to perceive the Laws of Eon. According to the rules of the Ancient Eon Sect, only those who obtained accomplished great deeds and obtained enough sect points would be able to exchange them for a chance to meditate on Eon’s Laws.

But the Elders weren’t bound by such limits. Even if they had zero contribution points they could perceive these Laws whenever they wished.

Many high level characters within the Ancient Eon Sect dreamed of becoming an Elder.

But there was one condition to become an Elder. That was… one had to be a True Divinity level abyssal.

The disparity between an Empyrean abyssal and a True Divinity abyssal was far too great. To many Empyrean level abyssals, this was a moat that could not be crossed. Thus, their dreams of becoming an Elder could only remain dreams.

But now an upper Empyrean level abyssal had somehow magically become an Elder, and this newcomer would be apportioned some of the time allowed to perceive Eon’s Laws. How could anyone be convinced by this?

Suddenly, from all through the Ancient Eon Sect, both high and low, many disciples were unhappy.

Because the Council of Elders had yet to announce that the Book of Eon had been found, the disciples didn’t know why Lin Ming was able to become an Elder.

On almost the second day since Lin Ming entered the Ancient Eon Sect, many of the sect’s Empyrean level abyssals desired to challenge him.

Compared to the humans of the 33 Heavens, the abyssals preferred to be direct and find solutions to problems through violence. This was a world where strength was revered above all, and if they didn’t like what they saw they would change it with their own strength.

Within the Ancient Eon Sect, where would there be Empyrean level abyssals that dared to challenge an Elder?

But, the situation was different if that Elder was only an upper Empyrean level abyssal.

If their strength was greater and their cultivation was higher, how come Lin Ming could become an Elder but they couldn’t?

This was the thought process of the overwhelming majority of Empyrean level abyssals. Several Empyrean abyssals had already cultivated to the peak Empyrean realm, moreover, they were even outstanding existences amongst peak Empyreans. In the Ancient Eon Sect their status was only inferior to the Council of Elders’.

They had been in the sect for so many years and had always coveted the position of Elder. Yet now, some outsider had ridden above their heads to become one, so these people certainly weren’t happy about these events. These people all had loud voices and a great deal of power. Driven by them, the sounds of discontent grew louder and louder in the Ancient Eon Sect.

Now some peak Empyrean level abyssals and upper Empyrean level abyssals, and even middle Empyrean level abyssals, requested to challenge Lin Ming. Their momentum was far too great and their requests made it to the Council of Elders.

But the Council of Elders didn’t do anything about this at all. They had no obligation to help Lin Ming in this matter, and as they saw this situation, some of them even gloated over it.

If one wished to become an Elder with an upper Empyrean cultivation, then they would naturally have to face the troubles that followed it.

If Lin Ming were to walk through the Ancient Eon Sect in the future, one could expect that there would be higher abyssals challenging him from all corners.

In truth, besides being able to examine some of the internal texts in the Ancient Eon Sect, Lin Ming’s title as Elder gave him no true power or prestige.

However… Lin Ming had no plan to walk through the Ancient Eon Sect to begin with, and he simply turned a blind eye to all his challengers. As soon as he entered the Ancient Eon Sect, he went into seclusion and started to perceive the Law crystal left behind by Eon.

This left many Empyrean level abyssals even more dissatisfied; they felt that Lin Ming was timid, scared of them.

However, since Lin Ming was in seclusion, they naturally couldn’t do anything against him. They became even louder.

Seeing this situation, several Elders of the Ancient Eon Sect gathered in the Assembly Hall.

“Elder Eon God, about this matter concerning the Book of Eon, what do you plan on doing? Are you really planning to allow this boy to take the book into the Demon God’s Tomb?”

Within the hall at the highest heights of the Ancient Eon Sect, an Elder suddenly asked.

Every Elder of the Ancient Eon Sect had their own title, a title that started with ‘Eon’. But, there was only one who could be called Elder Eon God – this was the Ancient Eon Sect’s Great Elder.

The Ancient Eon Sect had no Sect Master. According to traditions of totem level influences, the Sect Master of a totem level influence was the totem level abyssal itself.

Now that Eon had died, the seat of Sect Master had been empty for all these years.

“This Ninth Elder isn’t even at the True Divinity realm. Even if he doesn’t bring the Book of Eon with him, the chances of him surviving the Demon God’s Tomb are low to begin with. And if he were to bring the Book of Eon with him, he would absolutely be seeking death!”

Another Elder said. The Ninth Elder he referred to was Lin Ming.

When Lin Ming entered the Council of Elders, he was ranked ninth; this was also the last rank. He didn’t have a title and the Council of Elders didn’t even know his name nor could they be bothered to find out.

Thus, they simply called Lin Ming the Ninth Elder.

An upper Empyrean level abyssal wanted to take a ceremonial rites book into the Demon God’s Tomb. In this situation, any logically-thinking abyssal would believe he would die without a doubt.

Another Elder said, “We’ve obtained the Book of Eon after so much difficulty; we cannot lose it again.”

To the Ancient Eon Sect, the Book of Eon was an object required to stabilize their sect’s destiny. If the Book of Eon were to be wrested away by someone after being taken into the Demon God’s Tomb, then no one would feel comfortable about this.

Facing the questions of so many Elders, the Great Elder remained silent.

The Great Elder thought for a moment, then said, “Have you all thought about why the Ninth Elder wishes to bring the Book of Eon into the Demon God’s Tomb, what his goal is?”

The Great Elder’s words caused the rapid discussions to slow down. In truth, they had also thought of this question but they just couldn’t figure out why.

The Great Elder continued to say, “The Ninth Elder should know that with his strength alone, it should be impossible for him to protect the Book of Eon from others. In this world there are always arrogant and conceited individuals in all generations, but there shouldn’t be anyone arrogant to such a degree. Rather, this would be stupid, and the Ninth Elder isn’t stupid at all. Thus he should have another goal in mind.”

As the Great Elder finished speaking, another Elder said, “No matter what his goal is, it isn’t anything good for us.”

“That is true. The Ninth Elder doesn’t come from our Ancient Eon Sect so it is impossible for him to do anything for our Ancient Eon Sect. He should only be using us for our asylum and being able to provide him with a spot to enter the Demon God’s Tomb safely, all so that he can obtain his own benefits. So, I don’t plan on letting him succeed…”

The Great Elder slowly said. A cold light shimmered in his faint red eyes.

This old abyssal was like a snake lying in the grass, flicking out its tongue and staring at its prey.

“Or, how about we just kill him now. Since the disciples who know about this have been sealed away by us, matters concerning the Book of Eon will also be absolutely confidential! If we kill him now and take away the Book of Eon, this would be the best and most simple plan!”

A younger Elder said. His Elder title was Eon Light and he was eighth amongst the Elders. He was the youngest of them but also possessed the greatest potential.

He had his own ambitions. He even wanted to take the Book of Eon and bring it into the Demon God’s Tomb himself.

There were no rules in the cycle by which the Demon God’s Tomb opened. Sometimes the Demon God’s Tomb would open after several tens of millions of years, and sometimes it wouldn’t even open once in a billion years.

If he missed this chance, there was no guarantee that he would be able to take the Book of Eon into the Demon God’s Tomb in the future.

The Great Elder faintly looked at Eon Light, a meaningful look in his eyes.

Eon Light’s stiffened and no longer spoke.

The Great Elder said, “The Book of Eon is connected with the influence of our totem level influence. This is not a rumor, but the truth. We cannot move against the Ninth Elder. Whether it is killing him ourselves or hiring someone to kill him, neither choice is one we can make. But, while we cannot move against him in that manner, we can still use some external conditions so that he cannot enter the Demon God’s Tomb.”

The Great Elder gently pressed down on the stone chair he sat on. He didn’t use any force, just gently brushed it, but that chair made of timeless god stone seemed to experience the weathering of countless years as it turned to black dust and completely vanished…

Chapter 2114 – Meeting

In Deep King Road’s towering pagoda above the wild plains, there were totem poles stabbed into the earth, encircling a demon force field that extended outwards in a radius of 10,000 miles.

This force field was filled with thick demonic aura, as if some ancient demon were slumbering here.

The disciples of every influence only had to approach this force field to feel a massive pressure.

This pressure was mixed with a mighty killing intent. Unless a martial artist was at the World King level or above, it was simply impossible to enter.

“This is Deep King Road’s deep king force field. It is Deep King Road’s great guardian array formation. It was established 10 billion years ago, and for the last 10 billion years Deep King Road has paid a great price to keep it maintained with blood sacrifices so that it can retain its rank as an extreme True Divinity level array formation. If a True Divinity level abyssal were to enter this array formation they would be restricted beneath it.”

Before entering the deep king force field, the Ancient Eon Sect’s Great Elder began explaining what it was.

Lin Ming looked at the totem poles that surrounded the great array formation. These totem poles weren’t inscribed with runes, but had images of all sorts of ancient abyssals carved into them. The images of these demons inherently contained the highest truths of the abyssal Laws, and the aura that overflowed from them left one gasping for breath.

Upon truly stepping into the force field, Lin Ming could feel his own strength be suppressed a great deal. Whether it was mobilizing the energy within his body or utilizing the Laws of the world, everything was affected by the invisible suppression of the force field.

If Lin Ming wished to rid himself of this suppression then he could only break open the force field. But, the current Lin Ming didn’t possess even the strength to do this.

“Everyone’s strength is suppressed so the battle is fair. This is to prevent Deep King Road Headquarters from being damaged due to the great destruction that could occur when True Divinity level abyssals fight.”

Lin Ming watched as more and more abyssal influences entered the force field. This force field was like a giant cage, swallowing all those who entered.

The group from the Ancient Eon Sect arrived at their assigned region. And at a place not too far away from them, another crowd of higher abyssals had already arrived.

“Those are the abyssals from Nine Nether Palace.” Eon Light said from beside Elder Eon God, his voice low as he glanced over the several Elders of Nine Nether Palace.

The many abyssal disciples of Nine Nether Palace also saw the Ancient Eon Sect arrive.

Nine Nether Palace and the Ancient Eon Sect needed to join forces to resist Deep King Road. But at the same time, they were also fellow competitors.

“Haha, Elder Eon God, it seems that your Ancient Eon Sect has trained many masters in preparation for today!”

The one leading Nine Nether Palace was an old abyssal. He stood eight feet high and had an emaciated figure. His body was like a bamboo pole with a wooden head attached to one end. As his eight eyes looked at Lin Ming, all Lin Ming felt was disgust at this odd and ugly-looking creature.

This old abyssal was the Great Elder of Nine Nether Palace. Behind him were three relatively young abyssal Elders who had clearly reached the True Divinity realm.

It was obvious that these three abyssal Elders were the ones sent out by Nine Nether Palace and would also be the ones participating in the competition.

When competitors met, sparks would fly. On the side of the Ancient Eon Sect, as Eon Light, Eon Moon, and Eon Fire stared at the three abyssal Elders from Nine Nether Road, a fighting intent sparked in their eyes.

The three abyssal Elders of Nine Nether Palace were different from those of the Ancient Eon Sect. The three Elders of the Ancient Eon Sect were relatively similar in strength, but in Nine Nether Palace, the difference in strength between their three Elders was extremely great. A young Elder named Nether Nihility was the strongest, another was in the middle, and another was the weakest, who was only brought here to make up for numbers.

“Mortals propose and the heavens dispose. All I can do as I wait is prepare as much as I can!” Elder Eon God slowly spoke as he bowed.

“Haha, Elder Eon God is too humble. I heard that not only does your Ancient Eon Sect have high hopes for the Demon God’s Tomb, but you even want to propose marriage and have one of your sect Elders marry Deep King Road’s Holy Demoness. Such courage is something that leaves my Nine Nether Palace quaking in shame at our own inferiority!”

The voice of Nine Nether Palace’s Grand Elder echoed in the air, so boisterous that one couldn’t tell if it was mockery or praise. However, no matter what thoughts he had in his heart it wasn’t important.

After Nine Nether Palace’s Great Elder mentioned marriage, the three young Elders from the Ancient Eon Sect felt uncomfortable; they were already cursing Lin Ming in their hearts.

However, Elder Eon God retained his composure. He slowly said, “Deep King Road’s Holy Demoness has informed the world thousands of years ago that any abyssal demon, as long as they can defeat her at the same boundary, may marry her. This is common knowledge and everyone is free to participate. Our Ancient Eon Sect also wishes to try our luck, so this is far from any sort of courage. If we lose then we lose, so what does it matter?”

Elder Eon God’s reply not only lifted the awkward atmosphere but also opened an escape route for himself later. The Great Elder of Nine Nether Palace laughed, but just as he was about to say something, sounds began to rise in the distance, ancient demonic sounds that reverberated in the void.

As the demonic sounds rose up, the originally bustling scene suddenly quieted down. Everyone looked over and they could see that in the far off void, a massive black boat cut into the deep king force field like waves in water as it drove forwards.

Atop the deck of the bone boat stood 10 higher abyssals. These 10 higher abyssals all had cultivations at the True Divinity realm!

For an influence to suddenly appear with 10 True Divinity level abyssals, the only one that had the background to do this was Deep King Road.

“It’s the Elders of Deep King Road!”

Someone quietly said, suppressing their voice. Facing Deep King Road, all of the influences here felt a great pressure.

“What a terrifying aura domain. I heard that Deep King Road has over 20 True Divinity level abyssals; that is much more than Nine Nether Palace and the Ancient Eon Sect combined!”

As Lin Ming heard the discussions of some disciples from smaller influences, he felt a bit wistful.

In the Dark Abyss, if the True Divinity level abyssals of the six totem level influences were added up then there would be over 80 of them. And there were also True Divinity level abyssals that were in sects other than the six totem level influences, or perhaps they were hidden somewhere else. But altogether, there was at least a hundred True Divinity level abyssals in the Dark Abyss.

This was a terrifying number. This was because in the 33 Heavens, when it came to martial artists that possessed a combat strength at the True Divinity level, even if Lin Ming included himself there was only 11-12 of them.

Compared to the Dark Abyss, this was a difference over 10 times greater. If it weren’t for the channel that connected the Dark Abyss to the 33 Heavens being blocked off, then perhaps the 33 Heavens would have already been swept away by the Dark Abyss.

Thinking of this, Lin Ming could also feel just how strong the Asura Road Master of 10 billion years past was. Of course in order for the ancient races of that era to defeat the abyssal demons, they had to pay a tragically deep price.

As Lin Ming thought of this, his heart suddenly shook and his pupils shrank.

At this moment he could see that above the bone boat stood the figure of a woman.

This woman wore black clothes. As she stood there she was like the source of all darkness in the universe. Where she stood, the Laws assembled themselves into lines that formed black flower petals which gently fluttered down in space, falling onto her clothes before slowly dissipating away…

Standing there, she was like a dark enchantress of the night. This woman was Deep King Road’s Holy Demoness!

Lin Ming sucked in a deep breath, his thoughts wildly tumbling in his mind. He could feel an inexplicably familiar bloodline connection from Deep King Road’s Holy Demoness. With this connection he could almost instantly confirm that the Deep King Road Holy Demoness he saw before him was the same as the Soul Empress of the 33 Heavens – Sheng Mei!

Lin Ming knew that when he was at the Sky Spill Planet where he had become one with Sheng Mei, Sheng Mei had left him her primordial yin and part of her source soul. It was also because of this that he could feel the faint connection between them.

At this time, it wasn’t just Lin Ming who saw Sheng Mei, but many other abyssals did too.

As Deep King Road’s Holy Demoness, Sheng Mei’s talent was without peer and her status was unreachable. Her temperament was as ephemeral as dust and her appearance far surpassed all others in the Dark Abyss. Such a proud daughter of heaven made the countless abyssals present drool with desire.

“So that’s Deep King Road’s Holy Demoness. Just seeing her once is better than hearing about her a hundred times!”

“That’s her. This time she will likely venture into the Demon God’s Tomb also. In terms of cultivation I heard she is already beginning to attack the True Divinity realm!”

“What horrifying talent. She’s probably only several tens of thousands of years old…”

Everyone started to discuss amongst themselves. With so many gazes on her body, Sheng Mei’s heart suddenly stirred. For a brief moment she felt something inexplicable, a strange feeling that passed over her gently and swiftly, one that she couldn’t touch her finger on. Inadvertently, she looked towards the direction of the Ancient Eon Sect.

Her eyes stopped upon a vigorous and robust abyssal, one who was covered with black scales and had two bone blades jutting out from his elbows.

Amongst the other higher abyssals this abyssal seemed common. But for some unknown reason, as Sheng Mei looked at him she couldn’t help but feel something faintly familiar…

Chapter 2115 – Choosing an Opponent

“Strange… I shouldn’t have seen him before…”

Sheng Mei faintly frowned. At this time, the current Lin Ming had already completely concealed his human aura.

Lin Ming’s true self was within the inner world of his demon avatar and his aura was completely isolated, thus Sheng Mei was unable to recognize him. However, because of some inexplicable intuition that couldn’t be explained, she was able to instinctively feel that Lin Ming was special.

As Lin Ming felt Sheng Mei’s gaze touch upon him, he suppressed his thoughts, restraining his emotions so that nothing showed.

He deeply hid his aura, not planning to reveal his status to Sheng Mei any time soon. This was because for him, the Dark Abyss was the lion’s den, and if his identity was exposed then the consequences would be inconceivable.

Therefore even though Lin Ming wanted to believe in Sheng Mei, who knew why she was in the Dark Abyss and what her goal was? Was she good or evil?

In this completely unsure situation, there was no way that Lin Ming could believe Sheng Mei. After all, in those events that occurred on the Sky Spill Planet 12,000 years ago, although Sheng Mei had saved him, everything that she had revealed to him caused him to feel complex emotions of attraction and opposition to this riddle-like woman, as even though he wanted to approach her he also wished to keep his distance from her.

Sheng Mei looked at Lin Ming for a moment and then turned away. She asked one of the abyssals following her, “That royal abyssal from the Ancient Eon Sect, who is he?”

“Reporting to Miss, he is the Ninth Elder who was just recently promoted by the Ancient Eon Sect. He is at the upper Empyrean realm so it’s a bit strange that is became an Elder, moreover…”

The abyssal follower looked at Sheng Mei as he spoke to here, hesitating for a moment.

“Moreover what?”

“Miss should know that during this competition, one of the Elders of the Ancient Eon Sect wishes to challenge Miss for marriage. And that challenger is this Ninth Elder.”

“Mm?”

Sheng Mei glanced at Lin Ming with surprise. She had heard about this but simply didn’t care, thus she never asked for information related to this challenger. But today, after seeing Lin Ming and hearing this so-called challenge again, a bizarre feeling rapidly flew through her thoughts.

“What is Miss thinking about?”

“Nothing.” Sheng Mei shook her head, no longer speaking.

This inexplicable flash of intuition left Sheng Mei confused. She racked her thoughts, carefully looking through her past memories for some abyssal demon whose image overlapped with Lin Ming.

However, she simply couldn’t find anything. She would never have imagined that this royal abyssal, whose bloodline had no problem no matter how much she investigated, would actually be a human…

“Everyone, let us not speak much nonsense here and directly start the battle! I will now announce the rules!”

After all the abyssal demons arrived, a tall and strong abyssal in dark gray metal armor flew up in the skies. Even though he didn’t pour any demon energy into his voice, his words still rang loud and clear amongst every present.

This tall and strong abyssal was an Elder of Deep King Road.

“Now, all abyssal demons who wish to participate in this competition, step into the center of the field!”

The tall and strong abyssal roared. On the side of the Ancient Eon Sect, the three young Elders flew out. Then, from Nine Nether Palace, Nether Nihility and the other Elders also flew out one after another.

Finally there were the Elders of Deep King Road.

All the influences were concerned about which six Elders Deep King Road would send out.

Many abyssals looked with wide eyes. They watched as a black beam of light came shooting down from the black bone boat that the group from Deep King Road had come in on.

From this beam of light, a horrifying abyssal aura swelled outwards.

These were the Elders of Deep King Road.

“Deep Child!”

The first Elder that flew down from Deep King Road caused everyone’s hearts to shake, because this Elder called Deep Child was at the middle True Divinity level.

Whether it was the Ancient Eon Sect or Nine Nether Palace, the young Elders or Elders in the prime of their youth that they sent out for this venture into the Demon God’s Tomb were all at the lower True Divinity level.

But, Deep King Road had already sent out a True Divinity level abyssal whose true potential was yet to be dug out. From this alone the disparity between the sects could be seen.

With the appearance of a single Deep Child, Nine Nether Palace and the Ancient Eon Sect’s momentum was all suppressed!

Fortunately, following that, the other candidates from Deep King Road were all at the lower True Divinity level.

“Deep Moon, Deep Glory, Deep Echo, Deep Solitary… mm?”

An abyssal familiar with the high level Elders of Deep King Road began to announce their names as they flew down. But when he came to the sixth person, he froze.

“Wait a moment, this is…”

“How could it be her!?”

As the abyssal demons saw a woman in black clothes come fluttering down from the skies, all of their eyes popped open. They never imagined that the sixth competition candidate would not be one of their Elders but actually the Holy Demoness!

“Deep King Road’s Holy Demoness! Is she going to compete?”

“But her cultivation has yet to reach the True Divinity level. Without having reached the True Divinity level can one challenge True Divinity abyssals!?”

The eyes of all abyssals focused on Sheng Mei. The aura that she exuded loudly declared that she had one foot in the threshold of True Divinity.

But, no matter how close one was to True Divinity, someone that wasn’t at True Divinity was someone that wasn’t at True Divinity. The gap between an Empyrean and a True Divinity was vast beyond compare, and for an Empyrean to fight a True Divinity was beyond difficult!

In the past, many influences already knew that Deep King Road’s Holy Demoness possessed formidable talent and that she was invincible among those at the same boundary. After all, no matter how many outstanding abyssals wished to dual cultivate with Deep King Road’s Holy Demoness, all of them were in the end mercilessly beaten to the ground.

But no matter how exaggerated the legends of Deep King Road’s Holy Demoness were, no one would have expected that on this day, she would be chosen to fight on behalf of Deep King Road!

Could she, at the limit of an Empyrean, now possess the ability to fight a True Divinity?

The abyssals present felt this all unbelievable. But, no one felt that Deep King Road’s Holy Demoness would come out and participate in this struggle for benefits of the Demon God’s Tomb if she didn’t have full confidence in her abilities. If she wasn’t then she would be far too stupid.

It had to be known that the Ancient Eon Sect and Nine Nether Palace had the ability to choose who their opponent was and could even repeat a challenge against someone. If the Holy Demoness was too weak then the Ancient Eon Sect and Nine Nether Palace’s six Elders could simply all choose her and win six matches like this.

This was a naturally impossible matter.

As the abyssals present realized this, their vision as they looked at Sheng Mei changed.

It turned to awe, reverence, jealousy, even obsession…

All sorts of complicated emotions filled the hearts of the abyssals present. And at this time, the host of this great competition spoke out and interrupted the thoughts of the crowd.

“We shall now begin. The Elders of the Ancient Eon Sect and Nine Nether Palace, you may now choose your opponents!”

As the host spoke, the Ancient Eon Sect and Nine Nether Palace immediately quieted down.

The choice of opponent was naturally extremely important.

In particular, due to the rules, Deep King Road’s Elders could be chosen multiple times. All six Elders could choose the weakest warrior of Deep King Road. As for the strongest, Deep Child, no one had to fight him.

But the key question here was which one of these six Elders of Deep King Road was the weakest?

Besides the obvious answer that was the basically invincible Deep Child, the Elders of the Ancient Eon Sect and Nine Nether Palace began to look over their possible opponents.

Between every opening of the Demon God’s Tomb there was a vast span of time. Thus, the warriors that every influence sent out would be different each time. In addition with Deep King Road’s tight intelligence security, it was simply impossible to know the depths of Deep King Road’s Elders.

The Elders of the Ancient Eon Sect and Nine Nether Palace could only make speculations based upon the auras and Law fluctuations of these higher abyssals, as well as using the intuition of a martial artist.

“Eon Light, have you chosen?”

On the Ancient Eon Sect’s side, the Great Elder asked out loud.

Eon Light pondered for a moment more. Then, a cold light flashed in his eyes. He finally looked at Sheng Mei and said, “I have chosen. I choose the Holy Demoness!”

Eon Light knew that Sheng Mei likely wasn’t weak and if she dared to come and compete then she naturally had hidden cards in her hands. But when compared to the other True Divinity level Elders, Sheng Mei gave off a slightly weaker feeling.

After all, most people who jumped ranks to fight were barely able to do so.

The Great Elder frowned but didn’t oppose. He turned to another Elder and asked, “Eon Fire, what about you?”

Eon Fire thought deeply for a moment. Then he said, “Although it doesn’t seem honorable, I plan on choosing the Holy Demoness also. She should be the weakest…”

Chapter 2123 – Demon Asura

On the Deep King Wheel, Lin Ming and Sheng Mei stood 200 feet apart from each other.

The two of them motionlessly stared at each other. Only the demon power that burned like blazing flames and icy fires upon their weapons reminded everyone just how intense the battle just now had been.

“You… just what are you…”

Sheng Mei’s frosty voice reverberated through the audience. She was well aware that it was impossible for a higher abyssal like Lin Ming to appear out of nowhere.

However, no matter whether it was this person’s abyssal bloodline, aura, techniques, or whatever else, she still couldn’t find any clues about him.

This abyssal gave off a strange feeling. He only calmly stood there but he was like a deep pool lying still in a mountain, an eternal proud son of heaven looking down upon the world with disdain, carrying with him an inexplicable and unknown invincible spirit.

Lin Ming remained silent. He only raised the Black Dragon Spear, the barrel shaft crackling with bone. At this moment the Black Dragon Spear in his hands seemed to become a snake made of black bone, containing an incomparably powerful strength as well as a cunning attack trajectory!

Lin Ming felt more and more desire for this battle. This enigmatic Sheng Mei was no different from a riddle and she had entangled herself in his life in countless ways. And she, for the last 10 billion years, was one of the proudest elites – whether it was in the Dark Abyss or the 33 Heavens. She was someone that could step on that supreme road to become a horrifying character like the Immortal Sovereign.

This was a match that was fated to be and it would begin today.

Lin Ming took a deep breath, his dark amber brown pupils slowly contracting. The power of demons formed a black snake around him that wildly weaved about.

At this time Lin Ming’s true self was sitting in his demon avatar’s inner world. Above his truer self, nine brilliant stars manifested; this was the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace!

Facing Sheng Mei, Lin Ming couldn’t switch out to his true body to fight nor could he openly use the Laws that were well known by Sheng Mei.

Otherwise, just relying on the intuitive sense of familiarity that Sheng Mei felt towards Lin Ming, as well the Laws that were unique to Lin Ming, how could she not guess his identity?

As the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace appeared, the strength of Lin Ming’s true self rapidly rose. All of this strength was constantly fused into his demon avatar to bolster it.

Woosh!

Lin Ming’s figure vanished in the void. With overwhelming potential he rushed towards Sheng Mei!

His demon body fused with his bone spear, forming a heaven-shattering and earth-sundering divine light!

After Lin Ming’s demon avatar was fused with the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, the intensity of his mortal body could compare with a True Divinity spirit treasure.

He thrust out his spear towards Sheng Mei, a billowing momentum following it that seemed as if it could pierce through the endless universe. The abyssal Laws interwove with the strength of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, spinning together like a river of stars and forming giant black stars that swirled atop the spear shaft.

This spear possessed an overwhelming potential and suffocating oppressive force. The surrounding abyssal disciples couldn’t help but tremble. They felt that this spear light contained a strength that could devour them whole and they started to retreat in panic. Even the complexions of many True Divinity abyssal Elders changed.

Facing such a powerful strike, Sheng Mei’s eyes burst out with brilliance once more. The dark wings on her back glowed with an icy metallic luster as demon runes bloomed on each one, light stars that floated atop them.

“Go!”

Dark wings soared upwards, rapidly folding in to directly welcome Lin Ming’s earth-striking blow.

Arrogant and filled with incomparable confidence, facing Lin Ming’s powerful attack, Sheng Mei only relied on her invincible dark angel wings to meet him.

Bang!

Dark wings collided with the blinding divine brilliance of Lin Ming’s spear light. Like two stars crashing together, billions of abyssal runes were annihilated as threads of abyssal Laws shattered!

This massive impact force caused the Deep King force field to violently rock yet again, as if it would tear apart.

As the totem poles that supported the force field had to withstand the pressure, 10,000 demonic spirits seemed to suddenly howl. Demon energy soared to the heavens as shadows rose up, as if a peerless ancient abyssal were reaching through the endless river of time to protect the force field.

War drums sounded like thunderbolts, humming in the air. An even more formidable demonic force field strength raged out to stabilize the Deep King force field.

However, Lin Ming’s attack hadn’t yet ended.

With a loud shout Lin Ming activated the power of the Asura blood in his demon avatar’s inner world. Thick scales covered his body and behind his true self, the phantom of an Asura war god emerged.

Within this war god phantom’s hands, three wheels slowly revolved like grinding pans.

This was power of the Asura Sutra.

Peng!

Peng!

Peng!

Three wheels shattered, turning into countless runes that fused into Lin Ming’s demon avatar’s body. All of this occurred within the demon avatar’s body so the many abyssals watching didn’t know.

At this moment, all these abyssals saw were the muscles of Lin Ming’s demon avatar crazily wriggle about. His joints released explosive crackling sounds and his towering body began to rise once more!

The bones and scales on Lin Ming’s body became harder and increasingly fierce. A pair of curved horns jutted out from his head.

Lin Ming’s demon avatar had turned into a ferocious Asura demon. The changes that appeared on his true self were minor, but after manifesting on his demon avatar’s body they became exaggeratedly terrifying.

Underneath the pressure of so much strength, many abyssals felt their eyes pop wide open.

“Higher abyssal body metamorphosis!”

The abyssal demons were similar to the saints in that certain clans amongst them could undergo body metamorphosis. After metamorphosizing, they would experience a rapid rise in all aspects of strength!

The truth was that body metamorphosis wasn’t strange, in particular higher abyssals with outstanding levels of talent. This shouldn’t have been enough to stir up any interest, but the crux of the issue here was that Lin Ming had already shown far too abnormal a performance just now. An upper Empyrean was able to fight a True Divinity level opponent to equally match with Sheng Mei.

And yet, Lin Ming even used body metamorphosis atop all of that!

“Heavens, this fellow is simply a monster!”

An abyssal Elder from a small influence said, his voice shaking. The current Lin Ming could no longer be described as being able to defeat a lower True Divinity; he might have the strength to fight against a peak lower True Divinity!

“Could he… really be able to defeat the Holy Demoness…?” The Ancient Eon Sect’s Elder Eon God whispered, his wizened face frozen in place.

If one defeated Deep King Road’s Holy Demoness then they would be able to obtain this number one elite of the Dark Abyss, someone that might even control the abyss in the future.

Lin Ming, Sheng Mei.

Both were proud children of heaven, and if they were to dual cultivate then their cultivation speed would rise to a new level.

That time would arrive before long, perhaps even as soon as 100,000 years. At that time, just what heights would they be at?

Moreover, if they could pass the abyssal ritual of the Demon God’s Tomb, just what would happen then…

Elder Eon God found this hard to imagine.

In fact, not only did the abyssals watching the battle atop the platform react with shock, but even Sheng Mei herself paled.

“Again!”

Lin Ming bellowed. He pulled up the Black Dragon Spear, grasping it in both hands and thrusting forwards again!

And what this spear stabbed at was Sheng Mei’s pair of dark angel wings!

This scene caused Sheng Mei’s abyssal fans to cry out in alarm!

The wings of a dark angel were indeed powerful, but no matter how powerful they were they still had their limits. In other words, Sheng Mei may not be able to use her wings to block this strike! And if the attack was too great then her wings might even break!

In this critical moment, Sheng Mei’s eyes sparkled with a cold light. She slapped her hands against the void and countless crystalline ice flowers appeared.

In that moment she had formed millions of Law seals. Each Law seal contained the source strength of extreme ice. A freezing atmosphere swept over the world, forming a wall of ice that was thousands of feet high.

Deep ice domain!

After undergoing nine revolutions of reincarnation, Sheng Mei’s mortal body had reached perfection and her strength was tens of thousands of times greater than before. She had comprehended the Ice Laws to the limit, and now she could even freeze and smash apart the Great Dao itself.

But as Lin Ming’s all-shattering spear crashed into the wall, he barraged it with an onslaught of attacks, crushing it apart as if he were breaking down a planet!

The bone spear shot out again and again without end. Compared to Sheng Mei, Lin Ming’s body was like that of an eagle pouncing on a sparrow!

As the ice wall was about to break, Lin Ming grabbed the Black Dragon Spear and thrust forwards one last time.

Kacha!

With a loud explosive sound, the ice wall shattered into countless pieces, causing the many abyssals watching to hold their breath.

Lin Ming’s spear collided against Sheng Mei’s black wings!

Chi - !

A grating sound filled the air. Beneath the impact the bone spear bent like a bow. Sheng Mei used her left arm to prop up her wings, and with her right hand grasped her sword to resist Lin Ming’s attack!

At this moment, her dark angel wings were now covered in faint rivulets of blood!

Chapter 2124 – Life Reaping Sword Strike

Heart-shocking blood flowed down from Sheng Mei’s black wings, dyeing them with traces of red.

Lin Ming’s powerful and fierce demon avatar, Sheng Mei’s delicate and beautiful figure, the two of them formed a blinding visual contrast.

The spear seemed as if it would pierce through Sheng Mei’s wings and stab into her body. The many abyssal Elders watching this battle were all left dripping with a cold sweat.

The Black Dragon Spear had bent into a crescent moon and Sheng Mei was also forced back to the edge of the light barrier.

However, the scene was frozen in this moment. After Lin Ming’s strike was weakened by the deep ice domain less than half of its original strength was left remaining. Finally, it was successfully blocked by Sheng Mei’s wings.

Its momentum had been ended!

Without the impact of energy, it was naturally impossible for the spear to pierce through Sheng Mei’s dark angel wings.

Lin Ming slightly frowned. In the end, because his true self couldn’t appear, then regardless of whether it was the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace he used or the Asura blood, if he couldn’t display it outwardly and had to funnel the energy through his demon avatar then there would inevitably be losses.

At this moment a warning signal flared in Lin Ming’s mind. He rapidly stepped back in space, hurriedly retreating.

Weng!

Borrowing the strength of the Black Dragon Spear unbending from its curved form, Lin Ming shot back like an arrow, his speed rapidly reaching the extreme.

But during this time, Sheng Mei’s bone sword appeared in front of Lin Ming without warning.

The bone sword’s sword light was even faster than Lin Ming’s retreat!

Above the sword blade, energy and Laws wildly surged. Tens of thousands of rays of light wove together and formed blood red lotus flowers that seemed to swallow all light.

An ordinary and simple sword strike carried with it an unfathomable vastness, a strange power that seemed as if it could pierce through space and crush time.

Lin Ming’s flesh and skin seemed as if it were already pierced through by this bone sword, making his heart race.

And no matter how quickly he drew backwards, the bone sword followed right after like a homing bird. If he slowed even just a bit then the bone sword would pierce right through his head.

Like a sword of judgment that presided over life and death, this came from the Life and Death Laws that Sheng Mei cultivated.

A single sword strike, it would not return without severing the soul and life!

With a distance of only an inch apart, Lin Ming could feel his protective demon essence pierced through and his forehead already dripping with blood!

As this minor wound appeared, Lin Ming could feel his life force slowly fade away, drawn out by the strange bone sword!

With the presence of the Death Laws, all things in existence would wither away, all life would be annihilated!

The life force in Lin Ming’s body was similarly being swallowed by Sheng Mei’s Death Laws.

“Her Highness the Holy Demoness has used her Laws!”

Many abyssals from Deep King Road began to stir up. Relatively speaking, Sheng Mei’s physical strength and abyssal body were weaker. Her speed lay somewhere in the center, and what she excelled in the most were the Laws!

And for the vast majority of abyssals, their weakest aspects tended to be the Laws.

In particular for a towering and powerfully built abyssal like Lin Ming. With such a potent bloodline and mighty physical body, it was likely that he had to pay for this with a smaller spiritual sea, making it so that perceiving the Laws would cost double the effort with half the results.

Perhaps from here on out the tides of battle would turn!

Many Deep King Road Elders were looking forwards to what would happen. In fact, over 95% of the abyssals present hoped that Sheng Mei could win. Sheng Mei had countless legions of fans and they were already accustomed to her awesome talent. As for Lin Ming, the abyssals present only felt envy towards him.

Only the Ancient Eon Sect faintly hoped that Lin Ming would be able to win. If so, then they could draw closer their relationship with Deep King Road and obtain even more advantages from the Demon God’s Tomb.

One running, one chasing. The Deep King Wheel wasn’t large and because of the confinement of the force field, the space within was small and narrow. However, to Lin Ming and Sheng Mei this wasn’t a problem at all, because during the rapid pursuit both of them constantly used the Space Laws and thus for them space had already lost all meaning.

But no matter how swift or deft Lin Ming was in shuttling through space, Sheng Mei’s sword remained locked onto the point between his eyebrows!

“Holy Scripture Laws?”

A bright light sparked in Lin Ming’s eyes. Sheng Mei’s sword was completely reflected in his deep brown eyes, just like an image in a clear mirror.

With a thought, a bloody demonic eye drilled out from between Lin Ming’s eyebrows, like a rock gushing out of lava. The gaze of this demonic eye carried with it a strange demonic charm, as if it could see through all lies and illusions. Then the gaze of this demonic eye fell upon the bone sword.

This demon eye was the fused form of Lin Ming’s Daevic Eye Dao Palace and Three Live Pupils. However, after joining together his true self with his avatar and using the power of demons to transform it, this eye had gained this appearance.

Lin Ming already had some understandings into the Holy Scripture Laws. Now, beneath the gaze of the demon eye he was able to see everything clearly.

The myriad Laws atop the bone sword were all perfectly balanced in his vision.

Sheng Mei’s attainments in the Holy Scripture Laws far surpassed Lin Ming’s. But, that didn’t mean Lin Ming couldn’t catch up to her.

At this moment the technique that Sheng Mei used was completely recorded by Lin Ming’s Daevic Eye Dao Palace and Three Lives Pupils. It branded itself deep into his memory, through his eyes and into his mind.

Lin Ming closed his eyes and when he opened them once more, they radiated a blinding divine light that could pierce through all puzzles. By relying on his own understandings as well as the Daevic Eye Dao Palace, he could find the most vulnerable point in Sheng Mei’s attack.

Woosh!

The Black Dragon Spear pierced out once more!

The pitch black spear swelled with roiling flames. Like a roaring bone dragon, it hurtled towards that singular point.

The Black Dragon Spear was a divine weapon refined by the Asura Road Master. Although it wasn’t the weapon used by the Asura Road Master’s true self, it was still incomparably powerful. This spear drew in the surrounding demon force field, causing thousands of black suns to erupt on the spear point and causing black light to flood through the audience.

Zhang!

The Black Dragon Spear collided with Sheng Mei’s bone sword. Sheng Mei’s sword that had recorded the ability to chase after life and death suddenly started to slow down. The Law runes that lingered upon the blade began to burst apart, instantly shattering into thousands of pieces.

Peng!

Runes danced in the air, dissipating like night stars fading in the morning skies.

Sheng Mei’s complexion changed. How was this possible!?

She never thought that in this situation, Lin Ming would be able to counterattack and see through her move!

She had used the highest Laws, so how had he managed to break through them? Was it just a coincidence?

Before Sheng Mei could think about what had occurred, Lin Ming’s second spear strike came towards her.

Zheng!

Another collision occurred. This time, Lin Ming didn’t choose Sheng Mei’s weakest point, but one that was only relatively weak.

This was because Sheng Mei’s sword potential had already been broken in half in his first spear strike. As for the remaining amount, Lin Ming could calmly deal with it. He didn’t need every spear strike to hit her weakest point, because doing so would definitely arouse her suspicions. After all, the Holy Scripture Laws weren’t easy to see through.

Now, Lin Ming didn’t want to expose too much of himself, lest Sheng Mei produce too many associations about who he truly was.

If Lin Ming couldn’t use continuous spear strikes at Sheng Mei’s weakest point to break through, then he would use an increasingly wild barrage of attacks instead.

Spear after spear, in a moment Lin Ming had already thrust out a hundred times, like flowers in a storm!

Sheng Mei felt her arm go numb. She suddenly froze!

Peng!

More and more runes burst apart in the skies. Sheng Mei’s hair wildly danced in the air as her eyebrows pressed tightly together!

Lin Ming had taken the initiative against her, and as for her, she actually felt strained!

What shocked her the most was that at this point, Lin Ming hadn’t used brute force to suppress her, but had used his understandings of the Laws!

How could this be?

Although Lin Ming’s following attacks seemed wild and ferocious, the truth was that his attacks avoided the strongest sections of her own. The only difference was that it wasn’t as exquisite as his first spear strike.

Hum –

Hum –

Hum –

Crazy and fierce spear strikes stirred up a savage tornado in the middle of the abyssal force field. The wind pressure tore through the air, colliding with the force field and causing it to moan.

The hellish pressure released by the two fighters on stage caused some of the weaker abyssal disciples watching to feel pressure. Some of them had no choice but to summon the demon power within them to resist it.

“Humph!”

Deep King Road’s Elder Deep Epoch coldly coughed. He raised up his own force field, allowing these weaker abyssal disciples to catch their breath.

But at this time, Elder Deep Epoch’s complexion was considerably ugly. Even being suppressed by the 12 totem poles, this Ancient Eon Sect’s Ninth Elder was still able to display such might in his attacks. Just where had he come from?

If things were to continue like this then it wouldn’t be long before this Ninth Elder surpassed him in strength.

If this Ninth Elder wished to marry Sheng Mei, then perhaps that wouldn’t be bad at all. The best result would be that Deep King Road would gain yet another top proud elite of heaven. In the future, this Ninth Elder could stand by Sheng Mei and the two could dominate the abyss.

But, the crux of the issue was – could he be of the same mind as Sheng Mei?

All sorts of thoughts flashed through Elder Deep Epoch’s mind.

And at this time atop the stage, Lin Ming had already occupied the winning side. The Black Dragon Spear continued in an unstoppable offensive, an onslaught that flowed forwards like liquid mercury. As for Sheng Mei, she was forced to retreat again and again, and the Life and Death Laws atop her sword light had already been scattered by Lin Ming!

Chapter 2126 – The Finale

For a time, the atmosphere on stage turned solemn.

All the abyssals had fallen silent. Lin Ming and Sheng Mei stood apart from each other, their gazes steady.

Lin Ming’s mortal body began to slowly regenerate.

The abyssals present stared blankly on as Lin Ming’s arm wound nearly stitched itself back together and they couldn’t sit still anymore.

“What is her Highness the Holy Demoness doing? How come she’s not doing anything and is just watching that fellow’s body repair itself? What use is there in talking about any sort of martial arts honor? Then again, this was a fair battle to begin with and that Ninth Elder was injured by the Holy Demoness so attacking him while he’s down is completely justified, so how come the Holy Demoness hasn’t attacked?”

A young abyssal anxiously asked. Most of the abyssals here were Sheng Mei’s supporters and only a few of them wished that Lin Ming could win.

“It isn’t that her Highness the Holy Demoness doesn’t wish to attack but that she cannot attack. The Holy Demoness consumed a considerable amount of energy just now, so how could she fight again so soon?”

An older abyssal said. By this point, the battle had reached a burning hot stage.

Lin Ming and Sheng Mei’s battle just now had exchanged wound for wound!

If they continued to fight, if this battle became any more brutal, then there would be dire combat techniques that came out next, such as someone burning their source soul force or blood essence as the price for greater strength.

And in this competition, this sort of behavior was against the rules. After all, this was only a mere comparison of skills to begin with and not a life or death slaughter. Any moves that caused permanent losses or where both sides were forced to perish together were forbidden. Because if one person used such a technique then everyone else would too, and the gains simply weren’t worth the losses.

As the older abyssal spoke, everyone looked towards Sheng Mei. At this time a continuously growing strength rose up within her, slowly supplementing her strength.

Just now she had used her nine revolution red lotus, fusing together the power of hope and desire from nine reincarnations. This was tantamount to nine Sheng Meis attack together, and thus the amount of demon power that she consumed was nine times that of her all-out attack!

If an ordinary martial artist or abyssal were to use such an attack then they would nearly exhaust themselves to nothing.

However, Sheng Mei had only slightly paled and her strength was slowly recovering. This was because with the power of life from the Holy Scripture Laws, Sheng Mei’s blood vitality and physical strength were able to last much longer and restore themselves faster than those of a martial artist of the same level.

As this scene fell into the eyes of the abyssals present, they were all numb with amazement.

Lin Ming’s regenerative abilities were astonishing, but so were Sheng Mei’s!

Lin Ming and Sheng Mei, they were nothing but two monsters. Not only did they possess terrifying strength, Laws, and speed, but their endurance was also at abnormal levels!

If one wished to fight against such freaks then one couldn’t have any weakness at all, because these two had no weakness and any weakness one possessed would become the reason for defeat!

In the entire Dark Abyss, just who would dare compete with them?

“I will not lose here!”

Sheng Mei glared at Lin Ming, her icy eyes shimmering.

Whoever could defeat her at the same boundary could dual cultivate with her. These were words spoken by her own mouth and confirmed by Deep King Road. It was impossible for her to go back on her words.

She didn’t wish to compromise with Lin Ming, and compromise was likely useless to begin with. She could only put forth everything she had in this battle and use the endlessly growing strength within her body to drain Lin Ming dry of strength.

And coincidently, Lin Ming also had such a plan.

Sheng Mei’s killing move was the nine revolution red lotus, and this was something that Lin Ming simply wasn’t able to deal with right now. Once they fought then he would surely be injured. The only positive part of this was that Sheng Mei couldn’t utilize this move multiple times because it consumed too much energy.

Thus, Lin Ming prepared to use his strength to outlast Sheng Mei and achieve victory in the end.

Lin Ming knew that Sheng Mei had the Laws of Life to rely on. But, Lin Ming was even more confident in what he relied on, because he still had his true self within his demon avatar!

Lin Ming couldn’t use his true self to fight, thus he couldn’t do anything to Sheng Mei right now because he couldn’t display his peak strength.

However, Lin Ming’s true self resided in his demon avatar’s inner world and he could continuously transmit strength into his avatar’s body. In terms of endurance, who could compete with him?

This was the same as two fighting against one. Moreover, the two of them had abnormal levels of endurance!

As long as the fight continued at a steady pace then he would emerge victorious in the end.

After an incense stick of time passed, Lin Ming could feel that his wounds had more or less healed. Then, he moved!

When he moved this time he didn’t even use the Black Dragon Spear, but simply punched out with his fist.

His fist was like a meteor, thundering down onto Sheng Mei’s chest!

Weng! Weng! Weng!

Abyssal Laws condensed into a vortex of runes around Lin Ming’s fist, forming an all-swallowing black hole. Several blood dragons rushed out from this black hole, roaring and snapping their jaws at Sheng Mei!

Each of these blood dragons contained the power of swallowing. In truth, they were similar to Famine’s tentacles!

“Swallowing Laws!?”

All of the abyssals watching could see this clearly. In the Dark Abyss, only a small minority of higher abyssals could grasp this tyrannical and overbearing Law which allowed one to swallow the strength of others for one’s own use, to swallow the flesh and blood of others as one’s own nourishment.

This was an extremely cruel and evil Law, one envied by all abyssals!

“This brat, how can he understand the Swallowing Laws!? Everything good has been taken by him!”

At this time, no one doubted Lin Ming’s bloodline. For him to possess the Swallowing Laws was well within reason, because the Swallowing Laws were one of the signs of a higher abyssal.

Facing these blood dragon tentacles, Sheng Mei didn’t dodge. Her delicate eyebrows furrowed together and the sword in her hands came slashing down, severing all the tentacles!

Ca!

Sword light radiated outwards. Blood flew out into the air!

Sheng Mei had already planned to engage Lin Ming in a battle of endurance. Thus, she naturally wouldn’t let go of any chances to exchange attacks with him. She believed that with her Laws supporting her she would eventually be the one to persist until the end.

Lin Ming was truly abnormal, but in this aspect he might not be able to compare with her!

Moreover, when comparing endurance, the truth was that it was also a battle of willpower. If one possessed great willpower, this often allowed them to surpass their own limits.

Sheng Mei was confident in her own willpower, because no matter what she could not lose this battle!

She no longer had an escape path left open to her. She didn’t dare to imagine herself being pressed down beneath the gigantic body of this abyssal and just how disgusting and stomach-retching that would be.

Rumble rumble rumble!

The intense collision stirred up raging waves of energy and caused the light barrier of the Deep King force field to violently tremble. In a breath of time, Lin Ming and Sheng Mei exchanged over a hundred moves.

They fought speed with speed and didn’t pause their onslaught against each other. They tried to preserve as much strength even as they tried to use up their opponent’s strength.

This was a short but furious battle that was extremely taxing on their energy!

At this time, both Sheng Mei and Lin Ming naturally discovered each other’s plans; they had come up with the same idea to win.

Sheng Mei’s eyes lit up with blazing fighting intent and the corners of her lips curved up in a smile.

And while Lin Ming’s eyes remained indifferent, his heart was filled with confidence!

They both brimmed with confidence because they both believed in their secret cards that gave them endurance!

As the fight heated up it became increasingly intense and savage.

Many abyssals only saw a great storm rise up within the Deep King force field!

But as for the exact process of the fight, none of them were able to clearly see what was occurring!

“They are comparing endurance… it seems that the difference in strength between the two of them is too minor so neither can do anything to the other, thus they have decided to use time to settle victory and defeat!”

An abyssal Elder said on the side of Deep King Road.

“Her Highness the Holy Demoness possesses a horrifying level of endurance… let alone abyssals at the same level, even True Divinity level abyssals might not be able to compare with her. But her opponent is also a monster. From him, it seems anything is possible. Her Highness the Holy Demoness might not be able to win!”

Another Elder of Deep King Road said.

In Deep King Road, the status of the members present was decided by strength.

This Elder’s status was below Sheng Mei’s, thus when he spoke of her he had to use a respectful tone.

But at this time, Deep Epoch chuckled. He said, “The battle has already gone this far, and I’m beginning to see things differently. Perhaps losing might not be a bad thing at all…”

“Oh? You are meaning…?”

“The Ancient Eon Sect doesn’t know where the Ninth Elder comes from either. After this battle, we will look up more information on him. The truth is that if the Holy Demoness doesn’t marry for the rest of her life, that isn’t a plan at all. Although she might not care about it, her bloodline is so excellent. If it isn’t inherited by her descendants then wouldn’t it just be wasted?”

“We have to find a way to marry her off. And if my Deep King Road’s Holy Demoness were to marry, then if we look through the entire Dark Abyss, just who can match up with her? This Ninth Elder came out of nowhere and although I might not like him too much, I have to acknowledge that he is the best possible candidate…”

As Deep Epoch spoke, the other Elders nodded in agreement.

Indeed, this was true.

In their eyes Lin Ming was truly an indisputable top choice. The Dark Abyss was a land that revered powerhouses above all, and if a higher abyssal like Lin Ming wished to choose someone to marry then there would be countless abyssal women who would desperately flock to him.

In the abyss, powerful and rugged abyssals, those with towering and thick builds, if they possessed enough strength then they were far more welcomed than the pretty and handsome male incubuses amongst the succubus demon race. And, Lin Ming’s strength, his ferocious and bulging muscles, all of that was perfectly aligned with this point.

However, they never imagined that Sheng Mei was simply unable to accept the aesthetic sense of the abyssal demons. She absolutely could not!

Chapter 2127A – The Finale

On the Deep King Wheel, Lin Ming and Sheng Mei’s battle continued.

The two of them maintained their extreme speed. Every time they exchanged moves was like a collision of planets.

Sheng Mei’s wings stretched out. Howling gales wrapped around her body, her figure drifting in an unpredictably bizarre fashion!

Woosh!

The Black Dragon Spear cut through the void, savagely tearing towards Sheng Mei’s chest and piercing through!

In that moment, the hearts of many abyssals tightened. But in the next moment that ‘Sheng Mei’ vanished, leaving behind only the Black Dragon Spear; it had been nothing more than an afterimage.

The true Sheng Mei had already appeared behind Lin Ming. Her sword came falling down, sword light recklessly gushing out like a black tide, tumbling and roaring!

In that instant, from within the inner world of Lin Ming’s demon avatar, the Heretical God Tree appeared. The air filled with demonic energy as a bone tree drilled towards the heavens. Demonic fire and thunder howled out, tainted with the power of demons as it welcomed the turbulent sword light.

Bang!

The sword light and Lin Ming’s demon power exploded and vanished together. Lin Ming didn’t even turn his head. The Black Dragon Spear came roaring out behind, the spear point drawing a full moon as he struck out in a circle!

Sheng Mei’s body was blown away like a flower petal by this horrific strength. Her protective demon essence violently shook and she couldn’t help but gather her wings together to resist Lin Ming’s strike.

Woosh!

Beneath the tremendous impact force, Sheng Mei was sent hurtling away like a meteor. She crashed into the Deep King force field’s light barrier. But, before the abyssals watching could even cry out in alarm, her figure instantly disappeared.

And in the next moment the Black Dragon Spear struck the area Sheng Mei had just vanished from. A terrifying explosion rang out once more!

The fierce intensity of this battle left the abyssals watching dizzy with wonder!

Most of the abyssals present were simply unable to see the fighting process between Sheng Mei and Lin Ming. Only the constantly shivering Deep King force field, and the flashes of shadows all around the light barrier reminded them just how cruel and savage this battle was.

Time marched on.

Two hours, four hours…

This intense fight continued for all this time without a single chance for anyone to catch their breath.

Every move was met head on with equally terrifying resilience. Lin Ming and Sheng Mei both relied on their potent restorative abilities to continue this battle.

As time passed, Sheng Mei felt more and more alarmed!

This battle had indeed gone as she had expected. It beat on with a rhythm of dragging on the battle with both parties being drained of energy.

But although this was the process she expected, it might not be the result she expected.

Lin Ming’s endurance was simply far too dreadful. If anyone were to consume energy at such a rate, then let alone an Empyrean level abyssal, even a True Divinity might have already been completely exhausted, like a dried up oil lamp.

But Lin Ming was able to continue onwards, even becoming increasingly brutal as the battle raged on!

Sheng Mei’s strength on the other hand was being weakened. Although the Holy Scripture Laws were heaven-defying, the so-called ‘endlessly growing’ still had its limits. If the battle continued like this then the first one to fall over might be herself.

Sheng Mei’s speed had already slowed down.

This scene fell into the eyes of all the abyssals watching. In terms of endurance, Deep King Road’s Holy Demoness was unexpectedly losing to the Ancient Eon Sect’s Ninth Elder.

Endurance was an important aspect of a martial artist’s strength.

In truth, from the very start, from feeling alone, Lin Ming consumed more energy than Sheng Mei did. This was because in terms of his size, the might of his moves, all of it used more strength than Sheng Mei.

Even so, the first one who wouldn’t be able to persist was Sheng Mei.

Ca!

Another ray of sword light slashed down towards Lin Ming before being scattered by his strength. The moment the sword light shattered, the Black Dragon Spear in Lin Ming’s hands thrust out like a viper, straight towards Sheng Mei’s left rib!

This was an extremely tricky attack angle. However, Sheng Mei didn’t dodge. Her left wing suddenly spread out and cut down at the Black Dragon Spear!

Kacha!

The sound of a fierce collision rang out. From the surface of the Black Dragon Spear, chips of bone scattered out!

But Sheng Mei’s left wing had nearly been pierced through by the Black Dragon Spear and was now dripping with blood!

In that moment Lin Ming’s eyes flashed with surprise. Sheng Mei had relied on nearly just the strength of her mortal body to resist this strike, and didn’t use her demon power at all. Otherwise her wing wouldn’t have been torn by his spear strike.

But then, Sheng Mei stretched out her arm and grabbed hold of the Black Dragon Spear. Her delicate and exquisite jade-white arm wrapped around the thick Black Dragon Spear, clasping the shaft right beneath her arm!

Ka ka ka ka!

All around Sheng Mei, the void shattered. An Ice Phoenix howled out and threw itself onto the Black Dragon Spear. For a time, the Black Dragon Spear began to rapidly freeze over, and as for Lin Ming who was gripping it, he suddenly paused. Cold energy recklessly rushed into Lin Ming’s body from all directions.

Sheng Mei had released her deep ice force field once more, but this time the force field had been reduced to the smallest area possible, all of it compressed onto Lin Ming’s body. Without a doubt, she was risking everything on this move!

From between Sheng Mei’s eyebrows, the nine revolutions red lotus began to shine brilliantly.

The void seemed to overlap and shiver. The revolving lotus flower once again manifested into nine revolutions of worlds. When these worlds were joined together, one could see mountains and rivers within them, plants and beasts and birds, a million, a billion lives being born and destroyed.

Within each world sat a cross-legged Sheng Mei. This was the power of hope and desire of Sheng Mei’s nine reincarnations.

The nine Sheng Meis gathered their hands together in prayer, their expressions one of supreme reverence.

In that moment, their power of hope and desire gathered together, forming a golden river of stars that crashed down atop Lin Ming!

Was this the final move!?

Lin Ming’s pupils shrank. Sheng Mei didn’t hesitate to suffer injuries in order to seal away his movement. All of this was in order to keep him at a close distance where she could use the nine revolutions red lotus to engage in a final showdown with him. This was because she had discovered that in terms of endurance, she might not be able to overcome him.

This time, seeing the nine revolutions of worlds form into sword light that slashed down on him, Lin Ming’s heart and mind were as still as water. From his inner world, the blood of Asura began to burn.

Even Lin Ming’s three avatars of essence, energy, and divine poured their strength into the demon avatar without reserve.

A blinding radiance burst out from Lin Ming’s eyes. In his inner world, the Asura Wheel was fused with and covered by the power of demons. Then, the Asura Wheel turned into a giant demon wheel that rose up from behind Lin Ming.

Wild demon power filled the air. A peerless demon appeared, slowly pushing the wheel forwards. This was the demon phantom formed by the Asura phantom.

The wheel contained thousands and millions of great demons roaring within. Inside, there was also the flesh and blood essence of the totem level abyssal demon, Famine.

As this demon wheel revolved, Lin Ming used both his hands and pushed outwards.

Lin Ming had poured all of his strength into this demon wheel and now it welcomed Sheng Mei’s nine revolutions red lotus.

Ka ka ka ka ka!

Chapter 2127B – The Finale

The demon wheel cut down onto the nine revolutions red lotus. Celestial bodies would be grinded apart by it, and even the river of time seemed to shake.

During this fierce collision, the power of hope and desire from nine reincarnations and the great demon wheel began to wear away at each other.

The strength of all Laws, every ray of light, space and time, beneath the impact of these two great strengths, everything seemed to stir up, forming visible beams of energy that fell down upon the Deep King force field in torrents.

The Deep King force field’s light barrier wildly shook. Because of the extended battle, the energy saved within the 12 totem poles was insufficient. Underneath this final impact the Deep King force field wasn’t able to withstand the enormous destructive force and a tiny gap was ripped open!

Peng! Peng! Peng!

From all over the force field, the abyssal phantoms that covered the array formation’s light barrier began to explode together. Beams of Law lights gathered together, shooting out from Deep King force field and recklessly spraying outwards!

These light beams were energy blades formed by the collision of Lin Ming and Sheng Mei. Each one possessed a terrifying penetrating force, destroying wherever it went!

“Be careful!”

An abyssal cried out in alarm. To some of the weaker abyssals, any one of these light beams could easily pierce through them and take their lives!

The younger abyssals quickly retreated, even taking out their weapons to fend off these light beams.

But at this time, the True Divinity level Elders actually stepped forwards. They summoned protective shields of demon power that blocked all the light beams.

“They actually drained dry the energy from the totem poles. This is just defying the heavens!”

Deep Epoch frowned. The Deep King force field was the sect-stabilizing array formation of Deep King Road. With Lin Ming and Sheng Mei’s strength they shouldn’t have been able to break through it. However, they had actually managed to forcefully exhaust the energy contained in the array formation.

At this time within the array formation, Lin Ming and Sheng Mei were in the center of the collision, both of them covered in blood!

Sheng Mei’s clothes were torn in numerous places. Her battle armor was broken and her long hair fluttered wildly about her.

And Lin Ming was in an even more tragic state. His chest was smothered in blood. The nine revolutions red lotus had been broken apart by the demon wheel, but as the two halves passed by him it nearly split him in half.

Although Lin Ming’s wounds were heavier, he actually had more strength remaining. This was because within the inner world of Lin Ming’s demon avatar, his true self and his three avatars were continuously supplying the demon avatar with energy.

This was the source of Lin Ming’s trump card.

But in comparison, because Sheng Mei had already consumed a great deal of energy and the nine revolutions red lotus she used once more, her face was already pale white. She had used up all her strength!

Lin Ming roared out and grasped the Black Dragon Spear. From beneath Sheng Mei’s arm, the Black Dragon Spear crazily shook!

Kacha!

The cold ice that froze over the shaft of the black Dragon Spear shattered, and even the bone armor atop the spear began to burst apart!

Lin Ming violently dragged out the spear, pulling the Black Dragon Spear out from the wreckage of broken ice and bone!

Sheng Mei’s delicate eyebrows pressed together and a trace of blood dripped from the corners of her lips. The Black Dragon Spear had been pulled out from beneath her right arm, and because of the shattered bone cutting her as it was pulled out, her right side was covered in blood!

Lin Ming’s eyes flashed with a cold light. The power of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace boiled over from within him as he suddenly pierced out the spear. The spear point continued to tremble as the power of Laws billowed outwards, shooting forth like a river of stars and releasing a terrifying brilliance that submerged Sheng Mei.

Sheng Mei’s pupils shrank. At this moment she could feel death approach!

This scene was fixed in the eyes of those watching for eternity. The light of Laws that danced in the air was like faded flower petals fluttering downwards. As for Sheng Mei shrouded in light, she was a black butterfly that had transformed into a fairy maiden.

Her long hair danced about her and she barely managed to use her still movable left wing as a shield. Beneath this black wing, Sheng Mei’s peerless looks were as cold and arrogant as a mountain of ice.

Her eyes weren’t focused on the spear that thrust towards her with cold brilliance, but the approaching Lin Ming’s face.

In her bright pupils, the image of Lin Ming was clearly reflected.

This sight seemed to touch something in Lin Ming’s heart. Just as the Black Dragon Spear was about to stab into the point between Sheng Mei’s eyebrows, Lin Ming turned his arm, changing the trajectory of the spear slightly so that it passed Sheng Mei’s cheek and turned out instead.

Puff!

Lin Ming’s spear light stabbed into the Deep King force field’s light barrier. The Deep King force field had originally been exhausted of energy and was now no longer capable of resisting Lin Ming’s strike; the Black Dragon Spear directly pierced through it.

Ka ka ka!

Atop the barrier of light, cracks began to spread out like a spider web, proliferating at a rapid pace.

In a mere moment, the egg-like light barrier burst apart! Energy fell down like rain, sprinkling down onto the world like the endless stars glittering in the skies.

And in the inexhaustible rain of light, Lin Ming and Sheng Mei stood in the void. The Black Dragon Spear’s point was only three inches away from Sheng Mei’s beautiful face, where it cut off a strand of her black hair.

Time came to a standstill.

Sheng Mei looked at Lin Ming, an indescribable look emerging in her eyes.

She had been defeated. In a frontal battle she had actually been defeated by a higher abyssal who had a lower cultivation than she did.

This truth was hard for her to accept. At this moment, an inexplicable feeling began to rise up in her heart. This abyssal that held the spear in front of her left her confused and muddled. Although he was close, she couldn’t see through him at all.

After the Deep King force field exploded and while the rain of light was still silently falling, all around the battlefield the entire audience had fallen silent. The winner and loser of this battle was already clear to all. In that last spear strike, if Lin Ming hadn’t held back then Sheng Mei wouldn’t even be able to stand there right now.

“He won… he really won?”

The Elders and disciples of the Ancient Eon Sect felt as if they were living a dream. Within the Dark Abyss, Deep King Road’s Holy Demoness was no different from a living legend, but now that living legend had been beaten by an Elder of their Ancient Eon Sect, and this Elder had even jumped ranks to do so.

Did this mean that their Ancient Eon Sect would develop a relationship of marriage with Deep King Road?

As the disciples of the Ancient Eon Sect thought of the numerous rumors concerning Deep King Road’s Holy Demoness and as they recalled the countless higher abyssals that chased after her, they couldn’t help but gulp. While they admired and envied Lin Ming at the same time, they felt that everything that just occurred was too fantastical.

But as for the other small influences around the Ancient Eon Sect, they were so envious that their eyes turned red.

However, none of them dared to speak out at this time. In the Dark Abyss, strength was the ultimate deterrence. Lin Ming had already proven his own strength. As long as he didn’t perish then in the future his accomplishments would even surpass those of Sheng Mei. Facing such a ruthless person, who dared make snide remarks?

In fact, the abyssals that taunted Lin Ming before began to feel weak at heart. They were all afraid that Lin Ming would remember their taunts.

“Her Highness the Holy Demoness really lost…”

A Deep King Road Elder said with deep emotion, unsure of what feeling was in his heart.

There was a bit of loss but also a bit of expectation. Who could say what would happen in the future?

“What do we do?” An Elder asked Deep Epoch.

Deep Epoch waved his hand, saying, “We do what we have to do and that is naturally to conduct the grand dual cultivation ceremony. But, this matter needs to be reported to the higher ups. The Sovereign is secretive in his movements, a dragon that cannot be seen, so the report shouldn’t be for him. Instead, report this matter to the Great Elder.”

In Deep King Road, above Deep Epoch was an upper True Divinity level abyssal Elder. Besides Deep, this Elder could be called the highest authority of Deep King Road.

Chapter 2128 – Marriage

On the Deep King Wheel, the dense rain of light subsided. From all around, many of the surrounding disciples and Elders of the abyssal influences had yet to respond. Then, many abyssals began to quietly discuss amongst themselves. To them, this scene was a dream they never would have imagined.

“Those from Deep King Road, are you ready to announce the end of the match?”

At this time the Great Elder of the Ancient Eon Sect stood up, drawing the gaze of many nearby abyssals.

Without a doubt, the Ancient Eon Sect had been able to feel proud and overjoyed, and even earned a great deal of face in front of everyone.

There were many Elders of large influences present who coveted the status of the Ancient Eon Sect. As they looked at Eon God, their complexions were filled with envy and unwillingness.

The Deep King Road Elder responsible for overseeing the competition awkwardly coughed. Then, he stepped onto the Deep King Wheel and loudly announced, “The battle has ended. The victor is the Ninth Elder of the Ancient Eon Sect!”

The stag remained silent. Many abyssals discovered that even until now, they didn’t know what the name of this Ancient Eon Sect’s Ninth Elder was.

“Then…concerning marriage, I believe that everyone from Deep King Road will not forget, right?”

Eon God spoke out once more, looking towards the Elders of Deep King Road before glancing over at Sheng Mei. At this time, the Elders of Deep King Road all had various emotions written on their faces, and as for Sheng Mei, her complexion was paler than normal.

In Lin Ming’s last strike, because of the Laws Lin Ming used, the strangely familiar aura, and finally Lin Ming suddenly holding back, a weird feeling began to surge in her heart. This was something that tickled her mind yet she wasn’t able to place a finger on it.

For a time, Sheng Mei thought she wanted to understand just where this strange feeling originated from. But after hearing Elder Eon God’s words, everything she felt towards Lin Ming suddenly disappeared.

In her pupils, Lin Ming’s demonic incarnation was reflected in them. This fierce black monster had shattered scales all over his body and the two bone blades that jutted out from his elbows had broken off. His entire body was covered and blood at it seemed that his injured were far more serious than her own.

At this time, his dark brown eyes were also gazing back at her.

By now, Lin Ming had already undone the Asura body metamorphosis and had returned to a normal size. Of course, this was in comparison to the life forms of the 33 Heavens. He was still towering and thickly built, and even though Sheng Mei was tall herself, she only reached just below Lin Ming’s chest.

Sheng Mei simply found this hard to accept, that this monster had defeated her and would soon obtain her.

“Hahaha!”

At this time, Elder Deep Epoch laughed and his foots came hurrying forwards. He appeared atop the Deep King Wheel, right between Lin Ming and Sheng Mei.

“What Elder Eon God said is correct. Since your sect’s Ninth Elder has won then we will naturally fulfill our side of the promise and allow our Deep King Road’s Holy Demoness to marry your Ninth Elder in a grand dual cultivation ceremony!”

Elder Deep Epoch readily agreed, causing the Elders of smaller influences to be startled. As for the younger abyssals, they were despondent upon hearing this. Even if Sheng Mei didn’t marry Lin Ming, they were clearly aware that it still wouldn’t be their turn. But, upon knowing that the most perfect goddess in the entire Dark Abyss would be ravaged by such a towering and ferocious abyssal demon, they still found this somewhat hard to accept. This sort of feeling was like seeing the most perfect thing in existence being polluted.

As for Sheng Mei, her eyelids jumped up as she heard Elder Deep Epoch’s words. She looked at Lin Ming but didn’t speak. However, the light in her eyes clearly turned much colder…

“Elder Deep Epoch is truly refreshing!” Eon God laughed. “Then…tomorrow my Ancient Eon Sect will prepare a dowry gift to settle this marriage. How about it?”

“Haha! Elder Eon God is too courteous. We can discuss this wedding further, after all, this must be a grand occasion for all of us.”

Elder Deep Epoch didn’t oppose Lin Ming marrying Sheng Mei. In his opinion, this would also be something beneficial to Deep King Road.

“Then about the date of this marriage ceremony….” Elder Eon God continued to say. What he planned was to publically confirm a marriage date so that they could avoid future nights of headaches.

Although Lin Ming had seemingly appeared from nowhere, and his victory of Sheng Mei had left all the abyssals bewildered, in the end Lin Ming was still an Elder of their Ancient Eon Sect. If the Ancient Eon Sect could use Lin Ming to climb the big tree that was Deep King Road, then Elder Eon God would absolutely love for this to occur.

After all, the Ancient Eon Sect had suffered crisis after crisis and countless influences were eyeing them, waiting for them to break apart so that they could be replaced.

“Haha, Elder Eon God is quite impatient. However, there is still some time until the Demon God’s Tomb opens, so if we do hold the dual cultivation ceremony before then, although it may be a bit hastily done, I don’t see any reason why we can’t!”

Deep Epoch rubbed his chin and looked at Lin Ming. According to any logical reasoning, it would be best for Lin Ming to emerge from the Demon God’s Tomb before the grand dual cultivation ceremony was held, since the Demon God’s Tomb was filled with dangers and anything could happen within.

However, in Deep Epoch’s view, a peerless genius like Lin Ming would likely have a ridiculously tough life. At the very least, nothing should happen to him in the Demon God’s Tomb. If they could hold the grand dual cultivation ceremony ahead of time then this would be proof that Deep King Road trusted Lin Ming, and this would help them strengthen their relationship with Lin Ming in the future.

Deep Epoch and Eon God continued to agree with each other, seeming as if they would almost put the marriage on today’s agenda.

And by this time, Sheng Mei finally found it hard to remain calm. If she didn’t say anything then she feared that within several days, she would have to marry Lin Ming in front of all these abyssals.

It just so happened that because of the Demon God’s Tomb, all of the influences that were connected to Deep King Road had gathered here. All of them had been sent written invitations.

She sent a sound transmission to Lin Ming, “I must speak with you…”

“What is there to talk about?” Lin Ming glanced at Sheng Mei. Seeing her pale face, a strange feeling stirred in his heart.

This was an extremely complex feeling, one that seemed to originate from dark feelings, from the pleasure of taking revenge. But inevitably, it also came from Lin Ming’s unclear feelings about Sheng Mei.

Lin Ming’s deepest impression of Sheng Mei had been her cold and callous actions as she took his Eternal Soul and left.

But, when he had lost his strength and was completely dried up, on the verge of death, it was in that moment that he felt the warmth and fullness brought about by Sheng Mei’s source soul force and life essence.

If it weren’t for those things she left him then he wouldn’t have been able to understand the samsara of life and death before he perished, and he wouldn’t have been able to comprehend the Grand Reincarnation Art and slowly restore himself.

Sheng Mei gave Lin Ming a life saving grace. However, Lin Ming couldn’t clearly see through her actions or reasons. This caused Lin Ming to subconsciously be on guard against her, not trusting her, but also caring for her.

Because of his actions and the upcoming promise of dual cultivation, Sheng Mei was unable to maintain the cold arrogance of her heart. Instead, she nervous and panicked due to the upcoming agreement and Lin Ming couldn’t help but take pleasure in this sort of revenge.

Even though Lin Ming had experienced so many things in his life, it was still hard for him to rid himself of this part of human nature.

“Who are you? Where did you come from? What’s your name?” Sheng Mei asked Lin Ming.

“Who I am, where I come from, those aren’t things you need to concern yourself with. As for my name, you can call me Ninth Elder.”

Lin Ming didn’t plan to tell Sheng Mei about his own status. Even if he inwardly wanted to believe in Sheng Mei, she was still someone that worked from the Soul Emperor and someone who had complicated relations with Deep King Road. There was even a chance that she was an abyssal demon, a mortal enemy to him.

In this sort of situation, Lin Ming couldn’t guarantee that Sheng Mei wouldn’t betray him if she were threatened by someone or tempted by something. For instance, if she were tempted by that peak of martial arts so longed for in her dreams.

Moreover, Lin Ming had a faint feeling that to a certain extent, Sheng Mei was being controlled by the Soul Emperor. At the very least, the Soul Emperor was aware of all her actions. In this case, if Sheng Mei were to know who he truly was then it would be far too dangerous.

After listening to Lin Ming’s words, Sheng Mei frowned, clearly unsatisfied with his reply.

After all, they would likely have to conduct the grand dual cultivation ceremony soon and he wouldn’t even tell her his name.

“I want to make a deal with you!”

Sheng Mei icily said. She was already disinclined to banter with Lin Ming. The brief spell of goodwill towards him that had magically appeared from nowhere had disappeared.

Even Sheng Mei couldn’t clearly explain why she would have even the least bit of favorable impression towards this barbaric abyssal demon that was brimming over with an evil aura.

“What kind of deal?” Lin Ming’s eyes rose, his attention suddenly stirring.

Chapter 2131 – Deep Child

Deep in the night, Sheng Mei sat cross-legged in her chambers, shrouded in an endless illumination of black light. Thousands of strands of hair fluttered about her, emitting a light and enchanting fragrance.

She seemed to be the source of all darkness in the universe. As long as a ray of light neared her, it would be cleanly swallowed away.

Sheng Mei was accumulating strength in order to prepare for attacking the True Divinity realm in the future. In truth, her current cultivation was incredibly close to True Divinity.

Like a pool of water at night, although Sheng Mei was sitting in her chambers, she could still clearly feel the flow of energy around her. She faintly felt that somewhere not too far away from her, the circulation of energy began to speed up, as if some storm were brewing.

“It’s him…”

Sheng Mei opened her eyes, looking at some direction in the dark room.

The direction she faced was the room where Lin Ming was.

Sheng Mei gazed on for a long time and then gently sighed. She was sighing not just for Lin Ming but also for herself. For these past years, she had shouldered far too many things, things that no one knew of. From the outside she seemed to be living an infinitely glorious and wonderful life, but at the same time she endured a fate of samsara that was beyond understanding…

At this time the abyssal Laws suddenly began to stir up in the dark room. The Laws and energy coalesced together, forking a small vortex, and within this small vortex was a simple bronze mirror.

Shua!

With a loud sound, a black spatial gate appeared on the surface of the bronze mirror.

The spatial gate revolved, emitting a misty black light. It seemed like the maw of an ancient vicious beast, ferocious and cruel.

Seeing this, Sheng Mei frowned. She took back her wistful expression and returned to her heartless indifference.

“Junior-apprentice Sister…”

A sound echoed out from the spatial gate, thick and masculine, magnetic to the senses, one that was delightful to listen to.

With it, an abyssal demon wearing purple battle armor stepped out from the spatial gate.

As this abyssal appeared, the surrounding world seemed to resonate with him, beating in rhythm with the man’s steps as if true meanings of the abyssal Dao were appearing.

This abyssal was one of those that Deep King Road sent out to join the expedition into the Demon God’s Tomb this time – Deep Child!

When the three great influences of Deep King Road, the Ancient Eon Sect, and Nine Nether Palace held their competition of True Divinity masters, Deep King Road had sent out six True Divinity level masters, among which Sheng Mei was included. Of these six abyssals, only one of them had a middle True Divinity level cultivation – Deep Child!

Because of Deep Child’s high cultivation, neither the Ancient Eon Sect nor Nine Nether Palace had any Elders dare to challenge him. Instead, many of those Elders chose the one that seemed the weakest – Sheng Mei. But to their dismay they finally discovered that Sheng Mei was actually an incredibly ruthless individual, and all four abyssal Elders who thought to challenge her had been defeated.

“Junior-apprentice Sister’s strength is becoming increasingly fierce, soon to break into the True Divinity realm at any time. I fear that once Junior-apprentice Sister becomes a True Divinity, even I will not be a match for you.”

Deep Child chuckled, his tone gentle.

This voice didn’t seem like that of an abyssal demon at all. A tall and robust abyssal like Deep Child usually had a loud and resonant voice, one that rang like a bell, low and deep, a voice that caused the ears to hum.

But Deep Child spoke like a modest gentleman from one of the races of the 33 Heavens, with a voice that sounded like a cool spring breeze.

However, as Sheng Mei listened to him, a deep loathing and disgust flickered in the depths of her eyes. She said without expression, “The reason you came today is not to say this!”

“Mm… it isn’t…”

As Deep Child spoke he took out a black jade slip and flipped it around in his fingers a few times.

“There is a little more than a month until the Demon God’s Tomb opens. These are your orders and the division of duty between us all is explicitly clear. However, I also hope that Junior-apprentice Sister will cooperate with me.”

Deep Child tossed the jade slip into Sheng Mei’s hands, a playful expression on his face. Sheng Mei took the jade slip and swept through it. It only took her a breath of time to completely look through it.

Without any reaction, Sheng Mei crumbled the jade slip in her hands, “I understand.”

“Mm, very good!” Deep Child said, his face full of smiles.

Looking at the present Sheng Mei, he couldn’t help but twitch his nose several times and say with satisfaction, “Junior-apprentice Sister’s cultivation is rising higher and higher, and with your Grand Reincarnation Art having reached perfection, your aura is becoming that much more mesmerizing, haha!”

Deep Child frivolously commented. Sheng Mei didn’t respond. Instead, her icy cold eyes remained locked on Deep Child.

“Cheh, too heartless!” Deep Child said, a bit bored. He continued, “That Ancient Eon Sect’s Ninth Elder has a bit of skill. To think that he nearly managed to obtain you! But what a pity, he has missed his chance. In the future I fear he won’t have another opportunity!”

Sheng Mei couldn’t be bothered to care about Deep Child’s nonsense. She said, “I know you’ve been investigating the Ninth Elder’s status for these past days. Have you found anything?”

“I haven’t.” Deep Child shook his head, a suspicious color in his eyes. “His talent is at a higher level than yours, and that itself is inconceivable. But… there will always be surprises in this world, just like how he managed to somehow find the Book of Eon that had been missing for so long. It should be when he found the Book of Eon that he stumbled onto his fortuitous encounter. However, that doesn’t matter, because no matter what he encountered it is the same to us.”

Deep Child said with confidence. Sheng Mei remained silent. Not only had Deep Child not managed to find any information concerning the Ancient Eon Sect’s Ninth Elder, but Sheng Mei discovered that not only was she not disappointed, but faint threads of hope and joy were inexplicably appearing in her heart instead.

She was originally worried that this mysterious Ninth Elder might have some troubling identity. If Deep Child had really found anything he would have already taken action ahead of time.

As for that strange hope in her heart, even she couldn’t explain where it came from. However, Sheng Mei felt that when the end of the world was arriving, there would always be unanticipated and extraordinary outliers that would appear. And these outliers would always make others feel as if a favorable turnaround was possible…

“I asked you before about the situation in the 33 Heavens. Have you investigated it?”

The Dark Abyss was isolated from the 33 Heavens. Even transmitting information just once wasn’t easy at all.

Sheng Mei wasn’t an abyssal demon to begin with so she could leave the Dark Abyss if she desired. However, her freedom was limited so she hadn’t left the Dark Abyss for a long, long time.

If she wanted to find out anything concerning the 33 Heavens, she would have to ask Deep Child.

Deep Child also couldn’t leave the Dark Abyss. But, he had some unique methods with which he could obtain information about the 33 Heavens.

Deep Child chuckled, “The 33 Heavens? It’s the same old story, nothing has changed!”

Hearing Deep Child’s words, Sheng Mei fell silent for a moment. “The war between the saints and humanity, is it still continuing?”

“Mm, it is…”

“There hasn’t been some favorable turn?”

“Just what favorable turn can there be? Humanity is still hiding away in the wild universe. If it weren’t for the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign having gone into seclusion then humanity would have long since perished. But, their extinction is likely rapidly approaching.”

Deep Child’s words were somewhat grating as they fell on Sheng Mei’s ears.

She deeply looked at Deep Child as if she wanted to find something from his eyes or expression. However, Deep Child’s brown eyes only held mockery and ridicule.

Sheng Mei didn’t want to believe Deep Child’s words, but, she knew that what Deep Child said was the most reasonable and also most likely situation.

If there was some reversal in the war then that would be a miracle.

Sheng Mei shook her head, no longer thinking about it.

Seeing Sheng Mei’s reaction, Deep Child smugly smiled. He said, “Is junior-apprentice Sister worrying about someone in the 33 Heavens, or perhaps some matter there?”

Sheng Mei didn’t reply. Instead, she closed her eyes and returned to her meditation.

“You may leave.” Sheng Mei’s voice resounded in the air.

But Deep Child continued to say, “Hahaha! Junior-apprentice Sister, there is no need for you to continue daydreaming! All you need to do is be obedient and complete the orders you were given! You should know that regardless of what happens in the 33 Heavens, none of that matters because there is no significance to any of it at all! Everything that occurs is nothing but a farce playing out before the end of the world arrives. In the future, we will become legends, we will become eternal, and the entire 33 Heavens will belong to us. The lives of some ants or even many ants are meaningless to us. When a mountain floods, the ants will all drown, and even the strongest ants are no exception!”

Deep Child said, his words seeming to contain other meanings.

However, Sheng Mei seemed to not hear him at all as she continued to sit calmly in meditation.

Deep Child sneered, a wild and greedy light in his eye as he stared at Sheng Mei.

But at this time his expression froze. He could feel that the demon power in his surroundings had become chaotic!

This is…

Deep Child spread out his sense in all directions. Then, he was somewhat alarmed. Someone was making a breakthrough at this moment!

Chapter 2134 – Great Flood Crown Prince

The giant bone boat continued to break through the void like a lightning bolt.

In the 18 layers of the Dark Abyss, the Laws, the energies, everything was flooded with the wild aura of ancient times. This was true ancient times, a time that surpassed ten billion years and even a hundred billion years…

Lin Ming stood at the bow of the bone boat, looking down at the wild earth below him.

Those that lived in the 33 Heavens were enemies of the abyssal demons; this was destiny.

The abyssals’ ancient Demon God had used a heaven-defying method to find a road for the demon race whose destiny had been exhausted, and whose fate should have been to perish in the great Shattering that ended their universe. Now, after the birth of the new universe, they were doomed to fight a life and death war with each other.

For the 33 Heavens, abyssals were intruders and destroyers.

But to the abyssals, the 33 Heavens were trapped in a cage with a wild beast, and for a beast to eat the meat in front of them was perfectly natural and justified.

To discuss the rights and wrongs of this war was no longer meaningful. The only meaning to this war was… to completely annihilate the opponent!

As the bone boat flew through the 18th layer for 10 days, he finally saw vast wild plains appear at the end of his field of vision. And on one side of the plains was a giant cliff that seemed as if it had been cut out by the great axe of a divine god. Beyond this cliff was nothing but the endless starry skies!

This was the entrance to the Demon God’s Tomb. The Demon God’s Tomb was located in the center of the abyss’ 18th layer, and its entrance was this massive maw that led deeper into the world.

Beneath the earth lay the starry space.

And at this time, Lin Ming could see dark purple fortresses floating above the distant plains.

These fortresses resembled giant jellyfish. They floated hundreds of thousands of feet above the ground, with hundreds of tentacles that fell down to the earth.

“Those are the flying fortresses of the Great Flood Demon Kingdom. It looks like those fellows arrived earlier than we did.”

The one who spoke was Deep King Road’s Elder Deep Epoch. As he gazed outwards, there was a thoughtful light in his eyes.

“Great Flood Demon Kingdom…”

Lin Ming muttered to himself. The abyss had six great influences, and these influences had split into two groups of three that then joined with smaller influences to form an alliance.

These two alliances respectively took Deep King Road and the Great Flood Demon Kingdom as their heads; each was opposed to the other.

If this were the abyss’ 17th layer, then they could give face to each other and live peacefully alongside one another, occasionally even cooperating on the surface.

But in the Demon God’s Tomb, if these two hostile forces met then there would only be a single outcome – kill!

Because the Demon God’s Tomb contained many lucky chances and advantages.

One of the most desired aspects of the Demon God’s Tomb was a type of unique energy that existed there. The essence of this energy was spread down from the previous universe, and was the purified energy of demons that had existed 100 billion years ago.

This demon energy had once been in the bodies of peerless Demon Kings that existed 100 billion years ago.

This energy had been carefully refined and purified by these Demon Kings, and they even fused in their own lifetime’s worth of knowledge and the essence of the endless Laws they understood.

These energies had been accumulated over billions upon billions of years, constantly fusing and brewing in the Demon God’s Tomb. In terms of quality it reached inconceivable heights, and in the outside world just a single wisp would be considered a supreme treasure.

The abyssals called it – the power of demon gods.

When an abyssal entered the Demon God’s Tomb, their most important task was to refine this power of demon gods.

The power of demon gods had a spiritual intelligence of its own. When enough gathered, it would temporarily manifest on the surface of an abyssal in the form of a tattoo. Every abyssal would develop different tattoos, but the images they formed were all shared a similar design; the pattern of a fierce demon.

This design was called a totem by the abyssal demons.

Nether, Evil, Deep, Eon, Flood, Famine, the reason these six super abyssals were called ‘totem level abyssals’ was because of the totem of the power of demon gods.

In the Dark Abyss, this sort of totem was considered the symbol of a powerhouse at the limit of True Divinity, or even one that had stepped Beyond Divinity.

When an abyssal entered the Demon God’s Tomb, having a greater number of totems appear on their body represented that they absorbed more of the power of demon gods, and thus their cultivation had also risen higher.

After this abyssal left the Demon God’s Tomb, these totems would slowly fuse into their body and vanish from sight. The totems would subtly transform into true strength, giving them astonishing benefits.

All abyssals that entered the Demon God’s Tomb hoped to obtain more power of demon gods from within.

Because there was a limit to the speed at which abyssals could absorb the power of demon gods, and because they wanted to obtain more, they chose another method; that was to kill other abyssals and steal away the power of demon gods that they had already absorbed.

This was a kind of shortcut.

This also meant that after entering the Demon God’s Tomb, there was doomed to be a great slaughterfest!

But besides the power of demon gods, there were also many inheritances and treasures left behind in the Demon God’s Tomb by ancient peerless Demon Kings.

To the abyssals, all of these things were a tremendous fortune and lucky chance!

Not just that, but because the Demon God’s Tomb was nourished by the incomparably pure power of demon gods, all kinds of miraculous medicines would be bred, as well as strange and precious beasts, heavenly materials, and all sorts of lucky chances. If one managed to somehow pick up a world-shocking treasure, it wouldn’t be strange at all.

Treasures, the power of demon gods, inheritances, and even the final qualifications for the test of the abyssal ritual, all of this combined together meant that there was inevitably a fight to the death!

“You’re about to go down shortly. After entering the Demon God’s Tomb, there is no need to show mercy to any abyssal from the Flood Alliance that you see. Just kill them off.”

Elder Deep Epoch coldly said. The Flood Alliance he referred to was the alliance organized by the Great Flood Demon Kingdom.

“As for the abyssals in our Deep Alliance, if you encounter each other than do not kill the other party, otherwise you will have to pay a corresponding price.”

As Elder Deep Epoch spoke these second words, warning flashed in his eyes.

The Deep Alliance didn’t exist in just name and word alone. When the numerous abyssals left for the Demon God’s Tomb they had already formed a vow through a Deep King Contract. If those in the same alliance slaughtered each other then they would be punished by the Deep King Contract.

However, this so-called Deep King Contract in truth couldn’t be considered too well devised, and the punishments were also bearable to an extent.

Thus, if one truly came across world-shocking lucky chances, then even abyssals in the same alliance could rely on each other. One had to consider whether or not those lucky chances were worth paying the cost of the penalty.

Thus, all members of the Deep Alliance that entered the Demon God’s Tomb this time had varying thoughts in mind. All of them knew the unspoken rules of the alliance – if they encountered the hostile alliance then they would first work together to eliminate the forces of this hostile alliance. Then, they would consider how the benefits would be distributed internally. If they could come to a peaceful resolution then that would be for the best.

Otherwise, everything would be decided by force.

At this time the giant bone boat slowly descended.

The Deep Alliance’s station was separated from the Flood Alliance’s station by a hundred miles. Each side looked at the other as they swung about in the air.

Several hours later, both sides sent out their leading Elders as well as the numerous higher abyssals that would enter the Demon God’s Tomb. They arrived at the cliff in the wilderness and the endless starry skies located deep underground.

Within the crowd of people, Lin Ming silently judged the abyssals from the Flood Alliance.

If Lin Ming didn’t consider himself, then the Flood Alliance had brought 12 True Divinity abyssals here, the same number that the Deep Alliance had brought.

These 12 abyssals were clearly the elite forces of the Flood Alliance!

At the front of these 12 abyssals stood a towering abyssal in purple armor. He had a human face and could even be considered extremely handsome. However, his entire body was covered in lizard scales and he had a thick tail extending from behind.

This human-faced abyssal was the current Crown Prince of the Great Flood Demon Kingdom.

“Middle True Divinity level…”

Lin Ming instantly thought as he looked at this Great Flood Crown Prince. However, he felt that there actually wasn’t any good reference value for knowing this Crown Prince’s cultivation level.

He could feel a dangerous aura from this Great Flood Crown Prince’s body. It was clear that this person’s strength was far more horrifying than what he estimated.

“Hehe, Ninth Elder is quite perceptive.”

A light voice suddenly sounded out near Lin Ming’s ears. He turned and saw that the one speaking was Deep Child.

Lin Ming felt his heart turn cold. His minor mental thoughts hadn’t appeared on his face and yet had been realized by this Deep Child.

Lin Ming remained quiet. He had always been wary of this Deep Child. In these past days he often saw Deep Child together with Sheng Mei, and he could also feel a dangerous aura coming from Deep Child. In fact, this aura was even somewhat heavier than the Great Flood Crown Prince’s…

“Rest easy.” Deep Child chuckled. He turned his head, no longer looking at Lin Ming. “If you are compared against this Great Flood Crown Prince, then I think the current you should try to avoid him as much as possible…”

Deep Child passed out this advice and them smiled as he walked towards the Great Flood Crown Prince. “Crown Prince Flood, I haven’t seen you in such a long time!” Deep Child’s rich and magnetic voice echoed through the air.

Chapter 2135 – Entering the Demon God’s Tomb

Deep Child and the Great Flood Crown Prince were old acquaintances. After they met, they exchanged some polite greetings and small talk. Although everyone knew they were just spouting empty wind, whether it was Deep Child or the Great Flood Crown Prince, their performance was perfectly on point, as if they truly were good friends.

At this time, more and more abyssals began to gather at the entrance of the Demon God’s Tomb. Besides the two great alliances, there were also many small influences trying to survive in the seams who also caught up.

Deep King Road and the Great Flood Demon Kingdom had especially left behind a small portion of the spots for these influences, and didn’t completely eliminate them from entering.

To share some of the benefits, this was how a true ruler survived.

And at this time the Demon God’s Tomb finally began to open.

From all around the quiet wilderness, energy began to stir, turning chaotic. Icy storms of energy emerged from the void, sweeping through the world.

The groups of Elders sent by the large sects stood around like towering mountain peaks, their eyes electric as they looked at the void.

When the storm was at its zenith, they lifted their hands up together and summoned six thick totem poles. These totem poles were engraved with images of demons; the totem poles were passed down from ancient times and were the easiest and most convenient method to open the Demon God’s Tomb. In fact, these six totem poles were the keys required to open the Demon God’s Tomb.

The six totem poles flew into the dark starry space, forming a hexagonal star design. With this star design the starry space began to ripple like waves in a stormy sea, distorting. Gradually from within the swirl of stars, a tear split open and dazzling black light gushed outwards.

This black light seemed like the source of all darkness. Profound and ancient, it fell down like a roiling black sea, shrouding the numerous powerhouses of the wilderness within.

For a time, Lin Ming felt his spatial ring violently shake, as if something were about to howl out!

He knew that this was the response of the Book of Eon.

When the Demon God’s Tomb was about to open, the strength of the Book of Eon connected with the power of the world, nearly breaking Lin Ming’s spatial ring to pieces.

This was why it was impossible to hide the ceremonial rites book, and why when everyone entered the Demon God’s Tomb it would be perfectly clear how many books there were and whose hands they were in!

In order to prevent his spatial ring exploding, Lin Ming took out the Book of Eon.

Woosh!

A forlorn energy shot out from the Book of Eon, blasting towards the dark and raging skies, shooting into the vortex of energy and fusing together with it!

And at this time, from not too far away from Lin Ming, two more divine lights shot into the skies!

These two divine lights naturally came from two other ceremonial rites books.

Lin Ming already knew that these two books were the Book of Nether and the Book of Evil.

The Book of Evil was in Sheng Mei’s hands, and ‘Evil’ was the ruler of the Demon Association.

Lin Ming once heard some rumors that Evil was still alive somewhere in the world, but it was only afterwards that he learned that these rumors were purposefully spread out by the Demon Association. Evil had truly died, but he didn’t die in the great war 10 billion years ago when the Dark Abyss fought with the 33 Heavens.

However, after that, Evil had been injured and its life essence slowly faded away until it perished.

The Demon Association intentionally hid this information behind a screen of rumors and fog in order to consolidate their own status.

The Book of Evil was in Sheng Mei’s hands but the Book of Nether was in the hands of the Great Flood Demon Kingdom. From this, one could see the feud between the six totem level influences; they each took the books of other sects to enter the Demon God’s Tomb.

The six ceremonial rites books had a mysterious connection with the world within the Demon God’s Tomb.

Abyssals that held a book of ceremonial rites would obtain an advantage. That was that the person who held one could absorb the power of demon gods at twice the effectiveness and half the effort!

This was also a reason why abyssals who held onto a book of ceremonial rites would be hated and targeted by all.

Without grasping true strength, to hold a ceremonial rites book was no different from seeking death.

Thus, when the Book of Eon in Lin Ming’s hand began to bloom with divine light, all of the abyssals in the Flood Alliance looked towards Lin Ming.

They had long since become aware that Sheng Mei had the Book of Evil, thus they didn’t find it strange at all. But, Lin Ming’s Book of Eon was information that had only been recently spread out. Although everyone knew that another ceremonial rites book appeared in the Deep Alliance, they thought that this newly appeared book should be in the hands of Deep Child.

But, it was in Lin Ming’s hands.

The Great Flood Crown Prince looked at Deep Child, a smile touching on his face. “Brother Deep Child, you’re more humble than you appear. You actually gave two ceremonial rites books to your junior-apprentice brother and junior-apprentice sister. What, are you lacking the courage to take a ceremonial rites book into the Demon God’s Tomb? Or, could it be said that this is only a smokescreen that you sent out, and after you enter the Demon God’s Tomb the book of ceremonial rites will be handed to you and this fellow will only be made into your shield?”

The Great Flood Crown Prince pointed at Lin Ming, a glint of ridicule in his eyes.

Deep Child laughed with confidence, “Treasures are for those who are able to hold onto them. Although my cultivation is a bit higher, it is only because I have been training for longer, so, my talent can only be considered decent at most. I actually cannot compare to my Deep King Road’s Holy Demoness nor can I compare to the Ancient Eon Sect’s Ninth Elder. Since my talent is inferior to others’, it isn’t strange if I give way to them!”

Deep Child’s words were all naturally spoken and caused the surrounding abyssals to be bewildered.

They all knew about Deep Child’s talent and it was rumored that he had incredible hidden depths; his true strength was terrifying.

The Holy Demoness was understandable. She had been famous for a long time, but Deep Child actually spoke honestly and said that he was inferior to this obscure Ninth Elder of the Ancient Eon Sect…

Thinking like this, many abyssals secretly paid attention to Lin Ming, all of them with different thoughts in mind. Some of them believed Deep Child’s words and were wary of him, but some of them saw Lin Ming’s upper Empyrean cultivation and killing intent started to flash in their eyes.

Lin Ming openly greeted all the gazes cast towards him. Deep Child’s words had pushed him directly onto the crest of the wind and waves.

However, Lin Ming knew that even if he didn’t say anything, he would still end up here because the Book of Eon was in his hands.

Compared to Sheng Mei who had accumulated fame and renown over all these years, it was far easier for Lin Ming to become the target of others!

And at this time in the endless starry skies of the wilderness, after the six totem poles absorbed the strength from the three ceremonial rites books, they began to hum and shake!

This shaking became increasingly fierce, until even the wild plains that everyone stood on began to tremble.

Large chunks of rock cracked open from the plains, rolling upwards as they were sucked into the endless starry skies.

More and more black light rose up all around the totem poles, filled with infinite mystical meanings. Trillions of Law runes floated within. With a loud cracking sound, space collapsed and a profound and infinite world slowly presented itself in the eyes of the abyssals present!

This world was the mysterious and ancient Demon God’s Tomb.

In order to open the Demon God’s Tomb, one first had to have the qualifications to enter it.

In the past when the demon race overcame the great Shattering and established the Dark Abyss, the Demon God’s Tomb became the smelting trial for the peerless children of heaven amongst the abyssals.

This mystical land could be called the reason for which countless powerhouses were born amongst the abyssals during all these years, the reason they were able to stand above the 33 Heavens in strength!

For all these years, at least 90% of the True Divinity level abyssals that were born in the Dark Abyss had entered the Demon God’s Tomb when they were at the Empyrean level.

During a trip into the Demon God’s Tomb, many Empyrean level abyssals would perish. But those that survived would soar into the skies.

Sometimes the Demon God’s Tomb wouldn’t open for 600-700 million years, and this would cause the number of True Divinities in the Dark Abyss to rapidly drop. From this alone, one could see the heaven-defying cultivation effects of the Demon God’s Tomb!

This valuable pressure naturally couldn’t be wasted on the bodies of mediocre trash. Thus, before entering the Demon God’s Tomb, these rippling black lights were the first test that those who entered faced.

The black light contained a pure demon energy. Only those with extraordinary talent, a solid foundation, and a tremendous amount of demonic energy within their bodies could cause this demon energy to resonate with them and finally enter.

As for those abyssals with lower levels of talent, they would be flushed out by the impact of this demon energy.

The surging demon energy was like a massive tide of the heavens and earth that swelled outwards. The wilderness shook, and for a time the entire underground starry skies were obscured.

Many Empyrean level abyssals stood in front of this tide and profoundly felt just how small they were. Compared to the countless ancient Demon Kings buried with the Demon God’s Tomb, they were insignificant.

“Let’s enter!”

Deep Child’s voice spread over the Deep Alliance. Many abyssals from the Deep Alliance grit their teeth, their bodies turning into beams of light that flew towards those horrifying waves of energy.

Chapter 2137 – Tracked

The terrain within the Demon God’s Tomb was extremely dangerous and cruel.

Some mountain peaks pierced into the skies, like great swords thrusting into the heavens.

Some places had cracked land, revealing fathomless black abysses.

In some other places one could see bones scattered all over the ground. These shattered bones were small and large and glittered like cracked black crystals.

Upon approaching these bones, one could feel a faint force field. In truth these bones had already been exhausted of their energies, and yet they still maintained a light force field that continued onwards, leaving one sighing with emotion.

Without a doubt, after the owners of these skeletons died, the energies in their bodies were similar to those Empyrean abyssals that had died, and had been absorbed by this world.

All that was left over were their broken bones and a light force field that lingered upon them. They would forever be buried here.

Thinking of this, Lin Ming felt something unusual.

Every time the Demon God’s Tomb opened, countless proud abyssal elites would converge towards this land.

These abyssal elites could absorb the unimaginably pure energy that had been refined over 100 billion years in the Demon God’s Tomb. But at the same time, over 80% of the abyssal elites would perish here.

The demon energy in their bodies and the strength of their blood vitality would be cleanly absorbed by this world.

Like this, energy went in and out, forming a particular balance that sent a chill down one’s spine.

This meant that the abyssals took the eliminated dead as fertilizer so that powerhouses could soar to even greater heights.

Thinking of this, Lin Ming sighed. The brutality and laws of the jungle that existed in the Dark Abyss weren’t as simple as that. Rather, they were the true laws of the jungle – laws where the strong ate the weak.

At this time, an amazing demon aura swiftly passed in front of him. A black ray of light flashed through the world, the intensity of the impact causing the earth to shake in waves.

From where the vibrations appeared in the void, the vague phantom of a fierce demon appeared in the black light. It slowly condensed, its demon energy gushing out into the world.

The demon roared, its voice echoing through the heavens and earth.

“The power of demon gods.”

Lin Ming narrowed his eyes. According to the jade slip, the power of demon gods had wandered about the Demon God’s Tomb for over 100 billion years, slowly forming a spiritual wisdom of its own. If one could smash these energies apart, they could obtain their essence.

The power of demon gods was one of the most important lucky chances of the Demon God’s Tomb. Many proud abyssal elites entered the Demon God’s Tomb specifically for this reason.

Lin Ming stepped forwards and his body vanished in the sky. Facing this flying demon, he punched out with his fist.

Peng!

With a loud shattering sound, the demon cried out in misery before disintegrating into smoke and dust. It turned into a stream of black energy that began to dissipate into the world.

Lin Ming reached out a hand and slowly gathered this energy.

“It really is pure…”

Lin Ming was shocked. In fact, describing this power of demon gods with the word ‘pure’ really wasn’t enough. Lin Ming had seen all sorts of lucky chances in his life, but solely in terms of the quality of energy found in mystic realms, nothing could compare with this power of demon gods in front of him.

This was because out of all the mystic realms that Lin Ming had seen in his life, even the one that existed the longest wasn’t even a tenth of the age of the Demon God’s Tomb.

The energy within the Demon God’s Tomb had been purified and refined for all this time, like wine brewed from heavenly materials. After being fermented for 100 billion years it had become a peerless vintage.

Every abyssal that entered the Demon God’s Tomb was a lover of such a wine, and the taste of it was difficult to put into words.

Lin Ming used his soul force to control the wisps of demon energy that gathered in his palm. He formed it into the phantom of a small demon, and this demon phantom seemed incredibly lifelike, as if it were alive.

Lin Ming clenched his fist tightly and directly absorbed this demon phantom.

In the next moment, a blurry mark appeared on his arm.

This mark was a faint demon tattoo; this was the so-called totem.

For every abyssal that entered the Demon God’s Tomb, there would be a limit to the number of totems they could form from the power of demon gods.

Some could form eight, some could form ten, some could form 15. But, once they surpassed their limits this number wouldn’t increase anymore.

The limiting number of totem tattoos that formed would depend on an individual’s own martial talent and potential.

Of course, the more totem tattoos that one could form the better it would be. However, in truth, because the Demon God’s Tomb was a land filled with frigid slaughter, the more totems one formed the more one became a delicious plump sheep in the eyes of others. For the weaker and smaller abyssals that entered this mystic realm, they were already thanking the heavens and earth if they could form three or four totems and survive to leave.

To them the totem limit wasn’t too meaningful.

By this time, Lin Ming could see that at the ends of the horizon there seemed to be abyssal demons already beginning a scrambling massacre due to the struggle for the power of demon gods.

But this was only a small fight. Once more and more treasures appeared then the slaughter would escalate until the entire Demon God’s Tomb turned into a bloody hell.

Lin Ming didn’t pause here for long.

According to the jade slip he reviewed, the number of lucky chances was much smaller on the edges of the Demon God’s Tomb, and the quality and density of the power of demon gods was also lower. The truly precious treasures were located deep in the Demon God’s Tomb.

Of course, there were more dangers there too.

Lin Ming flew towards the depths of the Demon God’s Tomb. Its space had an extremely great difference from that of the outside.

The Demon God’s Tomb was a mysterious great world built to resist the great Shattering of the past universe. Here, the intensity of space and had been tempered for 100 billion years and flooded with the flesh and blood of countless Demon Kings, and had now reached a nearly indestructible state.

Even with Lin Ming’s absolute strength and his comprehension of the Space Laws, he still couldn’t freely utilize the power of space nor could he distort space.

And he definitely couldn’t break through space and hasten his pace with great void shifts.

Thus, whether one was a True Divinity or Empyrean, they would have to honestly and simply fly. And because of the omnipresent force field, the speed of all abyssals was suppressed.

But although Lin Ming was only flying along and didn’t pause much, the power of demon gods that he condensed was actually no less than that of other abyssals.

Lin Ming seemed to possess appeal to these demonic things.

Many abyssals would search in all directions for the power of demon gods, spending several hours before finding a little. As for absorbing it, there might even be conflict in doing that, because if other abyssals were there then there would be a battle to decide ownership of the power of demon gods.

However, Lin Ming only flew forwards and yet demonic spirits formed the power of demon gods and approached him on their own initiative.

In fact, they were not actually looking for Lin Ming, but for the Book of Eon that he carried with him.

This mysterious and ancient demon book possessed a strange aura and special energy fluctuations. In the Demon God’s Tomb, the Book of Eon was like a bright light that attracted moths, or a fresh dewy flower that attracted honeybees, constantly drawing in demonic spirits condensed from the power of demon gods.

These demonic spirits weren’t too strong. Lin Ming easily struck them down, and soon, over time, Lin Ming’s first totem on his arm was already a third completed.

In forming totems, the further one went the more difficult it became. But, Lin Ming wasn’t in a hurry. This opening of the Demon God’s Tomb would continue for a long period of time. At the shortest it would be seven or eight years, and it might even go on for dozens or hundreds of years.

In the history of the Dark Abyss there were times when the Demon God’s Tomb opened for one or two thousand years.

The longer the Demon God’s Tomb was open, then the more time the abyssals that entered would have to seek out lucky chances and the power of demon gods. Thus when they emerged, they could also have large benefits.

But at the same time, there would be a longer period of slaughter so fewer abyssals would be able to walk out alive.

Lin Ming didn’t look for trouble, but that didn’t meant trouble wouldn’t come knocking on his door.

Two days later, Lin Ming felt threads of light killing intent waft over his back like a cool spring breeze.

His thoughts stirred; an abyssal had targeted him!

His pace didn’t slow down in the least but he did release his sense in all directions. However, what was amazing was that he didn’t find who it was that was following him. This surprised him. It meant that this person who was hiding was at a level that surpassed his expectations.

“It shouldn’t be the Great Flood Crown Prince…”

This thought immediately flashed through Lin Ming’s mind and he calmed his mood. He began to fuse the soul force of his true self into his sense.

Lin Ming’s true self contained the Eternal Soul, and the strength of his soul force wasn’t something that common abyssals could compare with. And after investigating the situation, his thoughts stirred once more; it seemed things were different from what he had thought.

He fell into thought for a moment and then slowly changed directions, flying towards a far off direction of the Demon God’s Tomb…

Chapter 2139 – Lin Ming’s Strength

Before the Yin Yang Twin Ghosts could react, a heavy mist suddenly erupted from Lin Ming’s body. This mist carried with it a deep and powerful strength that proliferated through the air all around; this was Lin Ming’s grandmist space.

The grandmist spread within the ancient bronze bell, completely sealing up the already sealed battlefield.

Immediately, the Yin Yang Twin Ghosts raised their guards. An upper Empyrean was surrounded by two True Divinities in a sealed space, but not only did he not panic but he even laid down a force field to block off the area; it seemed he wanted to fight some sort of final battle.

If such a person wasn’t an idiot or crazy, then they were someone who had more than enough confidence in their own strength.

And, when recalling the fact that Deep King Road allowed Lin Ming to carry the Book of Eon into the Demon God’s Tomb, the chances of Lin Ming being an idiot were near zero.

“How interesting. We are going to kill you, but it looks like you want to eat us up instead. Are you afraid that we are going to run away?”

“A mere upper Empyrean actually wants to contend with us two brothers…”

The Yin Yang Twin Ghosts cackled, their voices gloomy and evil. They spread out, standing on both sides of Lin Ming. And at this time Lin Ming was continuing to bolster his grandmist force field, blocking out this space.

Lin Ming’s eyes swept over the arms beneath the voluminous robes of the Yin Yang Twin Ghosts. On each of their arms was a totem mark.

The Yin Yang Twin Ghosts’ totem marks were actually not much dimmer than Lin Ming’s was. Lin Ming possessed the Book of Eon so his speed in absorbing the power of demon gods should have been amongst the fastest of all, yet he wasn’t able to surpass the Yin Yang Twin Ghosts. This meant that the Yin Yang Twin Ghosts had killed a great number of abyssals from the Deep Alliance before this.

Only by killing other abyssals and plundering their totems could one rapidly accumulate the power of demon gods.

“After killing them, my first totem mark should be able to reach perfection, and it might even go a little beyond that… unfortunately, the Book of Eon draws the hate of others too easily so now I must fight True Divinities. If I were able to delay this for a few days and allow them to gather more power of demon gods before I killed them, then my harvests would have been even greater…”

As Lin Ming was thinking this, the Yin Yang Twin Ghosts had already begun to rush towards him!

They were skilled in coordinating their attacks. The moment they moved, they had already blocked out all of Lin Ming’s angles of avoidance!

Facing Lin Ming, neither of them held back. Lin Ming’s actions of sealing away the battlefield once more had caused them to become wary of him.

The black and white light of abyssals flooded the battlefield.

The Yin Yang Twin Ghosts struck out with an extremely cunning attack trajectory and also attacked from two sides at once. For a normal abyssal this would have been difficult to fend off.

However, facing such an attack, Lin Ming only sneered.

In this instant Lin Ming’s inner world opened and a raging and boundless energy wildly gushed out!

This sort of energy was drastically different from the demon energies within the Dark Abyss. That demonic abyssal energy was fierce and cold, filled with thick killing intent. But, this sort of energy was vast and broad, yet it didn’t lose its sharp edge.

This was the power of divinity from the 33 Heavens, and also the strength from unifying true essence, spirit essence, and astral essence!

Ho - !

Like a dragon roaring out into the horizon, an incredible hum rang through the ancient bronze bell, wildly reverberating all around.

Lin Ming’s true self rushed out from his demon avatar’s inner world!

Like a treasure sword being unsheathed from a thousand years of dust, divine light recklessly shot out, nearly piercing through the ancient bronze bell.

“What!?”

The Yin Yang Twin Ghosts were panic-stricken. In an instant, Lin Ming had become two.

Moreover, what shocked them the most was that this Lin Ming no longer had the appearance of an abyssal, but rather had the appearance of someone of the ancient races, or even someone from the dark angel race!

From looks alone it was impossible for them to determine whether Lin Ming’s true self was an abyssal demon or not. But, the vast power of divinity exuding from Lin Ming’s true self allowed them to instantly confirm that this person who suddenly appeared was neither an abyssal nor someone from the ancient races.

Rather, he came from… the 33 Heavens!

Thinking of this possibility, the hearts of the Yin Yang Twin Ghosts quaked. Someone from the 33 Heavens, how could they appear in the Dark Abyss?

Could this be some sort of great plot?

Before they could respond, Lin Ming’s true self suddenly attacked!

Lin Ming raised his spear and thrust outwards. Spear light howled, seeming as if it could overturn the universe as it pierced towards the white-robed abyssal.

And at the same time, Lin Ming’s demon avatar also attacked. He grabbed a thick bone spear and pounded down at the black-robed abyssal!

Without a need to hide his strength any longer, without a need to hide his Laws, in this moment, seven great stars from the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace suddenly appeared above Lin Ming’s head. Endless starlight poured into the bodies of Lin Ming’s true self and his demon avatar, causing their strength to rise to a new limit.

Bang!

The Yin Yang Twin Ghosts simply weren’t able to resist the raging impact at all. The two of them miserably coughed as they were sent tumbling away.

Bang! Bang!

With two loud rings, the Yin Yang Twin Ghosts smashed into the ancient bronze bell, causing it to thunder out loud.

“What… what is going on!?”

The Yin Yang Twin Ghosts were bewildered. From this short glance, they faintly realized that this person from the 33 Heavens who suddenly appeared had a cultivation inferior to that of a True Divinity, but, how could someone who hadn’t reached True Divinity possess such a freakish level of strength?

One abyssal, one life form from the 33 Heavens, could they have been one body to begin with?

“Take away the bell!”

The black-robed abyssal shouted out loud. The situation had undergone heaven-shaking changes. They had already lost all control of what was occurring. This life form from the 33 Heavens had mixed itself into the Dark Abyss, and not just that but their strength was incredible and they obviously had dark intentions. This sort of important discovery needed to be reported!

“You want to escape? Keep on dreaming!”

Lin Ming’s true self sneered. At this time, the inner world of Lin Ming’s true self also opened.

Shua! Shua! Shua!

Three more figures flew out!

These were Lin Ming’s avatars of essence, energy, and divine. Now that Lin Ming didn’t need to hide his strength any longer he could finally go all-out!

Roar!

The cry of a dragon echoed from Lin Ming’s inner world. The little black dragon that had been hiding in Lin Ming’s inner world throughout his entire time in the Dark Abyss finally joined the fray!

Little Black had long since reached the limits of an Empyrean. Although its strength still fell short of that of a True Divinity, it could rely on its powerful vitality and potent body to act as a deterrent in battle.

Within the ancient bronze bell, even though Little Black had shrunk its body to an infinitesimally small portion of its original size, it still took up nearly half of the available space. It immediately became crowded inside!

Little Black was like a giant wall of meat. When combined with the grandmist space, it blocked the ancient bronze bell from opening.

Thick killing intent flashed in Lin Ming’s eyes. He had planned from the very start to reveal all cards in his hands, because he could not allow a single one of these abyssals to leave.

He had to cut down the Yin Yang Twin Ghosts here, otherwise the consequences would be unimaginable!

When Lin Ming was at the middle Empyrean realm and hadn’t yet opened the Twofold Dao Palace, he had used all means and had managed to slay a lower True Divinity. Now, in this sealed space with his strength greatly enhanced, it wouldn’t be difficult for him to eliminate these two lower True Divinities.

“The power of Yin and Yang!”

Lin Ming’s true self and his demon avatar moved together. Their four hands moved as one, drawing a primal chaos diagram with their hands. Endless power of divinity and demons rushed out from Lin Ming’s true self and his demon avatar, fusing together to form a yin yang wheel.

This giant wheel sliced down onto the black-robed abyssal!

The black-robed abyssal was panic-stricken. At the same time, the white-robed abyssal was diverted by Little Black and the three avatars, completely unable to help.

The reason that the Yin Yang Twin Ghosts were known to be powerful was because the two brothers could coordinate without the slightest gap. But once they were split apart, their combat strength would drop precipitously.

When they faced Lin Ming it had been two against one, but now it had become two against six; the sudden change in disparity could be imagined!

The black-robed abyssal’s complexion rapidly changed. He opened his lips and a small green fork came spinning out.

Countless evil spirits lingered atop this small fork. They emitted pained hisses and wails, causing the small fork to seem extremely fierce!

Facing this small fork, Lin Ming’s true self and demon avatar simply disregarded it. They savagely pressed down the yin yang wheel.

Kacha!

With a loud explosive sound, the small green fork was sent flying away!

The yin yang wheel flew down without slowing. At the same time, the faint phantom of a black Phantom appeared behind the wheel.

In this crucial life or death moment, the black-robed abyssal wildly roared. He summoned all the demon power in his body and smashed out his fist onto the yin yang wheel.

In the next moment, a wild vortex of energy swirled through the entire sealed space. Beneath Lin Ming’s suppression, the explosive energy didn’t sweep outwards so that the ancient bronze bell wouldn’t break.

Rather, these energies all swept towards the black-robed abyssal.

The black-robed abyssal spat out a mouthful of black blood as he was sent flying away!

Chapter 2141 – Cultivating

To kill others and wrest away their power of demon gods, this would forever be the fastest method.

The Demon God’s Tomb had only opened several days ago so the Yin Yang Twin Ghosts had accumulated a limited amount of the power of demon gods. Even so, after killing them, Lin Ming’s first totem marked directly reached perfection.

Not just that, but the second totem mark also started to slowly appear. Lin Ming could feel that even though this second totem mark appeared slightly different from the first one, if he wanted to completely manifest it then it would require much more power of demon gods.

The Demon God’s Tomb would remain open for a long time. Lin Ming absolutely had the option of slowly gathering the power of demon gods and didn’t need to be hurried. However, he was worried that if he stayed in the Demon God’s Tomb for too long then he might find that the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had already left seclusion.

At that time, humanity would once more fall into dire peril!

As for contending with the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, it would all depend on Divine Dream’s leadership. But no matter what happened it was sure to be a difficult and blood-filled battle.

All of these thoughts flashed through Lin Ming’s mind. He shook his head, placing these worries in the back of his mind. These were inevitable matters to begin with, and all Lin Ming could do now was do everything he could to increase his own strength.

There were far too many enemies he had to face.

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, the unfathomably deep Soul Emperor, and even the entire Dark Abyss!

Each one of these enemies was stronger than the last. They pressed down on Lin Ming’s shoulders, but with his current strength he wasn’t able to shake any one of them.

Still, Lin Ming didn’t give in. This pressure on him was also his great lucky chance.

And if he wanted to reach the peak of martial arts, he needed such a lucky chance.

Since ancient times, peerless powerhouses often required more than just heaven-defying talent and destiny; they also needed the momentum of the world to be pushing them towards greater accomplishments.

10 billion years ago, the Asura Road Master and Immortal Sovereign had been in such a situation when they faced the invasion of the abyssal demons.

100 billion years ago, the Demon God also experienced such a situation facing the great Shattering of the demon universe.

This is what others meant when they said situations made the hero.

The current Lin Ming also stood atop this wave that swept over the world.

He was pushed to his current position, and if he could stand proudly where he was then he would become a legend that would be passed down for over a hundred billion years!

……………….

The earth was boundless and barren. In the world of the Demon God’s Tomb, besides demonic spirits, there was no other life. The only lives that stood out were the other abyssal trial challengers.

But, they were enemies that could kill you at any moment.

This was a world of deathly stillness, but also a world where dangers pervaded every corner. To stay in such a world for dozens, hundreds, or even thousands of years and withstand endless loneliness, infinite slaughter, and desolate cultivation, even someone with powerful nerves and tenacious willpower would find it hard to bear.

Peng!

Amongst the midst of scattered demon bones, a brilliant light suddenly burst out like fireworks in the night sky, dissipating between the heavens and earth.

With it, a miserable cry echoed out. An abyssal demon tumbled onto the ground in distress, his body covered with blood.

Lin Ming grasped a bone spear and quietly followed him from behind, like a devil emerging from the depths of hell.

“Stretch out your arm!”

Lin Ming’s voice was cold and brooked no resistance.

The abyssal he struck down from the air came from the Flood Alliance and only had an Empyrean level cultivation. Facing Lin Ming’s pressure, this abyssal nearly suffocated.

It was impossible for the abyssal to resist Lin Ming’s aura. He obediently stretched out his arm, and then Lin Ming reached out sharp claws to wrap around this arm. With a bit of strength in his fingers, five sharp nails pierced into the abyssal’s body.

Laws of Famine – Swallowing!

Lin Ming revolved the Swallowing Laws, savagely sucking out the pure power of demon gods within this abyssal’s body.

A moment later, the abyssal lay splayed out on the ground like a dead dog, his entire body soaked in a cold sweat. In that instant just now he had felt as if his entire bloodline had been sucked out by Lin Ming.

However, he didn’t die and Lin Ming didn’t seem to have any intention of killing him.

Lin Ming waved his hand and said, “You can screw off!”

Hearing these words, the abyssal was dazed, in disbelief that he could survive this.

“Are you not leaving?”

A cold light flashed in Lin Ming’s eyes and the abyssal quickly scurried away.

Lin Ming took a deep breath, drawing in every wisp of the power of demon gods into his body so that he didn’t waste even the tiniest bit.

He opened his eyes, slowly turning towards a position somewhere in the void and faintly said, “Since you’ve come, you might as well come out.”

From the silent void, loud laughter suddenly echoed out. “Hahaha! Ninth Elder’s senses are truly sharp!”

With this voice, a hand suddenly appeared and ripped open the barrier of a concealing array formation. An abyssal walked out – this was Deep Child!

After being in the Demon God’s Tomb for a long time, this was the first time Lin Ming encountered Deep Child.

Lin Ming didn’t know how much power of demon gods Demon Child had absorbed. Facing Deep Child, Lin Ming was deeply wary of him. He could feel that this Deep Child was like a cold and ruthless wild beast, hiding his fangs until the moment came to reveal them.

“Interesting, you actually let that Flood Alliance abyssal go.” Deep Child said, a thoughtful light in his eyes as he stared at the fleeing abyssal from the Flood Alliance.

“But… you shouldn’t be some kind of blindly benevolent fool.”

As Deep Child spoke he looked towards Lin Ming. Lin Ming didn’t reply, instead glaring back at Deep Child and coldly asking, “Just what are you looking for me for?”

He was already prepared for a fight. Although those in the Deep Alliance had made an oath, such an oath likely wouldn’t have any binding force on Deep Child.

Deep Child chuckled. “This is just a chance encounter. Since you don’t wish to talk to me much, then… let us meet once again in the deepest depths of the Demon God’s Tomb!”

As Deep Child said this, he turned and left.

From start to finish he never attacked Lin Ming and didn’t even reveal a bit of killing intent.

Lin Ming frowned and watched as Deep Child slowly disappeared from sight.

He didn’t know what tricks Deep Child was playing at. Deep Child clearly possessed formidable strength and yet he restrained himself this entire time.

Deep Child didn’t try to take his ceremonial rites book nor did he seek out the Great Flood Crown Prince for some sort of final showdown. In these past months, the Deep Alliance and Flood Alliance had come into conflict numerous times, but there had yet to be a great battle with deep losses yet.

Lin Ming shook his head, no longer thinking about it. His time in the Demon God’s Tomb was extremely precious; he needed to grasp every moment he could to raise his strength.

As for whatever traps or secrets were in the Demon God’s Tomb, or whatever plots Deep Child was planning against him, only when he had sufficient strength could he deal with these things.

Lin Ming’s figure flickered and he flew away. He searched for his next target, whether it was a demonic spirit or more abyssal prey.

This was already Lin Ming’s tenth month in the Demon God’s Tomb.

The Demon God’s Tomb was extremely broad. In these ten months, Lin Ming travelled, spending the majority of his time in quiet cultivation.

Slaughter and cultivation, this was the entirety of the Demon God’s Tomb.

Lin Ming didn’t want to involve himself in the great war between the Flood Alliance and Deep Alliance. But, as long as he met someone from the Flood Alliance he would attack them without hesitation.

They were his prey.

This venture into the Demon God’s Tomb was meant to be a grand slaughterfest to begin with. Since Lin Ming joined in, he naturally would make use of these rules.

As for things like mercy or morality, to talk about such things now was foolishness.

During these ten months, Lin Ming’s name also spread out. There was no longer an abyssal stupid enough to consider Lin Ming as a mere upper Empyrean abyssal.

Because no one knew Lin Ming’s true name and only knew of him as the Ninth Elder, slowly, the abyssals of the Flood Alliance gave Lin Ming a new name – the Ninth War Demon.

These days, in particular the Empyrean level abyssals of the Flood Alliance, they all shivered upon hearing the name of the Ninth War Demon.

But no matter how infamous Lin Ming’s exploits, he didn’t kill every Flood Alliance abyssal that he saw. He discovered that by using Famine’s Swallowing Laws, he could easily draw out the power of demon gods from the bodies of other abyssals.

Thus, as long as some abyssals were willing to offer him their power of demon gods, he would mostly let them live.

This was no some act of mercy, but because Lin Ming had his own plan. He did this because he wanted to raise his cultivation speed up as fast as possible.

Lin Ming had his own ambitions. He wanted to accumulate his totem tattoos to the limit in the shortest time possible.

According to the jade slip, the more power of demon gods that a trial challenger possessed, the greater their chances of withstanding the inheritance of totem abyssals and passing the abyssal ritual.

Moreover, once he succeeded in receiving this inheritance, then this power of demon gods would also be perfectly absorbed by the trial challenger during the process, sublimating into a part of their strength.

Chapter 2142 – Cultivation Shortcut

Within the Demon God’s Tomb, the slaughter continued grinding on.

Perhaps it was abyssals slaughtering demonic spirits to absorb their power of demon gods, or perhaps it was abyssals slaughtering abyssals to steal their achievements.

And like this, three years passed.

In a black swamp within the Demon God’s Tomb, Lin Ming was slowly absorbing a wisp of pure power of demon gods. He glanced at the totem marks on his arm; currently he had already condensed his sixth totem.

In these past three years Lin Ming’s cultivation speed was equivalent to the results of training for dozens of years outside.

He had fully stabilized his upper Empyrean boundary and his cultivation was rapidly progressing at 10,000 miles a day as he approached the limits of an Empyrean.

Seeing the sixth totem mark about to be completed, Lin Ming hesitated for a moment. He radiated his sense outwards. Then, his lips slowly curved up.

In an area not too far away, he saw that it was time to harvest some of the previous arrangements he made…

He slowly rose upwards, turning into a beam of light that shot towards the direction his sense told him to go in.

He was extremely fast like a coursing lightning bolt. In a quarter hour of time, he had already flown to his destination.

Here there was a canyon. And deep in the canyon was a concealing array formation.

This was an Empyrean level array formation, but to Lin Ming it simply existed in name only.

Lin Ming raised his right fist and demon power shivered as it stirred in his body.

Kacha!

A fist punched out, smashing into this concealing array formation.

“What? What happened!?”

After the concealing array formation exploded, several abyssals rose up, bewildered.

They had established a momentary resting spot here some time ago. Even for an Empyrean, if they were to participate in endless days of cultivation and slaughter they would still feel mentally worn out and need to rest.

They would normally gather here and there were abyssals that were specifically charged with being on lookout and guardian array formations. But today, all of these precautions had failed.

It was only when someone came knocking at their door and the array formation exploded apart did they respond.

If someone could quietly approach and then easily smash apart their hidden array formation, such an opponent was likely at the True Divinity level!

A True Divinity level opponent wasn’t someone they could deal with!

However, as they rushed out and saw this intruder, their complexions suddenly turned incredibly ugly.

“The Ninth War Demon!”

“Y-you… it’s you again!”

Those that gathered in his canyon were Empyrean level abyssals of the Flood Alliance. In the Demon God’s Tomb they were considered weaklings, and it was always easier for weaklings to survive if they joined forces.

In these past days, they had relied on their teamwork to accumulate a great deal of the power of demon gods. They had always been careful in their actions lest they become prey for True Divinity abyssals of the Deep Alliance.

However, what was incomparably sad was that in these past three years, they had already bumped into this dark star known as Lin Ming twice.

The first time was two and a half years ago. Not too long after they entered the Demon God’s Tomb they fought with the Empyrean level abyssals of the Deep Alliance until they finally encountered Lin Ming.

Because of the massive disparity in strength they were beaten to the ground. But, what was strange was that Lin Ming actually didn’t kill them and instead let them go.

They originally rejoiced in such merciful actions, and at the same time they also laughed at Lin Ming for being stupid.

But after a year and a half passed, they actually encountered Lin Ming in this dangerous mystic realm once more. Lin Ming still didn’t kill them. He didn’t even take the cultivation methods or heavenly materials that they found so far, but only took away all the power of demon gods they had gathered.

This made them so depressed they nearly vomited blood. But, at least they passed through this danger with their lives intact and also had some minor harvests. As long as there was life, there was hope, and they started from the beginning all over again.

Now this was the third time they encountered Lin Ming!

For a time, the faces of these abyssals turned blue.

“You should all not want to die right? Hand over your power of demon gods! Obediently follow my orders and I will not kill you, otherwise, none of you will escape here alive. You should all know that I possess the ability to make sure none of you will be able to escape!”

Lin Ming’s words were overbearingly tyrannical. The lungs of these Flood Alliance abyssals nearly burst open with rage. They had gathered their power of demon gods after so much time and effort and yet Lin Ming wanted to savagely steal it all away.

“You… did you use some secret technique to follow us?”

An abyssal suddenly sucked in a deep breath. To be found once by Lin Ming was normal, to be found twice could be called a coincidence, but to be found a third time… how could this be possible!?

Even if they had bad luck it shouldn’t be this bad!

Upon hearing this abyssal’s question, a cold light flashed in Lin Ming’s eyes. Lin Ming traced his spatial ring and the surrounding temperature suddenly and precipitously dropped.

These abyssals felt as if they had all been caught by the scruffs of their neck and none of them dared to speak.

They were already sure that Lin Ming had some unknown methods to follow them. Moreover, when Lin Ming initially didn’t kill them but let them go, this wasn’t some random act of benevolent mercy, but because he wanted to fatten them up before harvesting them.

Thinking of this, the complexions of these abyssals turned darkly ugly. Those that were able to enter the Demon God’s Tomb were all proud children of heaven, and yet they were being raised as if they were farm animals.

“This demon, he is too evil!”

“How could a tracking mark have been placed on us… before this we gathered with His Highness the Crown Prince but His Highness didn’t tell us we were being tracked!”

The Crown Prince that these Flood Alliance abyssals spoke of was naturally the Great Flood Crown Prince.

The Great Flood Crown Prince was formidable, but the tracking mark that Lin Ming left on these abyssals was formed from his battle spirit.

To an abyssal, a battle spirit was a strange and relatively unknown thing. Perhaps a battle spirit might not be able to play any role in a battle between True Divinity level martial artists, but to use it to track someone was quite easy.

A battle spirit mark would nearly never wear away. Moreover, because abyssals were unfamiliar with battle spirits, they were extremely hard to detect.

With a battle spirit mark Lin Ming knew the locations of these abyssals from start to finish.

At a fixed interval of time he would harvest them. Otherwise, if too long of a time passed these abyssals might die somewhere and his arrangements would all be made useless.

“Hand over your power of demon gods or die.”

Lin Ming icily and decisively said. At the same time his grandmist force field spread out and covered this canyon. With just a hint of killing intent, these eight Empyrean level abyssals would never leave this place alive.

“Let’s attack together. I don’t believe that with so many of us working together we cannot deal with a single one!”

An enraged abyssal said, not believing in this situation. Lin Ming’s methods had touched his bottom line. Abyssals were born with violence and bloodthirst in their bones. In their lives they had only bullied others; just when had they been bullied like this?

Just as this abyssal finished shouting, before his voice fell a blinding spear light flashed through the void and caused a giant explosion to light up the world.

This abyssal cried out miserably and was sent soaring backwards. He smashed into the mountain rocks, his large body causing a sizable area of the divine iron-hard mountain walls to collapse.

Bang!

The rocks burst apart. This abyssal was drenched in blood and a bloody hole the size of a baby’s arm was pierced through his chest.

He hadn’t died, but in the Demon God’s Tomb such a heavy wound would mean that even if he didn’t die now, his future days would be a struggle indeed.

The complexions of the other abyssals changed. To hear rumors was one thing, but seeing was believing. An upper Empyrean abyssal had been easily and instantly felled by Lin Ming, and now they were filled with dread towards Lin Ming’s strength.

Because of what they saw, all these abyssals meekly handed over their power of demon gods.

Lin Ming used the Swallowing Laws to absorb all of this power. In a short incense stick of time, the sixth totem mark completely formed.

Everything was connected. To the current Lin Ming, whether it was the power of divinity, the power of demons or anything else, he could transform it into a part of his strength; he could already feel that he was making great strides towards the limits of an Empyrean.

After absorbing the power of demon gods from all these abyssals, Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred. The strength of the Magic Cube spread out from his inner world, forming a giant vortex that covered the surrounding area.

“You…”

These abyssals were panic-stricken. They thought that Lin Ming had lied to them and was about to kill them, but in the next moment, they lost their minds in the spiritual black hole created by the Magic Cube.

The abyssals all slumped over, one at a time.

Looking at these abyssals that fainted, Lin Ming unhurriedly used the Magic Cube to take away all memories of their power of demon gods being taken away today.

He used the Magic Cube’s illusionary abilities to create entirely new memories for these abyssals to explain why their power of demon gods had vanished.

Like this, although they would fall into extreme despair, they would still diligently continue to collect the power of demon gods to support Lin Ming’s cultivation efforts in the future.

Otherwise, anyone that knew they were being tracked by others and even raised like farm animals would develop thoughts of resistance. At this time, only an idiot would continue to gather the power of demon gods just to give it away to others. Even a normal person wouldn’t do this; they would rather not cultivate than vainly benefit someone else.

But if they forgot all of this then none of it would be a problem.

This also meant that Lin Ming could use this move multiple times.

It could be said that with the battle spirit tracking mark and Magic Cube, Lin Ming had found a cultivation shortcut in the Demon God’s Tomb.

Chapter 2144 – Underground World

“It’s you…”

Sheng Mei never thought that Lin Ming would appear at this time. As she looked at him, a complex light appeared in her eyes. In a sense, this black abyssal standing beside her was her fiancé.

Although Sheng Mei couldn’t accept him, she still had to acknowledge that she held some sort of peculiar and special feeling towards this fierce-looking abyssal.

Strong winds howled. At this time, Lin Ming stood a bit ahead of Sheng Mei. From Sheng Mei’s angle she could see the towering back of Lin Ming as well as the gloomy and uncertain face of the Great Flood Crown Prince.

Currently, the Great Flood Crown Prince was estimating whether or not he could severely wound Sheng Mei and Lin Ming in an incense stick of time if he attacked now.

But at this time, the ruptured earth below began to shiver and whine once more. The edges of the cracked earth started to close in, as if the opening were about to seal itself away.

That massive tide of demonic energy spouted out from the depths of that abyss, like the terrifying aura of a demon god being born into this world once more. But now it drew back, closing in, like a great maw that had opened and was now biting back down.

From everyone’s positions, they could see an infinite abyss exposed beneath that massive crack. It was clear that this terrifying and world-shaking aura was being transmitted from this underground abyss.

The entrance to this underground abyss was this massive crack, but now, the entrance was soon to be sealed up!

The several abyssal masters present were stunned. If they didn’t enter now and waited until the crack closed back up then it would be impossible for them to find another chance. To forcefully open up the ground in such a powerful mystic realm required abilities that no one here possessed.

“Go down!”

The Great Flood Crown Prince ordered after seeing the mystic realm about to close up in a dozen or so breaths of time. At this moment, he and the others couldn’t bother with Lin Ming anymore.

“We’re going also!”

Sheng Mei cried out. Without hesitation, her body plunged downwards like an arrow.

Lin Ming followed behind her. With the True Divinity Elder from Deep King Road, three figures plummeted like meteors, instantly crossing the 100,000 foot distance.

During this rapid flight, the Great Flood Crown Prince looked at Lin Ming and the others. After a moment of thought he decided not to attack. The crack was far too large; it would be impossible for him to stop them from entering. Even if he managed to force Sheng Mei and the others back, they would eventually enter from another direction.

If they entangled themselves in some melee, then if things didn’t go well even he wouldn’t be able to enter.

On the contrary, if they entered this underground space together then he could rely on his absolute strength to control the absolute initiative!

Woosh!

After Lin Ming and Sheng Mei flew down, other abyssal Empyreans unafraid of death followed them.

Even though they were aware of how perilous this mystic realm was, with such a lucky chance before them there would always be a chance for them to leap to the heavens in a single bound. In the face of such opportunity, there would always be desperados willing to recklessly risk their own lives.

The figures of numerous abyssals sank into that endless abyss. From left and right, the endless rock walls slowly squeezed in.

It was unknown how deep these rock walls extended. If they didn’t manage to enter the mystic realm before these rock walls closed up and were pushed between them then that would truly be a pitiful fate. With how hard the earth was in the Demon God’s Tomb, even a True Divinity level abyssal would have to spend a considerable amount of time and effort if they wanted to somehow force their way out. As for an Empyrean level abyssal, they weren’t too strong to begin with. If they were buried underground then they might not be able to crawl out for dozens or hundreds of years. It was even possible they would perish underground.

The True Divinity abyssals and those with similar strengths like Lin Ming and Sheng Mei were calm. But, the Empyrean level abyssals all had foreheads dropping with cold sweat. They continued to accelerate downwards, in fear that they would be caught in the pressure of the rock walls.

Woosh! Woosh! Woosh!

Abyssal after abyssal flew free from the underground crack. Then, infinite darkness flashed before them. In the next moment their field of vision suddenly widened and they saw that they arrived in a broad underground world.

Rumble rumble rumble!

Above their heads the earth began to close up; the entrance had been blocked.

During their hasty flight just then, after a brief estimation, everyone realized that this place was at least a thousand miles underground.

To suddenly be sealed in a mystic realm over a thousand miles belowground, many Empyrean abyssals felt their hearts racing. Such a mystic realm, it shouldn’t be inescapable right? If it were then that would truly be tragic.

Lin Ming looked at this underground world. He could not see where the end was and it wasn’t pitch black either; rather, there were shimmering sparks of light that overflowed from the rocks below, somewhat dimly.

But a True Divinity could still use their sense to perceive their surroundings in a completely pitch black world. Moreover, there was light here already, so it wasn’t any different from daytime to them.

Underground, rocky stalagmites littered the floor. And between many of these giant stone peaks there was a lake that was extremely eye-catching.

This lake was dark gray in color. It was around a hundred miles in diameter and covered a vast area.

The surface of this lake wasn’t calm. Fist-sized bubbles rose up and broke into the air, as if this were a pool of heavy and burning hot water.

As Lin Ming saw this lake, his heart skipped a beat.

He could faintly feel an inexhaustible essence of the power of demon gods condensed in this lake, as if all that vast energy that gushed out from before came from it!

Recalling the magma-like liquid gushing out from the ruptured earth, Lin Ming suspected that this was the ‘water’ from this gray lake.

Because the lake water had been stimulated for some unknown reason, it had pierced through the thousand some miles of rock and formed a tide of demonic energy. This was similar to the volcanic eruptions of the mortal world.

But, just how much strength would be required to break through a thousand miles of the Demon God’s Tomb rocky earth?

“This mystic realm should be related to the Demon God from a hundred billion years ago!”

Sheng Mei’s voice suddenly echoed in Lin Ming’s ears.

Lin Ming was startled. He looked at Sheng Mei.

Sheng Mei continued to speak in a sound transmission. “I’m not too sure of the specifics. Let us head down first.”

“Alright.”

Sheng Mei, Lin Ming, and the True Divinity from Deep King Road all flew towards the lake. And behind them, several Empyrean level abyssals from the Deep Alliance followed at a distance. It was at this time that the advantage of being in an alliance appeared. If they were to come here alone then these Empyrean level abyssals would surely be swallowed up in the battle without any bits remaining. But now, they found a slim chance of survival.

The more they neared the lake, the more Lin Ming felt that every drop of this lake water contained essence of the power of demon gods as vast and irresistible as a sea.

Strange lines spread across the surface of the lake, beating in rhythm with the most profound abyssal Laws and forming an absolute force field that locked in this part of the world.

A thousand feet away, everyone could feel this formidable pressure. Everyone’s flying speed suddenly slowed down.

Lin Ming swept his gaze outwards. He could see a massive amount of broken bone fragments scattered all around the lake. These bones had been here for countless years and were already bleached white.

However, what was strange was that in between these scattered bone fragments there were also several intact corpses. These corpses hadn’t turned into fragmented bones, but still had withered flesh. This left Lin Ming surprised. He didn’t know how long these corpses had been here. If these were trial challengers from the most recent times, then this could be understandable. But, if these bones came from ancient times then that would truly be shocking. It was hard to imagine just how they managed to withstand the corrosive strength that pervaded this world.

Lin Ming didn’t think much on this, because at this time, he could see a group of abyssals running in his direction. The one at the head of these abyssals was the Great Flood Crown Prince.

And besides the Great Flood Crown Prince were the two True Divinity level abyssals of the Flood Alliance as well as about ten Empyrean abyssals. This was around the total strength of the Flood Alliance in this underground world.

All around Lin Ming, the complexions of the abyssals turned ugly.

The Flood Alliance had the Great Flood Crown Prince holding the scene, but they only had Sheng Mei, Lin Ming, as well as an Elder from Deep King Road called Deep Echo.

In terms of masters, they were clearly at a lower level.

The Great Flood Crown Prince swept his eyes out. As he didn’t see that Deep Child who stirred fear in him, he suddenly grinned.

Without Deep Child here he could confidently say that he could completely wipe out all the Deep Alliance abyssals present!

“Really, the road to heaven is wide open and yet you refuse, but you would rather burst through the gates of hell! Originally, if you stayed up above then you would have been fine, but you insisted on coming down here to die. Then, how could I disappoint you? Let me fulfill your wish!”

The Great Flood Crown Prince looked at Lin Ming and Sheng Mei, a mocking light in his eyes.

Chapter 2145 – The Lake of Death

Facing the Great Flood Crown Prince, all the abyssals of the Deep Alliance were tense.

The Great Flood Crown Prince was already at the pinnacle of a middle True Divinity. Moreover, he was a considerable deal greater than those older True Divinity abyssals.

Facing such an opponent, just Lin Ming, Sheng Mei, and Deep Echo weren’t enough to be his match.

If this were back in the above world then they could scatter out in all directions to escape. But here in this underground world, they were no different than turtles in a jar, without any place to hide!

Killing intent slowly spread out from the two abyssal alliances. The air seemed to coagulate into something solid, making it so that the weaker abyssals found it difficult to move.

Sheng Mei took a deep breath and grasped her bone sword. Her mind reached a state of unprecedented concentration. As she held the bone sword in her hands, her palms were slightly wet. Even she found it difficult to remain calm when facing an enemy like the Great Flood Crown Prince.

She was aware that this battle would be difficult.

“Hehe! Your Highness Holy Demoness’ sword is truly extraordinary. It seems crafted from the bones of ancient sages and its quality even surpasses that of a True Divinity spirit treasure! Unfortunately, that sword will not bring you any miracles today. Your Highness, why must you be enemies with me? If you are willing to pledge an oath to me and dual cultivate with me, then we can work together to seek out the secrets of eternal life. How about it?”

As the Great Flood Crown Prince finished speaking, he casually swept his eyes over Lin Ming, a sinister and cold light flashing deep in his pupils.

Sheng Mei was renowned for being the number one woman to exist in the entirety of the Dark Abyss. If one could obtain her and dual cultivate with her, then the benefits to one’s cultivation would be incredible.

As for Lin Ming, he was the fiancé Sheng Mei had chosen. If he wanted to become one with Sheng Mei, he naturally had to eliminate Lin Ming first.

No matter how talented Lin Ming was, what mattered in a life or death battle was one’s absolute strength. He was fully confident he could kill Lin Ming.

Lin Ming maintained his calm as he rapidly analyzed the strength of the Great Flood Crown Prince. If he were to face the Great Flood Crown Prince then once battle erupted he would be forced to reveal his true self and it would no longer be possible to hide his identity.

If that happened then the situation would become troublesome. It would mean that he would have to kill all abyssals here who saw his true appearance!

Moreover, there was Deep Echo; if Deep Echo saw his true self would he possibly help the enemy instead?

“You, follow close to me once battle erupts. In the last moment I will use a secret technique and you will need to cover me!”

Because Lin Ming hadn’t ever stated his name, Sheng Mei simply referred to him as ‘you’.

Hearing Sheng Mei’s sound transmission, Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred. Indeed, Sheng Mei followed the Soul Emperor all this time. In a crucial moment she should have some sort of life-saving card.

Unless it was as a last resort, Lin Ming didn’t want to reveal his true self because if he did there would be far too many new problems.

All sorts of thoughts raced through Lin Ming’s mind. And at this time, there was a far off cry.

Everyone was startled. They turned towards the direction of the sound and what they saw left their scalps tingling.

In the few breaths of time before now, two Empyreans that didn’t belong to the Deep Alliance or Flood Alliance wished to take advantage of the time they were engaged with each other to be the first ones to delve into the lake. They wanted to quietly search for treasure as well as avoid the slaughter between the two sides.

But when they stepped onto the shore of the lake, the seemingly ordinary swampy ground, one of the Empyrean abyssals stepped on something and a black fog rose up that enveloped him.

In just a short breath of time, while this abyssal was violently shivering, the scales on his originally fierce body began to fall off and his towering and strong body started dissolving into bloody water that splashed onto the ground.

The Empyrean abyssal melted away. All that remained was a head that stared wide-eyed into the skies, filled with panic. But soon this head also dissolved.

Up until the moment he died, this abyssal didn’t make a single sound; it was only his companion that cried out.

An Empyrean level abyssal had died in such an inexplicable manner, simply melting away into nothing. This was just far too macabre a sight.

“This… this is…”

The surviving Empyrean level abyssal mumbled with a paper-white face. He didn’t even dare to take a deep breath. Slowly, he cautiously stepped backwards, wanting to withdraw from this murderous swampy land that seemed as if it came from hell.

After all, this Empyrean had survived many life or death situations in his time. He was well aware that if he didn’t maintain his calm but instead turned tail to run, then his death might come that much sooner.

One small step, another small step… just as he was about to leave the edge of the swampy ground, his foot seemed to step into some pit and he tumbled backwards.

With a cry of alarm, something seemed to grab onto his ankle from below and savagely pull him down!

“Ahh!”

This Empyrean level abyssal emitted a miserable shout. But soon his body sank into the swamp, and in just a breath of time his horrified shouts were also submerged.

After a little bit more time, bones began to slowly float up.

These bones still maintained the shape of someone struggling; they were the bones of the Empyrean level abyssal that just died.

This sort of feeling was like someone had been instantly eaten up with only bones remaining, leaving one frightened beyond compare!

“What is that!?”

Seeing this scene, all the abyssals present, even the inordinately arrogant Great Flood Crown Prince, couldn’t help but feel their hearts racing in their chests.

They had just probed whatever this underground existence was, but they still didn’t manage to discover just what it was that silently ate up two Empyrean level abyssals.

And, these Empyrean level abyssals were both proud elites of the Dark Abyss. But from start to finish, they were eaten and spit back out as quickly as cherries.

That mysterious underground existence absolutely possessed strength above that of a True Divinity level abyssal. As for what the exact rank was, no one could confirm.

All abyssals present held their breath for a time. In their minds, this calm underground world was becoming a dark land filled with horrifying terrors.

In particular, the abyssals with Empyrean levels of strength regretted their impulsiveness to fly into the underground crack.

Some abyssals gulped and subconsciously drew back from the direction of the lake. If it was them who rashly approached the lake just now, then the ones who turned into bones and bloody water would have been them.

The Great Flood Crown Prince’s complexion darkened. Even he felt pressured in such a situation. This was only near the shores of the lake and yet such a terrifying existence was here. Then, what would be at the bottom of the lake?

Even if a dreadful existence appeared from the bottom of the lake that could easily slaughter him, the Great Flood Crown Prince would still not be surprised.

After all, this hidden land had existed for over 100 billion years.

Moreover, the one who left this land behind was likely the Demon God of legends. As for what would evolve in this land through a span of 100 billion years, no one knew.

Thinking of this, the Great Flood Crown Prince and other abyssals didn’t dare to fight Lin Ming and Sheng Mei yet.

Even if the Great Flood Crown Prince was confident that he could slay Lin Ming and Sheng Mei, it would still require him to use up a considerable amount of energy. If several monsters leapt out towards him once he was weakened, he would simply become their dessert.

Moreover, a fight between several True Divinities would surely affect the surroundings. The two Empyreans just then had only reached the lake shore to alarm one of the monsters.

If their fight caused the heavens and earth to shake then perhaps even the monsters at the bottom of the lake would be stirred up. If a crowd of enraged monsters suddenly rose up, then their fates could be imagined.

“You still want to fight?”

Sheng Mei coldly stared at the Great Flood Crown Prince, her eyes shimmering and her voice decisive. The bone sword in her hand glittered. If there was a fight then she would naturally accompany them until the end.

The Great Flood Crown Prince frowned. He coldly snorted and finally said, “Consider yourselves lucky. I will allow you to live this time, of course, the premise is that you all don’t turn into bloody water!”

The Great Flood Crown Prince waved his hand and brought the others behind him to leave.

“Your Highness the Crown Prince, what are we to do…?”

A True Divinity level abyssal asked from beside the Great Flood Crown Prince.

“Let them live for now. At a key moment we might be able to use them as shields. First we will search the area for lucky chances and potential dangers. Once we have determined our situation then it still won’t be late to destroy them.

“And that lake…”

“We certainly must go in to take a look. There is at least a 70-80% chance that this mystic realm is related to the Demon God. If we enter a mountain of treasures and return empty-handed then what is the point of cultivating martial arts!”

Hearing the words of the Great Flood Crown Prince, many abyssals felt a chill run down their spines. They looked at the dark gray lake and to them it now looked like the jaws of a wild beast that were opened wide, alarming to the mind. As for the lake waters, they blocked out their sense; no one knew just what lay inside.

Chapter 2146 – The Lake Shore of Dripping Blood

“Hey, the several of you come over here!”

The Great Flood Crown Prince and his party stood in front of this killing lake. Suddenly, he turned his head and beckoned towards several Empyrean level abyssals in the distance.

These Empyrean level abyssals came from small influences. They didn’t belong to the Flood Alliance nor were they part of the Deep Alliance.

As these abyssals saw the Great Flood Crown Prince wave at them, their complexions suddenly turned extremely ugly.

Because the great crack in the earth had opened and closed so quickly, many abyssals had rushed down in a hot-headed decision; they never expected that they would be faced with such a situation underground.

“I told you all to come here, didn’t you hear me!?”

The Great Flood Crown Prince’s voice turned chilly. The several Empyrean abyssals wore gloomy faces as they walked towards the Great Flood Crown Prince.

When facing True Divinity level masters like Lin Ming and Sheng Mei, the Great Flood Crown Prince still held a measure of wariness against them. After all, wanting to kill a True Divinity level master wasn’t easy at all.

But against these Empyrean level abyssals, the Great Flood Crown Prince could kill them in an instant.

Thus, the Empyrean level abyssals didn’t resist, because doing so would only mean that death approached them faster.

The several Empyrean level abyssals trembled as they walked in front of the Great Flood Crown Prince. They already guessed just what would happen.

“Heh, what sort of expressions do you all have? I just want to cooperate with you.” The Great Flood Crown Prince said with a lingering smile. “Come, we will move forwards together. If we find anything good then we will divide it according to the number of people; it is an absolutely fair condition.”

How could these Empyrean abyssals possibly believe such words? One of the abyssals dryly laughed and said, “Crown Prince Your Highness, please don’t joke with us. How could we dare to struggle with you for lucky chances? This lake is likely a secret land left behind from the ancient era 100 billion years ago. With such a mystical trove, how could the likes of us possibly have the luck to enjoy it? Only someone as wonderful and fortunate as Your Highness could possibly be worthy of such a thing. As for us, we only rushed down here in a moment of hot-headedness. We will immediately disappear from your sight!”

A clever abyssals said, bowing as he drew backwards.

The Great Flood Crown Prince’s complexion turned cold and killing intent flashed in his eyes. “You sure speak enough garbage!”

The Great Flood Crown Prince’s face changed as his manner turned hostile. Demon power erupted from his body as he stretched out a hand and ruthlessly caught the retreating abyssal.

The Great Flood Crown Prince’s strength was considered at the peak of middle True Divinities; he wasn’t someone that ordinary middle Empyreans could deal with.

This Empyrean level abyssal was an overbearing ruler of his own influence, but in the hands of the Great Flood Crown Prince he was as powerless as a chicken, simply unable to put up a struggle.

“Crown Prince Your Highness… you… ahh!”

This middle Empyrean cried out in alarm as he was flung forwards by the Great Flood Crown Prince. “You, walk with us. Stay 100 feet ahead of me! I will make an oath on my demon heart that if we can take away the treasures here and safely return then I will leave a part of it to you! But if you try to play tricks with me or defy me, then I will kill you! Now, choose which road you wish to take!”

The Great Flood Crown Prince icily said.

After the abyssal heard these words, his complexion turned as pale as a corpse that had been dead for three days.

Safely return? Leave a part of the treasures to him? Did this possibility even exist?

Currently, he had been tossed forwards as a stone to explore the path ahead. In this underground world where killing intent overflowed from all around, he was nothing but cannon fodder, and those two abyssal Empyreans who had melted away into bones and blood were the best examples!

“You!” Although this abyssal’s previous words seemed extremely undignified and servile, the truth was that he also had a fierce nature hidden in his bones. How could he endure such a humiliating death?

“Heh! Don’t be in such a hurry to refuse me. You should be an Elder from the Apocalypse Sect, right?”

Hearing the Great Flood Crown Prince suddenly mention his sect, the Empyrean level abyssal’s complexion changed. He was about to deny this when the Great Flood Crown Prince smiled and said, “There is no need to try and hide it. When I grabbed you just now I probed your cultivation method and noticed that you cultivate the Apocalypse Sect’s Apocalyptic Devil Arts! Your clan is also in the Apocalypse Sect. If you obediently listen to me today then even if you die, when I make it out of here someday I will surely compensate your Apocalypse Sect. But if you disobey me, I will annihilate your Apocalypse Sect instead!”

The Great Flood Crown Prince’s words were incomparably domineering. The Apocalypse Sect’s Empyrean Elder was so mad that he shook from rage.

“I will give you one last chance. Not only can I destroy your Apocalypse Sect but I can also make you suffer pain worse than death. Even if you don’t submit to me I still have ways to replace you in exploring the path ahead, and it's only that it will be just a little bit more troublesome to me.”

The Great Flood Crown Prince’s voice became increasingly cold. It seemed he had reached the end of his patience.

Lin Ming listened from behind, quietly astonished. In the Dark Abyss, being weaker only meant to be freely oppressed.

That abyssal who had been grabbed was forced into a helpless situation and made to explore the way forwards.

The Great Flood Crown Prince and his group followed from a distance.

There were also some Empyrean level abyssals from smaller guilds that followed with aggrieved complexions. Without a doubt, once that abyssal in the front had the bad luck of randomly dying somehow, the next to stand in his place would be one of them.

The group quietly walked forwards. The atmosphere was so tense and constrained that it seemed as if someone could squeeze water from it.

“We will also go.”

Sheng Mei said after a moment of thought. She clearly didn’t want to give up on whatever secrets there were in this lake.

She looked at Lin Ming, asking for his suggestion. Lin Ming nodded, “We should release some of the power of demon gods that we absorbed and fully extend our senses. Since this energy comes from the same source, there should be a connection between it. If there really is danger we should be able to perceive some clues…”

“Good. Everyone be wary.”

Sheng Mei nodded and released some of the power of demon gods she absorbed. The abyssals around her followed suit.

At this time, the Great Flood Crown Prince’s group was now a mere 100 feet away from that killing lake.

At this distance the pressure was even more intense. Moreover, the abyssals could feel a rich death energy, one that was rank with the smell of blood, as if this lake they faced was a blood pond from hell.

“I… I…”

The abyssal leading the way turned paper white. With every step he took, it was like he walked over the precipice of death. His forehead was already dripping with sweat. This killing lake was simply far too strange and the ways one could die were too pitiful.

90 feet…

80 feet…

70 feet…

They approached a step at a time, each abyssal raising their guard as high as they could.

All the way to 20 feet, 10 feet, 3 feet… that abyssal leading the way would soon touch the lake waters.

Although he was frightened so badly his complexion was like that of a dying man, he had extremely good luck and still hadn’t died.

Could this so-called killing lake in truth only be dangerous in that part of the swampy ground? And in that swampy area there was some horrifying existence lying in wait, but the other areas weren’t dangerous?

This thought flashed through the minds of some abyssals. They even guessed that this killing lake had some guardian demon beast, and as long as they avoided it they might be able to safely enter the mystic realm left behind by the Demon God.

Soon, the leading abyssal reached the edge of the killing lake.

The abyssals following behind paused their steps. This was the crucial moment; they needed to test and determine whether or not this lake was dangerous in itself.

Perhaps this lake water was corrosive enough to melt away anything, and any abyssal that jumped in would turn into a pile of bones.

“Reach out your hand and test it!”

The Great Flood Crown Prince coldly ordered.

The leading abyssal clenched his teeth. Then, he first used a sword and gently dipped it in the lake water. Besides light ripples, nothing else happened.

After pulling out the sword, the blade also emerged unscathed.

The abyssal felt slightly relieved upon seeing this. After a moment of hesitation, he took out a container to remove a little water from the lake and analyze whether it was dangerous or not.

But at this moment, a miserable cry rang out from behind him.

“Ahhh!”

In a situation where everyone was highly tensed, whether it was abyssals or humans, it was easy for anyone to cry out.

Several abyssals were originally standing stably on the ground. But then, they felt the earth soften beneath them and their feet plunged into the ground.

Then they felt a strength that none of them could resist suddenly pull down their bodies, dragging them below!

“Damnit!”

The Great Flood Crown Prince was enraged. The abyssal leading the way was fine, but the larger force behind had been ambushed instead! It seemed that this mysterious underground existence had purposefully let go of the little fish up ahead to catch the larger group behind!

Clang!

In the Great Flood Crown Prince’s hand, the saber engraved with a ghost head rang out as it emerged from its sheath, roughly slashing down onto the earth.

Demon power swelled up like a raging sea tide.

Bang!

With a loud explosion, the divine-iron hard lake shore was sundered by the Great Flood Crown Prince’s saber. Muddy stones blew into the air, and the four or five Empyrean level abyssals that were dragged into the ground were suddenly forcefully blown out again by this strength.

However, of those Empyrean abyssals that were dragged into the ground just now, one could see that their bodies had been melted away in multiple areas, leaving nothing behind but white bones.

Their deaths were only a matter of time!

Chapter 2148 – Sheng Mei’s Past Life (A)

“Holy Demoness, can you hear me?”

Lin Ming tried to send Sheng Mei a true essence sound transmission, but he didn’t obtain any response.

At this time, Sheng Mei’s complexion was pale and her eyes were shut tight. Her eyelashes quietly shivered; it was clear that Sheng Mei, as well as the many abyssals all around, weren’t able to resist that massive soul-tearing strength just now and their minds had fallen into illusion.

“This is…”

Lin Ming’s brows pressed together. If he hadn’t been for the Magic Cube then he feared that he too wouldn’t have been able to withstand that strength.

Lin Ming noticed that many abyssals had pained expressions, as if they were experiencing something terrifying.

At this time, as the vortex continued to spin, all of the abyssals were scattered farther and farther apart from each other.

Lin Ming watched helplessly as the abyssals of the Deep Alliance as well as Sheng Mei were all flung increasingly far in their entranced state.

As for deeper within, he could no longer see the abyssals of the Flood Alliance.

“Just what was that soul-tearing strength?”

Lin Ming grimaced. After a moment, he loosened the connection between his soul and the Magic Cube.

In that instant, the soul-tearing strength roared at him once more.

Lin Ming’s divine soul was held by the Magic Cube. Slowly, he allowed his consciousness to free itself.

Currently, Lin Ming could be said to be in a half-dream, half-awake state. As long as he wanted to he could plunge his thoughts into the Magic Cube to free himself from the condition, but right now he wanted to know just what mysteries were contained in this mystical soul-tearing strength.

Gradually, Lin Ming felt his body become increasingly light. The endless lake waters around him vanished, and in the next moment he arrived in a beautiful world lit up with dappled sunlight…

“This is…”

He was stunned. He could see a giant structure before him as well as the signboard above the complex that had the words ‘Seven Profound’ written on it in large, flowing characters.

Seven Profound Martial House?

Upon recalling the name of this martial house, Lin Ming felt as if everything that happened was a lifetime ago.

This was the beginning of Lin Ming’s road of martial arts. After tracing back to the start, this was something that happened over 12,000 years ago.

12,000 years. To long-lived martial artists that might live for hundreds of millions of years, 12,000 years was only an extremely short period in their life. For some, a long period of seclusion might take 10,000-20,000 years.

But to Lin Ming, these 12,000 years were an incomparably distant matter.

“Could what this soul-tearing strength be dragging back are dust-laden old dreams from deep in my memories? It wants me to relive these events?”

Lin Ming looked up at the signboard of the Seven Profound Martial House in this dream and began to walk forwards.

As he expected, he saw many familiar people from the past.

Zhu Yan, Lan Yunyue, Qin Ziye, Qin Xingxuan…

There were even some characters that were hidden deep in his memory and that he normally wouldn’t recall. For instance, that girl in the Seven Profound Martial House who he always had a favorable impression towards, but whom he had lost news of later, Bai Jingyun…

Lin Ming watched from the viewpoint of an outsider, calmly looking at the life he had lived.

He gradually understood that after entering this killing lake, the soul-tearing strength that acted on them perhaps might be some sort of test on a martial artist’s divine soul.

If a person’s mind wasn’t firm then it was easy to fall into this dreamland and never be able to disentangle themselves from it.

Lin Ming’s mind stirred. The scenes of the Seven Profound Martial House shattered and then the experiences from the South Sea Demon Region came flooding in.

Familiar characters, familiar locations, all sorts of scenes took the stage.

He saw Divine Phoenix Island, saw the invasion of the South Sea Demon Region.

He saw himself entering Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm, saw himself being mistakenly assumed as dead, saw that Ouyang Boyan who had a grudge with him move against Qin Xingxuan and try to have her killed on Blood Demon Island.

After emerging from that Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm, he learned of this news and in his fury he rushed out on a vermillion bird, passing hundreds of thousands of miles to reach Blood Demon Island and save Qin Xingxuan.

This was one of Lin Ming’s deepest and most profound memories. When he successfully rescued Qin Xingxuan from the jaws of death, this allowed him to truly understand how happy he was to not lose someone he loved.

However, in these dreamland memories, what replayed itself was actually completely different.

He saw himself fly to Blood Demon Island. The moment he found Qin Xingxuan, a blood demon rushed at her, opening its ravenous jaws and biting down on her neck!

At this moment, the despairing Qin Xingxuan saw him. As she did, all sorts of emotion flooded her face. Love, joy, regret...

Lin Ming’s heart tightened and he found it impossible to remain indifferent. He wanted to move to save Qin Xingxuan, but he found that his speed became incomparably slow. From a True Divinity level of strength, he found that he had dropped down to that mere Houtian realm he had been at when he first saved Qin Xingxuan.

Like this, he could only stare blankly on as that blood demon bit down on Qin Xingxuan’s neck.

Blood gushed out. All the emotions on Qin Xingxuan’s face froze, as if time itself had come to a standstill.

The smiling Qin Xingxuan and the blood that dripped down from her formed a sharp contrast.

No –

Lin Ming cried out in alarm, in fear.

In the next moment, Lin Ming fiercely bit down on his tongue to sober himself.

“This is false!”

Lin Ming took a deep breath, violently gasping. He told himself this so that he could rid himself of that horrifying dream just now.

In the depths of his mind, Lin Ming knew that what he saw wasn’t real. Moreover, his divine soul had always been stabilized with that faint connection with the Magic Cube. Even so, when Lin Ming saw that scene just now it was like he had personally experienced it, and in his anger and sorrow he had nearly fallen into illusion, unable to drag himself out.

“What a terrifying dreamland…”

Lin Ming was bewildered. Even he had barely managed to avoid falling into illusion. Then, what about the other abyssals here?

Lin Ming still didn’t withdraw himself from the dreamland.

He wanted to take a good look for himself and what this strange soul-tearing strength was going to do.

Then, scenes continued to replay themselves.

These scenes were all things that Lin Ming had truly experienced in the past. However, instead of how they had truly ended, everything took a turn for the worse.

When competing for the Nirvana Dragon Root in Demon God Imperial Palace, Lin Ming saw his schemes be seen through by Xuan Wuji – as a result, he was executed where he stood.

In the bronze temple facing Yang Yun, Lin Ming saw his body being seized by him. From that point on, his body was possessed by Yang Yun and that strange and sinister smile hung on his face from then on.

Then, facing Tian Mingzi in the Asura Road, Lin Ming saw himself being the one that was killed.

Halfway through his life adventures, he saw the Magic Cube being discovered. He fled through the world but eventually he was discovered by someone and his soul was pulled out and refined.

He even saw the Good Fortune Saint Son defeat him and take Xiao Moxian for his own.

He saw the Good Fortune Saint Son brutally ravage Xiao Moxian. In that moment, Lin Ming’s soul nearly fell into illusion once more.

Peng!

Lin Ming punched out at the scene before him and the diabolically grinning Good Fortune Saint Son shattered into fragments. Lin Ming gasped for breath. The scenes in this dreamland were of things he feared the most!

If he weren’t for the Magic Cube, Lin Ming didn’t know if he would have been able to withstand all of this…

“What a fierce dreamland. I have the Eternal Soul so I should be fine for now, but what about the others? For instance Sheng Mei…”

Lin Ming remembered Sheng Mei, this woman that he wasn’t sure was a friend or enemy. As he thought of her he inevitably worried.

If Sheng Mei didn’t have any heart demons then it would be good.

But if she did have a heart demon, then she would be incredible danger in this soul dreamland!

Lin Ming could be called someone with a firm will and iron determination. But, even he didn’t dare say he didn’t have any heart demons.

The so-called heart demons were things that a martial artist longed for the most, or feared the most.

The stronger these obsessions were, the stronger the heart demons were.

Moreover, the more powerful a martial artist the more formidable these heart demons would become. Once these types of dreamlands appeared, or in a critical moment when trying to make a breakthrough, these heart demons might appear to haunt the martial artist and cause problems. If they suddenly manifested, it was possible that a martial artist could go crazy or fall into depravity.

“Sheng Mei, would she have heart demons?”

Lin Ming mumbled. He didn’t know why, but a foreboding premonition suddenly rose in his heart…

……..

In the dark gray lake waters, the vast vortex continued to wildly spin about. A peerless woman in black clothes was being spun about in these lake waters. Her thick and luscious hair fell about her, fanning out in the lake waters like a black rose in full bloom but also wilting.

At this time, Sheng Mei’s complexion was pale white, without the least bit of red remaining…

After experiencing the complete nine reincarnations and tempering her divine soul for all this time, she had become incomparably formidable in this aspect. In fact, when it came to the soul, she wasn’t much worse than Lin Ming.

However…

Her heart demons were also incomparably powerful.

In her divine soul, there were far too many things she longed for and feared…

……..

In a giant circular building similar to an area, a seven or eight year old little girl was standing in the center.

She had bright black eyes and her little arms seemed carved from jade. Her face was fresh and cute like a ripe apple, a completely lovable little child.

On her face, if one searched carefully, they could find shadows of the current Sheng Mei.

Such a lovable little girl actually had a face stained with blood. Her arms were also covered with blood. Her small jade-like arms were grasping a large sword.

This sword was longer than the little girl was tall. She only barely managed to hold onto it with both hands.

Along the sword’s thick hilt, blood continued to drip downwards. On the ground around the little girl was scattered pieces of flesh and puddles of blood. Organs, incomplete corpses; this area resembled a slaughterhouse.

The little girl lowered her head and supported herself on the large sword. She gasped for breath.

“Are you ready to continue?”

At this time, a faint voice echoed out.

The little girl was startled up. She looked up and from beneath her bangs, a doll-like face was revealed. From between her eyebrows, a single vertical red mark appeared, like the petal of a flower.

“I… am tired…”

The little girl muttered with difficulty. But at this time, from not too far away, an old man appeared.

This old man was thin but his build was naturally tall and wide. His face was deep and profound and he emitted a majestic aura. He wasn’t a spiritas nor was he a saint – he was someone of the primal god race.

“On the battlefield, the enemy will not give you time to rest…”

As the old man spoke he gently waved his hand. From not too far away, an iron gate was opened.

From behind this iron gate, black life forms wrapped in chains appeared.

These were… abyssals!

Moreover, because of some sort of reason, these abyssals had lost their minds and had turned crazy.

Roar - !

Dozens of abyssals roared out together. As they looked at the little girl, their eyes were filled with bloodthirst and killing intent.

Chapter 2149 – Sheng Mei’s Past Life (B)

Of these abyssal demons, the vast majority were originally of the kind that possessed low intelligence. After being stimulated by a secret technique, they had gone crazy and were now no different from wild beasts.

Seeing this little girl, these abyssals instantly became ferocious.

Ao!

The crowd of abyssals howled as they rushed towards this little girl!

Seeing these vicious and murderous abyssals, the little girl clenched her teeth. She wielded her sword and brought it slashing down. Sword light sparkled as abyssal after abyssal was cut apart by her!

Countless corpses littered the ground. Blood dyed her face, her clothes, drenched her entire body in the thickly rank smell of blood, as if she were someone that had crawled out from the blood ponds of hell.

For such a cute little girl to be drenched in thick blood, this formed an incredible visual impact. It was hard to imagine that the surrounding scene had originated from her hands.

The old man looked on indifferently as the abyssals rushed forwards. He only waved his hand and another group of wild abyssals flushed out of another gate.

These abyssals were even more formidable than the previous ones. They howled out as they raced towards the little girl…

Year after year, the little girl experienced endless and untold amounts of slaughter.

Many times, because her enemies were too strong, she was nearly torn to shreds by the abyssals.

Or sometimes she was severely wounded, suffocating on the verge of death.

But each time, as she lay dying, she would be put into a pot of boiling medicinal solution, suffering agonizing torment as she slowly recovered from her wounds.

She grew stronger and stronger and her cultivation grew higher and higher. Every inch of her flesh experienced inexhaustible tempering. From a young child she slowly grew up into a young girl.

At some unknown point, the singular red mark between her eyebrows became two.

Like two flower petals pressed in between her eyebrows.

Afterwards, she was tossed alone onto a vast wild plain.

Without pills, without supplies, she ventured through the wild plains on her own, encountering countless ancient great beasts and slaughtering them!

Without pills, she gathered everything she needed by herself. When she was injured she treated herself.

She passed a hundred million miles through a great desolate land, killing innumerable wild beasts all the while.

At this time, she had already become a woman whose beauty was capable of causing the downfall of nations. Her strength was outstanding. In the primal god race, her status was like the moon in the night sky, brilliant and glorious.

The flower petals between her eyebrows turned to three. When the third one appeared, she was locked on the reef of a small island deep in the sea.

This small island was the place where the bones of an ancient great emperor were buried. There was a giant force field that covered this land, and a normal martial artist would find it unbearable.

But this young girl was locked onto the ground here using chains.

With her slender and charming figure, she was tightly bound by these chains. The darksteel rings dug into her flesh and drew blood. On her beautiful body, fierce red marks were left behind.

And behind her were the rocky reefs. These reefs were not made from ordinary stones, but from extraterrestrial divine stones. These stones dug into her back, like countless needles thrusting into her body.

The chains weren’t common chains either. They were dragon trapping chains refined by an array formation grandmaster.

Not only could they bind the body they could also lock in one’s divine soul.

In addition with the pressure from the great emperor force field, from the very start the young girl found it nearly impossible to breathe.

When the tides rose, infinite great waves would smash into her body. She withstood that crashing pain time and time again.

And after the tide retreated, the blazing hot sun would burn her body.

She lost all color. She lay there motionlessly, not even blinking her eyes, as if she had already become a jade statue.

She withstood such monstrous suffering, silently enduring it, patiently waiting…

No one came to check on her and no one delivered food to here. She could only stare off into the distance and the horizon that was covered with thick fog and the limitless sea and boundless sky that spread out before her.

As if she were already forgotten hereby the world. If she wasn’t able to free herself, then she would simply die here.

Loneliness, despair, pain, such suffering could even make a brave man turn mad.

At the start, the young girl felt extremely helpless. But slowly, she discovered remnants of the mysterious great emperor’s Laws. And, she discovered that the roiling heaven and earth origin energy here was a hundred times richer than the outside.

She started to perceived the Laws, day in and day out.

Every morning she would lick the darksteel chains, drinking in the morning dew that had gathered on the cold metal. She would breathe in the purest power of the world here.

She constantly saved her strength, constantly raised her strength.

Until one day, as her strength rose higher and higher she finally broke through her bottleneck and her strength rose to a whole new level!

Like a phoenix bathing in the fires, on the verge of death she experienced her own nirvanic rebirth!

Bang!

She smashed apart the iron chains that bound her body and blew apart the divine stones behind her. With a loud and clear cry, she blazed into the boundless blue skies!

In that moment, she experienced another sublimation of her strength and experiences, another transformation.

Amongst her contemporaries, there was already no one capable of competing with her strength…

…….

Battle, slaughter, cultivation…

Her enemies ranged from abyssals, to endless wild beasts, and back to infinite waves of abyssals. Although she had a beauty that could fell kingdoms, she had never once experienced the love between a man and woman.

All she knew was blood.

All she knew was fighting.

And everything that occurred to these peerless woman flowed into Sheng Mei’s inner world.

As if this were a life she had experienced, an incomparably real life.

However, this seemed to only be a dream that had nothing to do with Sheng Mei. Because in her memories, Sheng Mei simply couldn’t find these scenes.

Just who was the young girl in the dream?

That beautiful woman had an appearance completely similar to that of Sheng Mei. And between her eyebrows, there was also the mark of a red lotus; that was the symbol of the nine revolutions of reincarnation…

As if she were dreaming, as if she were awake, Sheng Mei could no longer distinguish if she were Sheng Mei or the woman in this dream…

After experiencing untold years, this dream woman’s strength now stood at the highest levels of the universe. The red lotus between her eyebrows had long since reached perfection, and what Sheng Mei saw next left her gasping on her own breath.

She saw in the limitless vast space, there was a floating dark continent.

And on this continent were bones, endless bones!

Some of these bones were in the shape of people, some were in the shape of fierce monsters, all sorts of wild beasts, and even some bones in the shape of God Beasts that extended for thousands of miles.

Of these skeletons, all of them emitted an incredibly terrifying aura. If the bones of a weakling were placed within, they would immediately be crushed into dust by the pressure!

Without a doubt, only the remains of peerless powerhouses were on this dark continent.

It was unimaginable just how so many peerless powerhouses had died here.

Looking at the bones, one could see that they had died around the same time.

From this, one could speculate that this was an incredibly brutal war that involved countless peerless powerhouses!

The peerless woman stood above these endless bones, as if she were on another world.

She was barefoot, wearing a long black dress that flowed down her like water. Divine brilliance poured from her, sprinkling down onto her body, shrouding her in a faint hazy glow.

Her aura seemed to merge together with the one. In this brutal and savage world, she seemed completely out of place.

In her life, she had experienced endless slaughter. But at this time she was like a single orchid in a profound canyon, ethereal and otherworldly, her snow white skin untainted by mortal affairs.

Even this dark and ominous battlefield that was covered in layers of killing intent seemed to have nothing to do with her.

And at this time, in front of the woman, something appeared.

This was… a purple card.

The small card was only the size of a palm. And carved on this card were countless strange and indecipherable marks.

These marks were ancient and mystical. Just by looking at them, one felt as if their soul would fall within.

The card was like a fluttering butterfly, flying around this peerless woman.

The woman looked at this card. From within her bright eyes, infinite sorrow and regret seemed to appear…

However, all these complex feelings eventually returned to peace and serenity. There was no longer any waves in her mood.

The card fluttered about, slowly flying towards the peerless woman’s forehead.

Then… gently, gently, gently… it cut into the jade-like flesh of the woman’s forehead.

The nine petal red lotus was torn apart by the purple card, instantly fading…

Blood gushed out and all of it was absorbed by the purple card. Then, endless crimson light dyed this dark gray world…

In that moment, the world seemed to regain all its color. Infinite life essence recklessly gushed out from the woman. More and more light blazed from the woman’s body. Like a black phoenix burning itself, she dazzled with blinding brilliance!

Because of this woman’s brilliance, this dark world was filled with beautiful colors once more.

The woman burned everything she was without reserve. The final flash of brilliance of her life seemed to turn into eternity…

Chapter 2150 – Heart Demon

The moment that dream woman turned into a brilliant flash of light, Sheng Mei felt as if a sword had been stabbed into her heart. With a stuffy cough, her divine soul suffered excruciating pain as if she was being torn asunder.

In front of Sheng Mei, that dazzling divine light became increasingly strong, blotting out the skies. Like millions and billions of suns crashing down onto the world.

That black continent melted away.

And above that continent, the endless skeletons were sucked in by this strength, shattering and disintegrating!

The force fields inherent within these skeletons, the energy emitted from these peerless powerhouses after they died, everything was swept up into that blinding brilliance, turning into a kaleidoscope of colors that swirled into a giant vortex!

This vortex swallowed the continent, completely refining it!

Endless runes came shrouding down. The earth seemed to turn into a magic tool. The Purple Card fluttered in the center of that continent, giant ripples of energy pulsating outwards.

Then, as if it were being grasped by some great invisible hand, this continent was pushed towards another world, slowly suppressing it!

For a time, infinite tracts of space were cracked. Horrifying space storms stirred up, but nothing was able to stop the advance of this continent.

It was irresistible!

In the blinding brilliance, the continent became increasingly thin as it was refined. However, the energy within was being compressed to an infinite degree.

All the skeletons atop were refined, turned into endless fragments that tumbled about in the air.

As for the energy of those skeletons, all of it fused together in the center of this continent – the Purple Card.

This card seemed to be the center of all energy in the universe. As long as anything could be turned into energy, nothing was able to escape its control.

These skeletons, whether it was life forms of the 33 Heavens, God Beasts, or even abyssal demons, whether it was the power of divinity, the power of demons, the power of monsters, all of it was entirely absorbed by the Purple Card.

Finally, this continent turned into a giant wall of light that turned towards that mysterious dark world and ruthlessly came suppressing down on it.

Bang!

With an indescribable explosion, the world seemed to collapse.

That giant and profound dark world that hid in the void trembled, trembled…

It was like the apocalypse had arrived, as if the great Shattering were beginning once more!

In that moment, Sheng Mei’s divine soul violently shook. She suddenly spat out a mouthful of blood and the chaotic dream she saw shattered, turning into endless fragments.

Her face was pale white and her entire body streamed with dripping sweat.

Everything she experienced in that dream just now was far too real, as if she had lived tens of thousands of years in it. But when she woke up from that dream, it was as if only a mere moment had passed.

She experienced inexhaustible scenes in that dream, but as she tried to recall them, they were somewhat blurry…

Yet even though she already couldn’t recall many of the scenes, Sheng Mei still deeply remembered those final moments.

She remembered that dream woman burning away her life, refining those endless skeletons to forge that giant crystal wall with the Purple Card, and then maliciously suppressed that dark world with the crystal wall.

That mysterious dark world gave off an incredibly familiar feeling to Sheng Mei – it was the Dark Abyss

And above the Dark Abyss lay the Eternal God Wall, a barrier that isolated the Dark Abyss from the 33 Heavens. It was a wall that had existed there for 10 billion years.

And in her dreams, Sheng Mei had actually witnessed the birth of the Eternal God Wall.

The black-clothed woman burning away her life in a flash of brilliance, the suppression of the crystal wall, that apocalyptic scene, all of it became a mark that was forever branded in Sheng Mei’s mind!

“She is…”

Sheng Mei took a deep breath and earnestly tried to recall what she remembered. She wanted to seek out how she was related to that mysterious woman in her dreams.

However, just as she felt as if she had caught hold of something, she felt as if her spiritual sea was being torn apart once more.

Such fiercely aching pain was like a heavy hammer that brutally smashed down on her head. She felt her legs soften and her surroundings turn dark. In the next moment her consciousness became blurry once more…

She seemed to begin yet another long dream.

Countless mixed scenes appeared in this dream, and she saw many familiar characters.

Of these many faces, some were friendly, some were kind, some were disgusted, some were filled with hatred…

And finally, a youth’s face appeared, seeming as if it took up the entire dream.

This youth had pale white skin and cloudy eyes, as if he were a dead man walking.

Soul Emperor!

Seeing this old youth, a cold light flashed in Sheng Mei’s eyes. She was utterly unable to resist the Soul Emperor. But towards this evil man, what she felt the most was not fear, but hatred!

Bang!

A beam of divine thought burst out from between the Soul Emperor’s eyes and crashed into Sheng Mei’s inner world. Sheng Mei’s mind shook and space tumbled about her. As she opened her eyes once more, she discovered she had arrived in a world where the heaven and earth origin energy was extremely thin, but a world that was also extremely peaceful…

“This is…”

As this world appeared, Sheng Mei felt something that nearly left her gasping for breath.

This was the Sky Spill Continent, Lin Ming’s hometown!

Could it be…

Sheng Mei’s body quivered, as if she were living a waking nightmare.

This was something hidden deep in her memories, a box she wasn’t willing to open. Like a scar she couldn’t bear to see, she simply couldn’t face it.

She dreaded experiencing this scene, she truly didn’t want to…

However, in this scene before her, what she feared the most slowly happened. She saw – Lin Ming.

At this time, Lin Ming was lying despondent on the ground of his home world, looking at Sheng Mei.

At this moment, Sheng Mei wanted to withdraw, but she discovered that a flow of heat surged in her belly.

This flow of heat spread through her limbs and bones. She turned around and saw that not too far away, there was an old tree that looked as if it were molded from a horned dragon.

And on that old tree there had originally been two fruits. But, these two fruits had already disappeared.

Sheng Mei’s heart shook. She certainly remembered preparing this fruit tree for Lin Ming. It originated from the Dark Abyss, a type of enchanted fruit that inflamed one’s basest sexual desires.

In the past, without a road to take, she had chosen to use these enchanted fruits.

But now she didn’t want to experience this scene once more.

She revolved the strength in her body, wanting to drive out the medicinal strength of this fruit. But, she discovered that no matter how she tried, she simply wasn’t able to move any of the energy within her.

As if this body wasn’t her own.

Sheng Mei took and deep breath and suddenly understood what was occurring. This was her dream, and ultimately her true self was only a wandering traveler through this dream. No matter what she tried to do she couldn’t change the dream. She could only stand here and experience it once more…

“If you are destined to be destroyed, then you might as well… be destroyed by my hands…”

These were words that Sheng Mei once said to Lin Ming. These words reverberated in this dreamland, and as she heard them once more, she didn’t know how she felt…

She closed her eyes, not wanting to watch the following scene. But soon she felt her clothes disappear, and then… the movement of bodies.

That was a masculine body unreservedly fusing with her own.

This sort of strange feeling gradually blended together with the burning heat in her body, making her soul tremble.

She never would have imagined that on this day, in her dream she would experience this extremely profound memory once more…

In the past she too had eaten that enchanted aphrodisiac fruit of the Dark Abyss, and her consciousness had also turned blurry. Although she remembered that unforgettable touch, her experiences at the time had still be blurry.

As if she were being mesmerized by an intoxicating spring dream, although she had reached the pinnacle of bliss, she had still done so in a half-awake, half-dream state.

And the difference now was that Sheng Mei was experiencing all of this completely sober.

She kept her eyes closed throughout. But, the continuous impacts that seemed to strike at her soul continued to pass over that original pleasure from beginning to end.

In her dream, besides not being able to control this body, she personally experienced everything!

Beneath the medicinal properties of the fruit, she felt a wild joy that left her breathlessly enchanted.

This was something she had never experienced before in her dry and repressed life.

But at the same time, she also felt the confusion and pain hidden in the depths of this man’s soul beneath her.

His life source, his soul source was being slowly weakened, drawn out from him…

It was like watching a brilliant star slowly fading away.

In particular, this fading man had an inextricably linked relationship with her. And his fall also came because of her.

Without noticing it, Sheng Mei felt a crystal clear and cool tear fall down from the corner of her eye, breaking apart like a pearl as it landed…

Chapter 2151 – Soul Tear

Pata!

That crystalline tear drop fell onto Lin Ming’s face and gently broke apart.

In this confusing world, the sound of that teardrop was incomparably clear, like a sound that travelled through time and space.

This was a soul tear.

Some souls, when recalling their past pain and emotions, would leave behind tears…

Seeing this shattering soul tear, Sheng Mei humorlessly smiled. She knew just how pale and useless this tear was in such a situation.

Because… what had happened, could no longer be changed.

Moreover, even if that time returned, the result would still be the same. Because the situation at that time had been a dead end for Lin Ming…

In her lament, the joy she had felt in fusing together with Lin Ming once more slowly faded away.

At this time, Sheng Mei’s soul had gone completely quiet.

She watched helplessly on as the only man in her life who had managed to stir up her love and hate started to slowly lose his soul and life source beneath her actions…

He had turned incomparably weak, like a star that had burned itself away.

In that moment, Sheng Mei felt as if her own soul had turned to ice.

She looked at the deeply sleeping Lin Ming who had already become crippled by now. She felt as if a knife were slowly digging away at her, cutting through her heart…

In the final moments she left behind a wisp of her source soul in Lin Ming. However, she knew that this wisp of her soul wasn’t likely to play any useful function…

This was equal to saying that Lin Ming was already done for.

This was a man she had once wanted to leap out from this vortex of disaster with together. And now, she had personally destroyed him.

Before anything could begin, it was already over…

She quietly waited, her heart as desolate as a graveyard. In truth she only waited for several hours, but to her they were like a billion years.

At this time, the deeply sleeping Lin Ming quietly woke up.

He looked at Sheng Mei and bitterly smiled.

The grass was soft beneath them as a cool breeze blew past. The two looked at each other, this image captured in their minds for eternity.

At some unknown time, Sheng Mei finally spoke up.

These were words Sheng Mei had once said in the past. Now, she was listening to them once more as an outsider.

“Hate me…”

These didn’t seem to be words directed towards Lin Ming, but words aimed at herself, torturous words that questioned herself and him.

“What reason do I have to hate you? If it wasn’t for you then I would have already been killed by Soaring Feather and would be nothing but an icy cold corpse. In fact, I could even say that without you I would never have left the Soul World and would have already died to the Great Brahmic God King…”

As they were back then as they were now, Lin Ming’s every word was clearly remembered by Sheng Mei.

She fell silent, listening to these words. Every word echoed in her ears and she could even recall them exactly…

Until Lin Ming said, “You really… are willing to resort to any means possible. In order to cultivate the Art of Eternal Life, you are even willing to use your body as a tool. In the mortal world there are women that can sell their bodies for money. And you, just what distinguishes you from them?”

These words scolded Sheng Mei as a whore. In the past they had stirred up great waves in her heart, but today they stirred up nothing. She simply sighed in sorrow.

Perhaps there really was no difference. She also couldn’t control her own fate, and her ending was equally sad…

It was over…

Sheng Mei knew that all of this was already predetermined. No matter how many time it repeated, the result would be the same.

Then…

Sheng Mei watched as she broke through the void, leaving the despondent and seemingly dead Lin Ming lying on the earth, as if there wasn’t a single trace of life left within him.

Her soul actually didn’t follow her dream self in departing. Rather, she stayed in the Sky Spill Continent and gazed at Lin Ming.

This left Sheng Mei shocked.

How could this be?

Sheng Mei didn’t know why. But slowly, her heart trembled. She had been looking at Lin Ming in the Sky Spill Continent for several days already.

She still hadn’t left with her dream self.

Faintly, something stirred up in her heart.

Could it be…

Could she see what Lin Ming experienced in the past? During that time, because of the existence of the Soul Emperor she was simply unable to keep track of Lin Ming. Moreover, after she left the Sky Spill Planet she went to the Dark Abyss.

But now she had such an opportunity in her dream.

In this dream, was everything that was occurring truly what happened to Lin Ming?

As Sheng Mei suddenly thought of this, she finally slowly shook her head.

Perhaps these were only assumptions that her mind came up with.

No matter how wise and amazing this Demon God’s Tomb mystic realm was, it was impossible for it to learn of Lin Ming’s memories and let her stand near him.

Even so, Sheng Mei still continued to gaze quietly on.

She wanted to see what Lin Ming had experienced, even if it were all in her imagination.

The years changed.

Spring went and fall came.

Sheng Mei quietly waited beside Lin Ming, like a ghost defending a grave.

And in this wilderness, Lin Ming seemed to fall into a permanent state of sleep. Fall leaves and dust fell upon his body, and even grass grew over him.

Sheng Mei’s heart was heavy, but she held immeasurable patience.

She waited, always waited…

Until one day, Lin Ming slowly, slowly opened his eyes…

Shen Mei’s heart skipped a beat and her complexion changed. It was clear just how unsteady her soul was at this time.

She watched at Lin Ming slowly stood up. The earth and weeds rolled down from his body. At this moment, it was like Lin Ming was crawling out from a grave.

Lin Ming walked forwards. It was unknown where he wanted to go.

Sheng Mei quietly followed behind.

She followed him as he crossed mountains, passed rivers, walked through seas, and climbed a mountain that pierced into the skies like a sword.

On the mountain summit, Sheng Mei saw two swordsmen that seemed as if they had just started on the road of martial arts. They were holding a martial meeting on the summit of this sword mountain.

“These are people that Lin Ming knew from the mortal world!”

Sheng Mei looked at Lin Ming and could see this from his eyes.

She watched as the two swordsmen engaged in a fierce contest in the air. She also saw Lin Ming drinking wine with the two after this martial arts meeting, and freely speaking with them.

In Sheng Mei’s eyes, these two swordsmen were as faint as particles of dust. If it weren’t for Lin Ming, she wouldn’t have been interested in half a word they said.

But as she did listen to them, what she heard left her astonished.

The words that the two swordsmen spoke contained an inexplicable truth.

In particular, what the blue-clothed swordsman said. His words about climbing towards the peak of martial arts seemed to touch her own heart…

In this world there are endless mountain peaks. But, there must be a single mountain that is the highest. The higher a mountain peak, the more difficult it is for me. And to me, the most terrifying, the most horrifying this is that I simply don’t know where this mountain is…

I will never stop searching. I know that my vision is limited and I might never be able to find it, but I will climb up as I did before, unendingly. I do not need to truly reach the highest peak in this world, but as I climb, I will be more than happy to simply see that peak above me…

This is because when I climb to a new peak, my vision will expand further and I will be able to see where a higher peak lies. And when I climb up that new peak, I will find yet another higher one, and I will keep repeating this…

The words of this blue-clothed swordsman echoed in Sheng Mei’s ears for a long time. Even her fighting spirit seemed to inexplicably stir a little from these words…

This fighting spirit was also suitable to her.

As for later when they spoke of life and wine, they left even greater waves in Sheng Mei’s heart.

To savor the mellowness and spiciness of life, when the thoughts were truly muddled, perhaps that was when one could truly understand the mysteries...

The drunken blue-clothed swordsman’s words left Sheng Mei startled.

It wasn’t that the words he spoke contained some profound concept, but it was the appearance of words that should have never appeared in Sheng Mei’s imagination that left her heart racing.

She had an inexplicable feeling. That was that everything she saw in this dream might not be an illusion, but what Lin Ming truly experienced in the past!

The various names of places, the description of Lin Ming’s life, everything that these two swordsmen spoke of were full of vivid detail and life.

There were even concepts that she had never felt before.

The feelings of a martial artist were not like words of mortals that could be easily written on paper. Rather, they were things that they truly experienced, a sum of their adventures and philosophy on life.

It could be said that these feelings were their road of martial arts.

These two blue-clothed swordsmen’s road of martial arts was thickly colored in the paint of mortals. But in Sheng Mei’s mind, it was impossible for her to have such strange comprehensions.

Moreover, these feelings were clearly related to wine, but Sheng Mei herself didn’t drink wine, so how could she possibly come up with concepts of life and wine in this dream?

Could it be that what she saw before her wasn’t conjured from her imagination, but what Lin Ming truly experienced in the past?

Thinking of this, Sheng Mei’s heart shook!

Chapter 2152 – Unyielding

Why would Lin Ming’s memories appear in her dream?

Or, how could the Demon God’s Tomb have Lin Ming’s memories?

Thinking of this, Sheng Mei was left confused.

She couldn’t understand why. But all she could do now was quietly look on at Lin Ming’s life.

Her heart trembled all the while.

She felt anticipation because she wanted to know of Lin Ming’s life.

But what she felt more… was fear, fear that Lin Ming would die alone...

After she watched Lin Ming awaken, he bid farewell to the swordsmen and left that Sword Mountain.

She saw Lin Ming head up north, his body worsening with every day.

His cultivation fell at a dreadful speed; he had already become crippled.

Each day, each night, Sheng Mei would follow Lin Ming. Although his back was straight, it was actually filled with infinite desolateness and sorrow. She felt as if her heart was being shorn apart by a saber.

In the past when she left Lin Ming, she thought that he would face a bitter future. But as she truly experienced all of this following behind him, that feeling was completely different.

She was almost completely immersed, feeling for herself the mood of someone who had once stood at the peak of the 33 Heavens, a peerless genius who had saved humanity, but who had then been knocked off into the dust by a single move. Now, he only had several dozen years of life remaining…

Even though Lin Ming’s will was firm and steady, he still couldn’t resist such an attack.

Sheng Mei followed Lin Ming to Green Mulberry City.

She saw street vendors, fortune tellers, mortal martial arts masters, beggars, scholarly students, woodcutter, all sorts of mortals that she had never seen before.

Then, she saw a friendly aunt who gave Lin Ming sesame cake. As Lin Ming savored this sesame cake that was filled with the flavor of mortality, without knowing it, Sheng Mei’s gaze had turned hazy…

She couldn’t imagine how, when humanity was already close to despair, just how much Lin Ming withstood when he lost everything.

Perhaps… this was a fate crueler than allowing the Soul Emperor to freely kill him…

In Green Mulberry City, in the areas of his childhood, Lin Ming slowly visited each place.

Then Lin Ming continued north.

The northern desert was covered in fluttering snow. At some unknown time, Lin Ming’s face had turned pale and bloodless, and he shivered all over as he coughed up blood.

Time and time again.

Sheng Mei knew that what Lin Ming coughed up was his blood essence.

Although his divine soul was weak, his mortal body was still incredibly powerful and could regenerate blood. However, it was impossible for such a weak soul to control such a formidable mortal body; it simply couldn’t resist the exuberant blood vitality. Thus, his body tried to protect itself by coughing up all this blood.

If this continued then he would slowly die as his blood essence left him.

To Sheng Mei, every drop of crimson blood was blinding to the eyes.

She saw Lin Ming run into an old friend. Or, perhaps he had used his sense to find this person on his own initiative.

This was an old man, a man who had experienced the hardships of life to the fullest, and whose body was covered in hidden wounds.

She saw Lin Ming save a little girl.

This little girl’s eyes were pure and wide. Even in the chaotic age of war, when Lin Ming had become incomparably weak and fallen to the ground, only this little girl dared to give water to him.

She saw Lin Ming deal with several mortals. But because his body was wounded, blood continued to flow out…

A once incomparably talented individual had now become so thin and weak.

She saw Lin Ming bid farewell to these people, finally leaving by himself. His body had fallen to a horrendous state, and he limped with every step.

Sometimes, he would even tumble down as he walked.

His clothing was ruined, his hair was untamed and his face was dirty; he looked no different from a mortal beggar.

He wanted to enter a city, but in that wild age of war, a guard believed him to be a refugee and turned him away.

Lin Ming didn’t say anything nor did he do anything to that guard.

He quietly drew backwards and left. Beneath the setting sun, his thin and haggard figure became a needle that dug into Sheng Mei’s heart…

Vaguely, Sheng Mei’s surroundings seemed to blur. She remembered the words that Lin Ming had once said to her in the Soul World, before the great calamity of humanity had truly erupted…

“I remember… that when I was a mortal, an old friend of mine warned me not to be stubborn and practice martial arts. She didn’t want me to spend the rest of my days disabled on a bed. But, my answer was…

“The path of the martial artist is like a flame. Practicing the martial arts will only causepain. The dangers are countless and the road is filled with obstacles. Everyonewho walks down it will eventually turn to ash, but the true martial artist willbe reborn from these ashes. Even if I am only a small and weak moth, I willwalk into the flames without hesitation. I will fight my destiny for a one in amillion chance that I will experience my own samsara and be reborn as a flamingphoenix. And even now, I am no longer a moth…”

…..

I am not Empyrean Divine Seal. My road is one I will walk down myself. And the choices I make, I will not regret them in the future!

…

If only life stayed like the first time we met. Suddenly, looking back through the rivers of time, nothing fills the eyes but mist.

I must struggle in the dust and chaos. Even if I am only asmall wave, I will still bravely move forwards…

…

Sheng Mei was deeply aware just how persistent Lin Ming’s heart of martial arts was, just how unyielding it was.

In the past she had once urged him to give up all thoughts of saving humanity. At that time, Lin Ming had only been at the Holy Lord realm. No matter how one looked at it, he was completely unworthy of mention compared to the great tide of destruction that would sweep over the world; he wouldn’t even be able to cause a stir.

Once humanity perished, the small and weak Lin Ming would lose his protection. He would be swept up in the endless storm and likely destroyed.

But Lin Ming didn’t give up. He arrived by himself in the Soul World, searching out an impossible alliance with the spiritas.

Then he fought in the primal god realm. For a ray of hope, he went to the primal god realm to search out a path of salvation…

But now, Sheng Mei could only watch the back of such a person as well as the red blood that dripped from him…

Just what kind of change was this…?

Sheng Mei’s heart quaked.

Without following Lin Ming and experiencing all this for herself, she never realized just how bitter his struggle must have become.

“So many years have passed, he must have died already…”

Currently, everything that happened was from over 7000 years ago. And in any case, looking at Lin Ming’s physical state, he wouldn’t be able to last much longer.

But even so, Sheng Mei continued to follow him to confirm with her own eyes.

She saw Lin Ming go into a mountain valley to enter seclusion.

Sheng Mei saw with surprise that as Lin Ming’s life reached the precipice of despair, he began to disperse his martial arts. His weak soul was unable to withstand the strength of his blood vitality and his cultivation. Thus, he simply chose to drop down his cultivation to a level that his soul force could withstand!

Without a doubt, this would rapidly reduce his remaining life, and even make his final years much more painful.

But he continued forwards without turning back.

As if he wanted to break himself apart and rebuild from scratch, as if he were a butterfly that wanted to break free from its cocoon!

How was this possible!?

Sheng Mei shook her head in disbelief. His soul was so weak and the fires of his life were like a candle in the wind. If he dispersed his cultivation here, then he might simply die where he was!

This was the end. Perhaps the phantoms she saw could last a few more years, and this valley was Lin Ming’s final tomb.

All of this proved that the faint hope she had left within Lin Ming was something she did only to psychologically comfort herself for her own actions. Miracles could appear on Lin Ming’s body, yet what she envisioned would occur to Lin Ming was not a miracle, but an impossibility.

She watched as Lin Ming dispersed his cultivation. Blue veins stuck out from his forehead and he began to scatter blood essence from his pores.

The pain of this could be imagined.

Even so, Lin Ming didn’t cry out in pain once. His expression remained as firm as iron, without the least bit of pain or distortion.

He withstood such pain by himself, because he – would not yield!

Even if he had been pushed to a dead end!

Sheng Mei wasn’t cruel enough to watch. She could already foresee the following result.

Time passed. Through endless pain, Lin Ming grit his teeth and forced himself through it.

One year, two years…

With a completely ruined body, Lin Ming clenched his teeth and continued onwards. A normal martial artist would have died from the pain already.

But Lin Ming’s will was too formidable.

In these two years, the blood essence that overflowed from his body had already dyed the entire cave red. One could see the coagulated blood on the rocks.

Sheng Mei didn’t know how many times she saw Lin Ming fall onto the floor in dry heaves, how many times his forehead dripped with beads of blood, how many times he broke through his lips by biting them, how deep his toes and fingers dug into the rocky soil as it mixed with his blood.

However, he still didn’t give up. The unyielding will in his bones pushed him to give this his all!

Sheng Mei gently sighed, her eyes already becoming blurry…

Chapter 2153 – Child

Day after day, year after year.

Lin Ming continued his struggle in the cave, forcefully persisting for ten years!

Ten years later, Lin Ming already resembled an old man in his final years.

Although his back had been lonely, it had still be relaxed and straight.

But now his back was bent over with age.

His face was full of deep wrinkles and his eyes had become grim and dirty.

Sheng Mei could feel that Lin Ming would die soon.

The footsteps of the god of death rapidly approached. As someone who understood the Death Laws, how could she not feel the death energy emitting from within Lin Ming’s body?

This was the end…

Sheng Mei closed her eyes, no longer able to endure watching on. Even so, her sense continued to lock onto Lin Ming’s everything.

She watched as Lin Ming’s eye turned from pure brilliance to dirtiness, and then from dirtiness to nothingness.

Afterwards, his body no longer moved and his atrophied muscles became completely paralyzed. His beating heart becoming weaker with each beat, and his tiny wisps of soul fire slowly dissipating into the world…

Lin Ming, had finally, truly… died.

In that moment, Sheng Mei realized that Lin Ming’s spiritual sea had lost all color.

He still maintained his cross-legged sitting posture. In the final moments of his life, under extreme pain and duress, he still didn’t give up rushing towards that one slim ray of hope that never existed to begin with…

For a genius that once shook the heavens and earth, this was the final result. In a lower world, in a barren mountain cave that had no name, he had died alone.

No one knew just what sort of great legend was buried beneath this small mountain.

At this time, Sheng Mei’s face was wet with tears.

Although she knew that Lin Ming had died, she still quietly waited here. She continued to wait, feeling the entire time that a piece of her heart was being dug out.

She was determined to remember this place in her dream. In the future she would go back to the Sky Spill Continent, find this barren mountain hill and dig out Lin Ming’s bones to bury in her own inner world…

Year after year, Sheng Mei waited in this cave. She no longer knew how long she waited here.

She thought she had waited long enough; it was time to return.

But as she thought of returning, she was left stunned. She wanted to return, but return to where?

She was lost, as if the part of her heart that had been dug out was part of her soul.

And with this part of her soul missing, she suddenly forgot the road back.

Or, perhaps there was no road to begin with.

In this great world, whether it was the 33 Heavens or Dark Abyss, there was nowhere that was family to her…

What was family?

Safety? Warmth? Affection?

In this world, was there some place that could make her feel safe? Feel warmth? Feel affection?

She faced pressure at all times. She faced people who harbored dark and sinister intentions towards her, faced factions that fought each other and mistrusted each other.

She simply didn’t have a family.

There was no place where she could relax. In fact, there wasn’t even a place that could make her feel at ease as she could by lying in this dark cave, beside this corpse.

Thinking of this, Sheng Mei felt forlorn. She no longer wished to leave.

She was like a wild lone ghost, wandering about by herself, no longer remembering why she was here. All that remained in her memories was to stand guard in this place…

She seemed to have lost something important. But as for what it was, she couldn’t think of it.

She didn’t know how much time passed. It seemed endless, as if there were no end in sight.

But at some casual moment, she suddenly saw an unbelievably faint glow light up over Lin Ming’s corpse…

That dim light seemed to twinkle from the corner of a cube. And on that cube, all sorts of ancient and mystical runes flashed.

And that dim light itself possessed an indescribably mysterious aura. Like this, it wafted in between Sheng Mei’s eyebrows.

In that moment, in the depths of her soul, Sheng Mei shivered.

She seemed to awaken from a nightmare. As her body shook, the dreamland all around her shattered like glass!

Light flashed. Inexhaustible tattered thoughts flew around her. In a flash, Sheng Mei returned to a vast dark hall.

She dripped with a cold sweat as she gathered her scattered wits, recovering from the shock. She knew that she had nearly lost herself in that dream and had almost been unable to disentangle herself from it.

That was… a heart demon.

Everything she saw just now had become an incomparably strong obsession because of her heart demons, and what she saw tore at her soul again and again.

The marks that Lin Ming left in her memories were far too deep.

Sheng Mei’s life was filled with gray. What she faced was a life without hope. And at this time, no one was able to become a pillar that supported Sheng Mei, because no matter who it was they would eventually be overtaken by her and cast away in the dust.

In truth, she was incomparably lonely. She needed someone that could accompany her.

But the only person who could accompany her had been personally destroyed by her…

The impact of such a heart demon could be imagined. When a martial artist faced a heart demon, the most terrifying thought was that… their dream world would be even better than reality, and they would no longer wish to awaken from that dream.

Once that happened, they were destined to be lost forever!

Even though Sheng Mei had passed through nine reincarnations and her divine soul was incomparably powerful, she still couldn’t resist such a heart demon and in the end had nearly lost herself in that cave.

As she recalled that dream that seemed to have gone on for dozens of years, Sheng Mei discovered she could clearly remember everything about Lin Ming’s life.

She remembered Lin Ming’s hardship, downfall, resistance, everything was a vivid recollection that still twisted at her heart like a knife.

But in the final moments of that dream, there had been some unknown black sparkle of light that had allowed her to escape the clutches of her heart demons. As for what the light had been, she had no idea.

She didn’t even know if that spark of light had truly existed or not. Had it only been an illusion?

Could it be an illusion formed by her heart demons?

Just what was it?

Sheng Mei felt that the spark of light was extremely familiar. She should have been able to think about what it was, yet as she tried, it became even blurrier in her mind.

But at this time, as she was deep in thought, Sheng Mei’s heart chilled.

She could feel a terrifying aura approach.

She suddenly looked up. She could see a pale white youth with filthy eyes, whose body gushed over with rich death energy. This youth slowly emerged from the darkness to stand before her.

This old youth that resembled a corpse was the Soul Emperor!

Sheng Mei’s heart shrank.

Seeing the Soul Emperor, normally she wouldn’t been surprised. But why would the Soul Emperor appear in this scene? Was this a dream? Or reality?

She felt her memories were in chaos. Though she had just recently regained consciousness from that dream, she seemed to have forgotten something important, but she couldn’t recall what it was.

“You…”

Sheng Mei opened her mouth to speak. But before she could finish speaking, the Soul Emperor looked at Sheng Mei’s belly and diabolically grinned.

In that moment, Sheng Mei’s entire body turned icy cold. She didn’t fear the Soul Emperor to begin with, but as she realized something truly horrifying, she stood up tall, all blood draining out of her face!

The Soul Emperor pressed forwards, one step by one step.

Sheng Mei paled. She retreated, one step by one step.

Beads of sweat fell down from Sheng Mei’s forehead. Because at this time, she realized just what might be happening.

Finally, the Soul Emperor forced Sheng Mei into a corner.

He cruelly smiled, pointing at her belly and saying, “You used the strength of your nine revolution red lotus to seal away the child in your stomach. Are you worried that the growth of that unborn child will take away a part of the totem abyssal strength I left within you, thus alarming me?

“You sealed away that fetus for 7000 years, and in addition to the time you spent in time enchantments, over 10,000 years have passed. You truly thought this out well!

“What do you plan on doing? Surely you aren’t naïve enough to believe that you will be able to give birth to this child!”

Sheng Mei grit her teeth, not uttering a word. She quietly traced her spatial ring, already ready to bring out her bone sword.

“You want to resist me?” The Soul Emperor looked at Sheng Mei as if he had heard the funniest joke in the world. “Everything you have, I gave to you. Your cultivation methods were taught by me, and yet you actually think you can revolt against me! Hahahah!”

The Soul Emperor cackled and infinite killing intent burst out from him.

Then, his palm came crashing down onto Sheng Mei’s belly!

“No!”

Sheng Mei roared out loud. In this moment, she was like a mother tiger enraged at the injury of her cub, desperately attacking the Soul Emperor!

The black light of a bone sword leapt into Sheng Mei’s palm. Then, she turned towards the Soul Emperor and brought it mercilessly slashing down!

However, facing this sword, the Soul Emperor simply reached out two fingers and easily caught the blade!

Chapter 2154 – Awakened Dream

“This sword is quite good! The rate of your rising strength is such a pleasant surprise!”

The Soul Emperor laughed. At the same time, a horrifying force field spread out from him. It covered Sheng Mei’s entire body, instantly freezing her so that she couldn’t move an inch!

As for the Soul Emperor’s palm, after pausing for a moment, it continued to crash down on Sheng Mei’s belly with unstoppable momentum!

Roiling death energy swelled up beneath the Soul Emperor’s palm, causing the blood in Sheng Mei’s body to freeze over! She struggled to break free from the force field, however…

Peng!

A dull sound echoed out, as if something had been broken. Sheng Mei spat out a mouthful of blood as she tumbled backwards like a butterfly with torn wings.

In that moment, what was strange was that she didn’t feel pain in her body. Rather, she felt as if in her life she had lost something of extreme importance, something that left her despondent and utterly discouraged…

Over?

It was all over…

This was originally nothing but an impossible dream to begin with…

Sheng Mei could feel her consciousness blur. As for the pain in her belly, it couldn’t compare to even the tiniest percentage of the pain that wracked her heart.

She felt as if her entire life was laughable. She was well aware that from start to finish, she was only a tool.

She wanted to leave behind something in the senseless life she lived.

She had once placed hopes in Lin Ming, but Lin Ming had actually been personally destroyed by her.

She thought that there would never be color again in her life. But, when she left the Sky Spill Continent, departed the 33 Heavens and arrived at the Dark Abyss, she suddenly discovered that she was pregnant.

This was a matter that left Sheng Mei’s heart completely bewildered.

Her state of mind was incomparably complicated. She never thought that she would experience such a day.

She never imagined that after sealing away her heart, dooming herself to a life of loneliness and sorrow, vowing to never contaminate herself with useless feelings and emotions, there would actually be a day when she was a prospective mother.

Lin Ming and Sheng Mei were different races to begin with, so the chances of her becoming pregnant after sex was incredibly low. However, she had underestimated the strength of Lin Ming’s bloodline.

The appearance of this child left Sheng Mei at a loss for what to do.

The father of this child had been personally destroyed by its mother. Moreover, because of a variety of reasons, there was no way she could somehow allow this child a chance to survive.

But at this time the Soul Emperor just happened to go into seclusion to refine the Eternal Soul.

Sheng Mei could temporarily guarantee this child's safety. However, she knew that once this child was truly born, it would inevitably stir up the mark and energy that the Soul Emperor had left in her spiritual sea.

Then the Soul Emperor would surely know what was happening. Although he might not be able to immediately catch up to her because he was in seclusion, once he emerged she would surely have to withstand his rage.

And this child would undoubtedly die.

Sheng Mei once thought she could let this child live the life of a thorough mortal. In the Dark Abyss, she could open up a beautiful world like one from the 33 Heavens. She could buy up numerous ancient race slaves, allowing them to become residents in this world and to thrive and live on.

Then, she could allow her child to be born. She could accompany her child, gazing at the clouds, watching flowers bloom and fade.

She could satisfy all her child’s desires and live a life of good fortune and happiness.

Watching her child from birth, she could watch her child slowly grow, learn to walk, marry someone, age, and eventually pass on in their sleep…

She could only give this child of hers a short and brief life, a full and complete life before the Soul Emperor left seclusion. She could have her child believe themselves a mortal, living in their own idealistic dreamland…

However… when Sheng Mei decided to do this, she hesitated once more. She couldn’t imagine what would happen once she poured all of her love and joy into this child, and what would be left of her after her child died…

To live on through memories?

A small bug that lived amongst the withered leaves and branches would never know the true beauty and greatness of the world. If one wished to see all the world had to offer, they had to step towards the peak of martial artists. But because there were too many fetters, it was impossible to strengthen one’s heart…

However…

If one were to abandon all their fetters, what would be left over of life?

In these days, Sheng Mei was lost in a helpless daze. She watched the child grow in her belly with every passing day, and she knew she couldn’t sit back and allow this to continue.

Thus, she sealed away the growth of that child.

She found it hard to imagine her future, nor did she want to so easily arrange the future fate of her child.

But if this continued and the Soul Emperor were to leave seclusion, everything would be doomed to tragedy.

Sheng Mei felt as if she had rushed into a dead end. Would she also have to lose the only sustenance of her life…?

“Mama… why are you worried?”

As Sheng Mei was lost in confusion, a supple and weak child’s voice echoed in her ears.

This voice seemed to touch the softest parts of Sheng Mei’s heart.

Sheng Mei trembled!

She lowered her head and stared at her belly, her mind violently shaking like turbulent waves.

She could feel faint life fluctuations coming from her stomach.

This was her child, her flesh and blood!

In an instant, all the faith and will she had built up over the tens of thousands of years of her life instantly collapsed upon hearing the weak and tender voice of this child.

“Mama… I am so hot…” The child’s voice blurred, seeming as if it were in extreme pain. “There is a fire burning me, I can’t open my eyes…”

Fire?

Where did fire come from!?

Sheng Mei was left panic-stricken. She probed her belly with her divine sense, and what she saw left her drowning in a nine nether abyss!

There was a dark and ominous strength in her belly, like abyssal flames that burned away all. This strength wrapped around her child, wanting to melt away this tiny life!

This was the strength that the Soul Emperor had left in that palm just now!

“No!”

Sheng Mei felt as if someone were cutting open her heart with an axe. She placed her hands on her belly, using the power of her cold ice to neutralize the Soul Emperor’s evil strength and protect her child!

However, when Sheng Mei’s cold ice strength touched those dreadful abyssal flames, it was like snowflakes dropped in boiling water, instantly melting away.

The Soul Emperor’s strength was far too powerful. With her strength it was impossible to shake him.

The disparity was too great!

“Mama, I think I will die, it hurts so much…”

“No… no… my child, mama will save you. You must persist, you must fight on…”

Listening to the continually weakening child's voice, Sheng Mei’s heart was already crushed to pieces.

She hated her herself, hated herself for being weak!

What a ridiculous so-called proud daughter of heaven, what a pathetic peak of martial arts; she couldn’t even protect her own child!

“Mama… I can’t… last much longer… I have been inside mama for so long that I can’t remember… but I actually want to be born… I want to see mama…

“My mama… surely must be beautiful…”

That blurry child’s voice stopped here, like a dream that was suddenly shattered.

Sheng Mei’s hands trembled and her soul shivered… but, there was no longer the tiniest sound coming from her belly, no longer the weakest life fluctuations.

Everything seemed as if it never existed to begin with…

“No… no… no!!!”

Sheng Mei grasped her belly with all her strength. Her nails pierced through her smooth flesh and dripped with blood. Her eyes turned blood red and her hair scattered out, like a demon of the night!

Her child had died.

In her life, she no longer had her final sustenance!

Sheng Mei looked up. From her eyes, two trails of blood red tears flowed out!

Soul Emperor!

She wished to eat his raw meat, drink his fresh blood!

In that moment, Sheng Mei burnt all the strength of her soul. Like an erupting volcano, it broke into her spiritual sea, forming a terrifying storm!

Kacha! Kacha! Kacha!

With the sound of something breaking apart, in Sheng Mei’s mind, she burned away at everything with the horrifying storm formed by her soul.

She constantly attacked a black rune. This black rune formed a net of light that imprisoned this storm.

However, a crack suddenly appeared above this net of light!

The black rune couldn’t persist for much longer!

Ka ka ka ka!

More and more cracking sounds filled the air and the rune became increasingly dim. This storm was unleashed and could no longer be tamed; it became increasingly powerful.

Cracks spread throughout the net of light, and then, the strength it locked in suddenly erupted.

Peng!

With a loud explosive sound, strength crazily swelled outwards. The net of light as well as the black rune were torn to shreds!

The black rune was a spirit mark that had been sealed away in Sheng Mei’s spiritual sea. But at this moment, it blew apart to pieces!

Meanwhile, separated by endless space and time, in a dry and desolate soul sea of torment that seethed with innumerable bones…

Above this sea of torment sat a pale youth with snow-white hair. He sat on an island formed from piles of bones, meditating in quiet.

He had the appearance of a youth, but his body emitted a death energy that only a corpse should have.

This was the 33 Heavens’ Soul Emperor!

After stealing Lin Ming’s Eternal Soul in the Sky Spill Planet, he had gone into seclusion for nearly 10,000 years.

No matter how the waves of the soul sea stirred up, no matter how the bones floated, he was like a stone sculpture that remained unmoved for 10,000 years.

But today, his eyes flashed open.

He looked somewhere in the void, his filthy eyes flashing with profound astonishment.

“How… is this possible?”

The old youth stood up. His snow white hair fell down his back like a waterfall, making him look like a ghost.

His expression that was like a clear mirror that never saw any violent fluctuations of emotions for hundreds of millions of years, was now actually filled with amazement and disbelief.

Chapter 2155 – Regaining Consciousness

“She actually… broke through my… spirit mark? With her strength this should be impossible…”

The truth was that not to mention Sheng Mei, but even in the entire 33 Heavens and Dark Abyss combined, there wasn’t anyone capable of undoing the spirit mark left behind by the Soul Emperor.

This was because this spirit mark had taken deep root within Sheng Mei’s spiritual sea. Even if there was someone who possessed a soul force capable of rivaling the Soul Emperor’s, if one tried to forcefully undo the spirit mark then it would cause Sheng Mei’s spiritual sea to collapse.

Thus, this spirit mark could only be broken through by Sheng Mei herself.

The Soul Emperor reached out a bloodless white hand, the points of his fingers rapidly touching as he quickly deduced just what occurred. He wanted to figure out what this new turn of events was.

But bizarrely, he discovered that as he tried to investigate this matter, his efforts were hampered by layers of fog that blocked his sight so that he couldn’t clearly see what was occurring.

“What is happening?”

The Soul Emperor frowned. He did not like having anything surpass his control.

He narrowed his eyes and looked deep in the sea of misery and the endless skeletons that floated above it. Eventually, he sat back down and his mind returned to serenity once more.

Although the spirit mark he left in Sheng Mei’s spiritual sea had shattered, as long as he left seclusion then none of this would be a problem.

Currently, completely refining the Eternal Soul was the vital task at hand.

As for Sheng Mei, it was impossible for her to use this brief period of time to raise her strength to a level where she could escape his reach.

At this time, in the Demon God’s Tomb, Sheng Mei’s soul form had turned pale white without the least bit of blood. When she burnt her soul just now she had erupted with an unimaginable strength that had surpassed her present cultivation by several levels.

What should have been impossible had actually happened.

In the mortal world, during earthquakes when a mother saw their child being pressed beneath rubble, that delicate woman could actually erupt with a strength far surpassing that of an adult male, pushing apart stones that were several hundred jins to rescue their child.

What Sheng Mei just did was also the same.

This was a mother’s strength.

However, because she overdrew on her soul, it left her extremely weakened afterwards. Moreover, because Sheng Mei was immersed in her heart demons, with her weakened soul it would be impossible for her to resist the invasion of these heart demons.

She had already… lost consciousness…

………

At this time, in the bottom of the killing lake, in a deep underground cavern, a towering abyssal was crouched near a corpse. This abyssal stretched out a finger to pierce into the arm of this corpse and slowly absorb the power of demon gods.

The impact of the heart demons just now had been terrifying in intensity. Because Lin Ming possessed the Magic Cube, he hadn’t been affected the least.

He had also intentionally allowed himself to experience the attacks of the heart demons. Otherwise, he definitely would have been able to maintain his consciousness from beginning to the end.

Then, Lin Ming continued to be swept down by the vortex of the killing lake. After dropping for an unknown period of time, he was finally dropped into this deep underground cavern.

In this underground cavern there was not only him, but several other abyssals that had lost consciousness.

Lin Ming investigated them and discovered that these abyssals had already died.

During the test of the heart demons, the souls of these abyssals weren’t strong enough to withstand it. In the end their souls exploded to pieces and their spiritual seas had collapsed. Their blood vitality also slowly faded away. Before long, they would become nourishment for this strange world.

Seeing this scene, Lin Ming sighed with emotion. Each of these abyssals was an overbearing tyrant of their own land. Yet in the Demon God’s Tomb they were no different from cannon fodder.

It could only be said that the rank of this Demon God’s Tomb was too terrifying.

Through the 33 Heavens and the Dark Abyss, in all the universes combined, this was the highest rank, and the most terrifying mystic realm to exist.

Lin Ming continued his search. He wanted to see if these abyssals had any valuable treasures they left behind, and while at it he could also use Famine’s Swallowing Laws to absorb the bits of the power of demon gods still in these abyssals’ bodies before it faded away.

But at this time, another unconscious body fell into the cavern.

Peng!

The sound of this body landing was much lighter; it couldn’t be compared to the giant abyssal demons that crashed into the ground.

Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred. He stretched out his sense to search out the source of that sound. If his luck was good he could find this abyssal just as they died and then he could absorb even more of the power of demon gods from them.

However, when Lin Ming found that body with his sense, he actually froze. The one who just fell was not anyone else but a black-clothed woman – Soul Empress Sheng Mei!

“Sheng Mei… did she withstand the impact of the heart demons?”

Lin Ming’s mind tightened. After probing with his sense, he discovered that Sheng Mei still had a weak breath and heartbeat. However, she was deathly pale and her lips were blue. Her fires of life were weak and it was clear that she had overdrawn herself in the heart demon test just now.

Moreover, she was still immersed in her heart demons and hadn’t awoken.

This left Lin Ming surprised. The impact of heart demons had indeed been terrifying but he had easily passed it using the Magic Cube. But even if he didn’t use the Magic Cube, Lin Ming believed that with his Eternal Soul he could pay a certain price to persist through the heart demons.

In Lin Ming’s eyes, after reaching perfection of nine reincarnations, Sheng Mei’s divine soul was undoubtedly formidable. Although she couldn’t pass this test as easily as he did, she should still have been able to do so without losing consciousness.

Lin Ming swept out his sense. The already unconsciousness Sheng Mei could not resist Lin Ming’s sense. Lin Ming’s sense entered into Sheng Mei’s spiritual sea without any hindrance.

As Lin Ming saw the scene in Sheng Mei’s spiritual sea, he held his breath.

He had guessed that Sheng Mei had overdrawn her divine soul but he never imagined she had overdrawn herself to this extent. Her entire spiritual sea had dried up by over half!

And in the skies above her spiritual sea, deep dark cloud gathered. In these dark clouds, demons and ghosts rampantly danced and howled!

These were Sheng Mei’s heart demons. The degree of their formidability far surpassed Lin Ming’s own heart demons.

“Sheng Mei actually has such terrifying heart demons. Every heart demon is an obsession and fear of Sheng Mei’s heart… no wonder she couldn’t withstand this even with her divine soul of nine reincarnations.”

Lin Ming shook his head. With a nearly exhausted spiritual sea and such powerful heart demons, it was already a miracle that Sheng Mei could maintain the fires of her life without dying like the other abyssals.

Lin Ming fell into thought. If he didn’t quickly rescue her then she would likely fall into a permanent sleep and no longer awaken. And even if she did awaken, her spiritual sea would be forever wounded.

But if he rescued her, he wouldn’t know if she would be an enemy or friend in the future…

Between him and the Soul Emperor there would eventually be a battle. And when that time arrived, would Sheng Mei side with the Soul Emperor?

Perhaps the Soul Emperor had some method to restrain and control Sheng Mei. At that time if he wanted to fight the Soul Emperor, he might need to pass the test of Sheng Mei first.

If so, then he was only looking for bitter fruit to eat on his own.

But as he watched Sheng Mei’s divine soul gradually weaken, Lin Ming let out a gentle breath and opened the grandmist force field. After blocking out his surroundings, he lifted his right hand and the Magic Cube appeared in his palm.

Sheng Mei could be considered as having saved his life. Otherwise, 7000 years ago, whether it was Soaring Feather God King or the Soul Emperor, either one could have easily taken his life.

And no matter what, he should save Sheng Mei first. Even if he saved her she would surely be weak and definitely not a match for him. After saving her, could he somehow obtain more secrets of the Soul Emperor?

But doing so would likely completely expose his identity. If the Soul Emperor had left behind some sort of mark or contingency in Sheng Mei, then if he were to capture Sheng Mei there was a likelihood that his confrontation with the Soul Emperor would be shifted to an earlier time.

The present situation could be said to be filled with complicated intricacies.

At this time a red-clothed little girl emerged from the Magic Cube. She curiously looked at the slumbering Sheng Mei and said, “Brother Lin, isn’t this the big sister from the Akashic Dream Universe?”

“Mm, it’s her.”

Lin Ming lightly said. He gently patted the Magic Cube with one hand and some of the runes atop it began to sparkle. A dim light shot into the point between Sheng Mei’s eyebrows and then covered the skies above her spiritual sea. The layers of dark clouds that were her heart demons began to melt away like snow in the sun beneath this dim light.

Many heart demons cried out in pain and roared in misery. They wanted to plunge into Sheng Mei’s spiritual sea to hide, but in the end they were swept into the dim light and turned to ashes.

After eliminating all the heart demons, Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred and he poured a bit of his divine soul’s strength into Sheng Mei’s spiritual sea.

Like this, as if she had slept for an untold number years and awaited this moment, Sheng Mei slowly and quietly opened her eyes…

Chapter 2160 – Heavenly Demon Array

The Holy Scripture’s Laws were divided into the samsaric roads of life and death. But whether it was the road of life or the road of death, even if one had the complete Holy Scripture it still required a long period of meditation to perceive; it wasn’t something that could be completed in a few years!

But now, seeing this towering abyssal use the Laws of the Holy Scripture, although it was inferior to her own in certain ways, the difference wasn’t much off.

Moreover, Lin Ming seemed to have his own unique understandings of the Holy Scripture Laws, and these understandings were completely different from Sheng Mei’s.

At this time, Sheng Mei’s thoughts had already fallen into chaos.

How could this Ancient Eon Sect’s Ninth Elder thoroughly understand the Holy Scripture Laws?

Sheng Mei didn’t have time to think. At this time, the fierce battle between Lin Ming and the Great Flood Crown Prince heated up once more!

By now, the Great Flood Crown Prince no longer hid anything. His body erupted with dazzling divine light as he took off all his war armor!

As the purple gold war armor fell off, the demonic spirits around the Great Flood Crown Prince violently rumbled and countless heavenly demons roared as they rushed forwards!

After going all-out, the number of heavenly demons around the Great Flood Crown Prince had doubled, rising to 200,000!

200,000 heavenly demons gathered together, forming a giant wheel-shaped array. This array resembled an ancient totem, and these 200,000 heavenly demons formed the outline and ciphers of this totem. The entire array formation seemed as vast as the heavens, the power of this attack incomparable to before!

Seeing this Heavenly Demon Array, Lin Ming’s complexion turned dignified. Now, as his understandings towards the power of demons increased, he could see just how powerful this array formation was.

And at this time, Sheng Mei was also covered in the howling storm produced by the battle between the two. She watched as the Heavenly Demon Array formed and the Great Flood Crown Prince’s momentum rose higher and higher even as Lin Ming’s momentum was suppressed.

The Great Flood Crown Prince’s strength rose to a whole new level!

As for Lin Ming, he had clearly become much weaker due to the previous clash.

In this completely disproportionate follow up, it was obvious who was weaker with a single glance.

Sheng Mei watched Lin Ming silently grasp the Black Dragon Spear. She wanted to help him but she didn’t have much strength left remaining. There simply wasn’t anything she could do in her current state. Because of the impact of the heart demons in addition to her present weakness and the raging storm that blew everywhere, she slowly felt pain in her lower belly.

This pain was like a knife that stabbed at her heart. She didn’t fear anything happening to her, but she feared that the child in her womb might be injured.

If this continued then she really didn’t know just what possible consequences there would be!

Originally, Sheng Mei still had the totem strength left within her by the Soul Emperor. As long as she encountered a truly life-threatening situation, she could use this strength to eliminate all dangers!

But, this strength needed to be activated by the Soul Emperor’s spirit mark.

In a completely impossible situation, Sheng Mei had relied on the strength of a mother to overdraw her entire being and flush out the Soul Emperor’s spirit mark.

From that point on, while she had temporarily rid herself of the Soul Emperor’s control, she had also lost the ability to use the Soul Emperor’s strength.

However, Sheng Mei would rather die than willingly return to the shadow of the Soul Emperor.

In the storm, Sheng Mei tightly gripped her belly, her heart shaking.

She no longer had any cards hidden in her sleeves. If there was one thing she could depend on here, then that would be Lin Ming!

But the chances of Lin Ming winning were… too small…

If Lin Ming was killed then she would suffer a fate worse than death. As for her child’s fate, it would be even more tragic!

Sheng Mei bit down on her lips. She looked at Lin Ming. At this time, Lin Ming grasped his bone spear and faced the Great Flood Crown Prince. Because the bone armor on his back had split open in the vicious attacks, blood flowed outwards, dripping through the air. Seeing this shocking red color, a mix of emotions rose in Sheng Mei’s eyes.

Although Sheng Mei couldn’t accept this ‘fiance’ no matter what, in this moment of life and death, Lin Ming’s towering back had become deeply engraved into Sheng Mei’s heart.

His appearance was fierce and hideous and he was a quiet individual that never spoke much. But, in retrospect, Sheng Mei recalled that every time she was helpless or in distress, he never once took advantage of her while she was down, and instead stood in front of her.

“This is the end!” The Great Flood Crown Prince’s roar interrupted Sheng Mei’s thoughts.

At this time, the Great Flood Crown Prince’s hair was disheveled and his face was distorted. He originally thought that using all his strength to defeat Lin Ming was nothing but an insult to himself. But after repeated failures and repeated frustrations, all he wanted to do was to mercilessly kill Lin Ming using overwhelming strength.

Roar! Roar! Roar!

200,000 heavenly demons gathered. Cold winds howled as the world darkened.

Amongst the infinite demons, the Great Flood Crown Prince slashed his saber down at Lin Ming!

This saber condensed into a single line, the strength compressed to the limit. The potential within was so formidable that even the ancient array symbols that protected the walls in this mystic realm began to shiver!

But at this time, Lin Ming’s Asura Wheel had just been crushed and it would take time to reform it.

He poured the power of the nine stars into the Black Dragon Spear and brought it smashing down!

Bang!

A horrifying explosion of energy erupted outwards. A black storm enveloped the entire mystic realm.

The Black Dragon Spear’s spear light was entirely washed away!

Lin Ming’s eyes widened. He rapidly drew backwards, energy erupting from his body!

His strength seemed without end. Spear after spear, he thrust forth countless times. Hundreds and thousands of spear lights gathered together and crashed onto the Great Flood Crown Prince’s Heavenly Demon Array!

However, the Heavenly Demon Array was far too powerful. The difference in strength between the Great Flood Crown Prince who went all out and the Lin Ming who didn’t utilize the Asura Laws was obvious.

Kacha!

Spear light tore apart. Although Lin Ming just barely managed to disperse the Great Flood Crown Prince’s saber light, countless heavenly demons still hurtled down at him!

Lin Ming spat out a mouthful of blood. His body tumbled backwards as he crashed into the stone walls!

The bone armor and scales on his body split open in countless places. The two bone spikes on his elbows also broke apart.

Lin Ming’s strength had weakened not just a little with this collision, but by a great deal!

Sheng Mei’s heart skipped a beat.

The Great Flood Crown Prince viciously grinned.

The effect of this strike was what he was looking for!

“You’re finished!”

On the Great Flood Crown Prince’s face, demon seals began to appear. These were mystic demon seals that only special abyssal bloodlines possessed. These types of seals could be considered the secret technique of a clan.

After utilizing these demon seals, the Great Flood Crown Prince’s strength rose once more!

His body shook with energy. The sounds of landslides and tsunamis filled the air, and the heavens and earth howled as if they would flip over!

Aoo!

The 200,000 heavenly demons seemed to go mad as they became increasingly wild.

The Great Flood Crown Prince’s eyes burst out with killing intent. He slashed his saber down at Lin Ming once more!

With this saber strike, a black tsunami seemed to erupt. Waves rose to the heavens, blotting out the skies!

Just as Lin Ming was about to be torn apart by this saber light, he traced his spatial ring and flung out his right arm.

A bronze light flashed, becoming increasingly large as it spun about.

This was a giant bronze bell!

Atop this great bell, flowers and birds and insects were carved within, as well as all sorts of ancient demon marks.

Seeing the bronze bell, the Great Flood Crown Prince was stunned. “This is… the Yin Yang Twin Ghosts’ Yin Yang Twilight Bell? You… killed the Yin Yang Twin Ghosts!?”

The Great Flood Crown Prince was shocked. The Yin Yang Twin Ghosts were Demon Association Elders that were part of the Flood Alliance. They were blood brothers and their hearts and minds were linked together. They were inseparable and were also skilled in joint attacks.

On their own, the Yin Yang Twin Ghosts weren’t too strong. But together their combat strength was actually terrifying.

The Great Flood Crown Prince hadn’t known that the Yin Yang Twin Ghosts had perished and their life’s magic tool, the Yin Yang Twilight Bell, had fallen into Lin Ming’s hands. But now he was afraid that the Yin Yang Twin Ghosts had already died!

The Yin Yang Twilight Bell was a True Divinity spirit treasure that focused on defense. Moreover, it was of an extremely high rank and the heavy bell’s body was incredibly difficult to destroy.

But, it was impossible to stop an attack on the level of the Great Flood Crown Prince’s with this Yin Yang Twilight Bell alone. Moreover, this was a magic tool of others and Lin Ming had only possessed it for a short time, so the strength of the bell he could display was surely limited.

“Humph! You want to rely on that to stop me? How naïve!”

The Great Flood Crown Prince disregarded the bell and continued to cut downwards!

Clang!

With a loud bang, the Great Flood Crown Prince’s saber slashed down onto the Yin Yang Twilight Bell. The bell emitted a thunderous response, and as the saber light tore through it, a giant tear actually formed on the surface of the bell!

The bell was sent flying away by the saber strike! This bell only delayed the Great Flood Crown Prince’s saber strike for half a moment before it continued cutting down at Lin Ming without any hindrance. 200,000 heavenly demons howled, forming the Heavenly Demon Array to lock down Lin Ming in this killing strike!

Chapter 2165 – Riddle of Identity

“Just… what is going on here?” Lin Ming took a deep breath as he looked at Sheng Mei.

Sheng Mei said, “You should know that a great war erupted 10 billion years ago in the 33 Heavens, and in that war, several universes were destroyed and the ancient races were nearly completely annihilated?”

Lin Min nodded, “And then?”

“In the past, the Asura Road Master led the ancient races of the 33 Heavens to resist the abyssals. They waged fierce war against the six totem level abyssals and as the war dragged on, eventually the ancient races managed to seal away the Dark Abyss. This move removed the firewood from beneath the pot and severed the escape route of the abyssals. But at that time, there were still many abyssals that remained in the 33 Heavens, including totem level abyssals! These abyssals never imagined that the life forms of the 33 Heavens would have the ability to seal away the Dark Abyss.

“Without reinforcements, without supplies, the abyssals had their backs pushed to the river. Finally, they were slowly strangled to death by the overwhelming numbers of the ancient races. It could even be said that… the sealing of the Dark Abyss was the turning point of the war. If they Dark Abyss wasn’t sealed away then the abyssals could have returned to rest and restored their strength before making a comeback, finally rising into the 33 Heavens again and again until the 33 Heavens were destroyed.”

As Sheng Mei spoke to here, Lin Ming nodded. The things she said were all facts.

Whether it was 10 billion years ago or now, the 33 Heavens simply wasn’t a match for the Dark Abyss.

After all, the abyssals were life forms that managed to survive from the previous ancient universal era. They had a martial arts civilization that had been accumulated for over 100 billion years and this wasn’t something that the 33 Heavens could hope to compete with. Moreover, they were a race that had truly defied the heavens to change their fates. In a situation where the Heavenly Dao had sentenced them to extinction, they had relied upon the horrifying strength of their race to forcefully live on.

“The abyssals were at a dead end and they nearly died off in the encirclement of the ancient races. However, there were still totem level abyssals that managed to survive. They hid in space distortions and fell into a deep slumber, and at that time, the Asura Road Master had already gone missing…

“I don’t know the specifics of what happened 10 billion years ago and I don’t know how many totem level abyssals survived. I only know that up to several billion years ago, of the six totem level abyssals, only Deep and Famine survived.

“As for whether or not the current totem level abyssals are the same ones as those from 10 billion years ago, I am not sure…”

Lin Ming’s mind shivered. “What do you mean?”

Sheng Mei shook her head. “I don’t know. This matter is simply far too complex. My knowledge is limited, and I don’t understand the Soul Emperor. In fact, I don’t even know his name. All I know is that he is truly terrifying!

“In truth, the reason that the Soul Emperor has the appearance of an old youth is because several hundred million years ago, he seized the body of the true Soul Emperor, the true ruler of the 33 Heavens’ spiritas.”

“What!?”

Lin Ming was dumbfounded. “The true spiritas’ Soul Emperor… his body was seized and the current Soul Emperor is a fake… then could the spiritas be…”

Lin Ming’s entire body turned cold. Someone that could become the Soul Emperor of the spiritas must be at least an upper True Divinity, and likely an outstanding character even amongst upper True Divinities.

But, such a Soul Emperor had his body quietly seized by others, and not even the other spiritas True Divinities had detected it!

The current Soul Emperor was too terrifying!

For the last several thousand years the saints had fought a tumultuous war with humanity. But during this entire time, the spiritas had held their troops quietly in reserve.

The spiritas gave off a mysterious and ghostly feeling to Lin Ming. He simply was never able to figure out just what the spiritas wanted to do.

Now, with humanity’s strength having surpassed the anticipation of the saints, the war had reached a deadlock. Both sides had slaughtered each other and were greatly damaged.

The saints’ original plan was to eat up humanity and expand, but not only did they fail to eat up humanity but their teeth shattered in their attempt.

In the current impasse, both humanity and the saints mutually used up their strength. Wasn’t this the exact situation that the Soul Emperor desired to see?

And when the war between humanity and the saints entered its final act, could the Soul Emperor possibly… lead the abyssals of the Dark Abyss to enter the 33 Heavens once more?

At that time, would the 33 Heavens even have the strength to resist?

Although the Dark Abyss had been sealed up by the Eternal God Wall, who knew just how long this Eternal God Wall could continue sealing up the Dark Abyss?

Thinking of this, a cold sweat streamed down Lin Ming’s forehead. He looked at Sheng Mei, his voice a bit hurried as he asked, “You said that the current fake Soul Emperor is Deep, then what about the Deep in the Dark Abyss?”

“It is an avatar.” Worry flashed in Sheng Mei’s eyes. “Billions of years ago, Deep produced an avatar and when he managed to weaken the avatar’s strength to a low enough degree, the avatar was able to pass through the Eternal God Wall and dive into the Dark Abyss. The avatar slowly cultivated to become the current ‘Deep’. In fact, for all these billions of years, ‘Deep’ rarely appeared. As a puppet, whether or not this Deep avatar appeared was unimportant, and actually, not appearing made Deep’s avatar seem even more mysterious, even more formidable. The one that truly controls Deep King Road is the Soul Emperor. As for me, Deep Child, the Great Elder, and so forth, we are all merely chess pieces laid down by the Soul Emperor to control the Deep avatar in ruling over Deep King Road.”

The more Sheng Mei spoke, the more shocked Lin Ming was. Without a doubt, the Soul Emperor’s next move was to swallow up the entire 33 Heavens.

The Soul Emperor’s opponent had never been the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, but all lives that lived in the 33 Heavens!

“What can I do…”

A great pressure pushed down on Lin Ming’s shoulders.

He originally thought that the great calamity of the world was the disappearance of the 33 Heavens’ God Lamenting Wall and the saints invading humanity.

If they could defeat the saints then the great calamity would pass.

It was only afterwards that he learned of the existence of the Dark Abyss. It seemed that this current great calamity would be as terrifying as the one 10 billion years ago.

And now, before his first opponent, the saints, had been defeated, a second and more powerful opponent had appeared – the Soul Emperor!

This was a horrifying opponent, an opponent that he completely did not understand, but who he felt completely understood him instead!

In this situation, was there any strategy or method that could give them a chance?

Feeling Lin Ming’s worries, Sheng Mei also fell silent.

At this time, her thoughts were all incredibly complex. All the secrets she spoke of just now were the highest level of secrets of the abyssals. In truth, what she did now was no different from betraying her own race.

But, she said them anyways.

She didn’t hope for the Dark Abyss to annihilate the 33 Heavens, nor did she hope for Lin Ming to perish in the war. And, she absolutely didn’t wish to see the Soul Emperor rule over all of existence, because if he did, her fate would be truly pitiful.

At this time, Lin Ming suddenly looked up at Sheng Mei. Slowly and clearly, enunciating each word, he asked, “Are you an abyssal?”

Sheng Mei was stunned. She was about to subconsciously nod, but just before she did, doubts appeared in her mind…

She always believed she was part of the dark angel race.

But what was the dark angel race? In the Dark Abyss, this race was unbelievably rare and incomparably mysterious.

Moreover…

Sheng Mei recalled all those strange scenes in the dreamland of her heart demons…

There was that black-clothed little girl who always engaged in slaughter with the abyssals.

As well as the primal god race old man who seemed as if he was also callous and indifferent towards the little girl, but in truth paid careful attention to every single action she made…

From being locked down on a lonely island, facing the impact of the rough sea waves, the young girl had finally soared into the skies…

In that battlefield of slaughter, that peerless woman had finally made the ultimate blood sacrifice, becoming the incarnation of the Eternal God Wall to seal away the Dark Abyss…

And on this woman’s forehead was the same nine revolution red lotus mark, and her appearance was also completely similar to Sheng Mei’s…

Was this person… herself?

Was there a chance that these memories somehow came from her past life?

Sheng Mei’s thoughts fell into confusion.

And at this time, Lin Ming suddenly said, “I once entered the universe where the primal god race lived, and entered into a forbidden zone left behind by the Asura Road Master. In that forbidden land there was a Cold Ice Mirror, and this Cold Ice Mirror was a test. It recorded ancient geniuses from 10 billion years ago to fight trial challengers.

“And of all the matches I faced, there was a woman whose appearance was completely similar to your own.”

Lin Ming quietly said.

Hearing this, Sheng Mei’s heart shook and she was unable to speak for a long time.

“What else do you know of her?” Sheng Mei asked.

“I only know that in the end, she died on the Eternal God Wall, turning into bones…”

Chapter 2166 – The Joys of Life

“Eternal Wall, bones…”

Sheng Mei fell silent. Many things were now clear to her. 10 billion years ago, that peerless woman had sacrificed herself, turning into the Eternal God Wall with that Purple Card and blocking out the Dark Abyss!

But just who was that peerless woman? How were they related to each other?

There were still many things that Sheng Mei didn’t understand.

Lin Ming said, “About that mysterious woman from 10 billion years ago, what do you know?”

Sheng Mei sighed. Her ten fingers tapped the void in front of her, ripples blooming out in space. In the next moment, chaotic illusions gathered in front of Lin Ming, turning into a scene.

This scene was what Sheng Mei saw in the dreamland of her heart demons.

In that dreamland, everything she remembered was blurred. She could only reproduce the several scenes that left the deepest impression on her.

Lin Ming quietly walked out. He saw the mysterious young woman facing a hellish level of training, and also saw her engaging in life and death slaughter.

Finally, the images froze as the mysterious woman sacrificed herself, becoming the manifestation of the Eternal God Wall.

Lin Ming was startled. He said, “I see, so that’s what happened…

“The Purple Card was used to seal up the Dark Abyss, and when Mo Eversnow brought Fishy to pass through the Eternal God Wall, the reason Fishy suddenly disappeared was because she had been drawn in by the Purple Card.

“Fishy was a life form that evolved from the Purple Card, so it’s reasonable for the Purple Card to draw her back in…”

Lin Ming was originally worried about Fishy, afraid that she somehow got into an accident in the Dark Abyss. But now he learned that she had returned to the Purple Card.

With this, he finally felt relieved. The inner space of the Purple Card should be the safest place in the entire universe for Fishy. In particular, now that the Purple Card has turned into the Eternal God Wall, not even totem level abyssals were capable of shaking it.

“However, that mysterious woman who sacrificed herself 10 billion years ago, how is she related to the Immortal Sovereign? Is she the Immortal Sovereign?”

Lin Ming looked at Sheng Mei. It was obvious that there wouldn’t be any answers from asking her this. Sheng Mei just wouldn’t have any answers concerning something that might be her past life.

“Lin Ming, what have you experienced these past years?”

Sheng Mei turned to Lin Ming, her eyes deep and filled with a multitude of emotions. Worry, guilt, joy… all sorts of feelings mixed together, jumbled in a way in which not even Sheng Mei could discern what she was feeling.

She felt extremely concerned towards Lin Ming. But at the same time, she found it difficult to face him.

Subconsciously she had a desire to approach Lin Ming. But at the same time, she felt that he was actually too far away from her.

This sort of contradictory mindset caused Sheng Mei to feel as if there were some invisible wall separating the two of them.

This also made it so that she always strolled along the edge of this wall, wary and cautious, not daring to take a single step past it.

“It’s too complicated to say. I will send you a message with my spiritual sense.”

Ever since parting with Sheng Mei, Lin Ming’s life experiences could be said to have been filled with twists and turns.

Amongst his experiences, there were difficult tribulations and hardships, as well as successful returns and events that turned the tide and lifted the spirit.

Lin Ming sent out his spiritual sense. A beam of light shot into the point between Sheng Mei’s eyebrows.

With it, all sorts of things that Lin Ming experienced in the last 12,000 years were transmitted into Sheng Mei’s spiritual sea.

Although thought transmissions were extremely fast, this transmission still took a quarter hour of time.

During this period, Sheng Mei saw a man that struggled through his fate. Someone, who even though they were small and weak, still never succumbed to the destiny of being destroyed by the strong.

From suffering to despair, to a rise back to the top of the mountains… many times, a powerhouse was not just strong, but firm and unyielding in their heart.

It was hard to describe in words everything that Lin Ming experienced. After Sheng Mei watched it, she didn’t know what she felt in her heart. Admiration, guilt, sorrow, heartache… a kaleidoscope of emotions that muddle her senses.

After a quarter hour, Lin Ming withdrew his spiritual sense. Sheng Mei slowly composed herself. Then, she looked at Lin Ming, and as if she wanted to lift the pall of awkward silence between the two, she awkwardly said, “Are your wives and child doing well…?”

That thought transmission Lin Ming sent didn’t contain every bit of information. The vast majority of things were still unknown. For instance, Lin Ming hadn’t sent anything concerning his family or friends.

As for information he needed to hide like the Magic Cube, he naturally didn’t describe these things much.

Sheng Mei also saw the Magic Cube when Lin Ming battled the Great Flood Crown Prince. She had a faint guess about what the Magic Cube was, but tactfully didn’t ask and instead pretended as if she never saw it.

“Mm, they are doing well.”

Lin Ming subconsciously glanced at Sheng Mei’s belly as he spoke.

Seeing Lin Ming’s gaze, Sheng Mei bit down on her lips and quietly pressed her hands against her belly.

Ever since this small life appeared in her, Sheng Mei felt that it was impossible for her mood to return to the motionless lake surface that it used to be.

Now her thoughts were prone to fluctuations. As for her energy, she used to pour everything she had into chasing after the peak of martial arts, but now she slowly shifted her attention to the child in her belly…

In particular, after knowing that she might have had a ‘past life’, Sheng Mei’s thoughts were wrapped in a layer of confusing fog. She didn’t know what her future would be or how she would end up.

She had a faintly ominous premonition. As for the child in her belly, it had nearly become the only repose left in her life.

This child was already the most important part of her life.

Lin Ming stared at Sheng Mei. Then, he lifted his hand and slowly touched her belly…

Sheng Mei was startled. She subconsciously wanted to take a step backwards, but she eventually stopped and let Lin Ming’s hand approach.

Finally, Lin Ming’s hand fell onto Sheng Mei’s smooth belly. His palm was warm and somewhat numbing…

Time seemed to slow to a crawl in that moment.

Within this underground cavern, silence filled the air. Lin Ming’s hand gently touched Sheng Mei’s belly. The two of them had incomparably vast spiritual seas. With just a little physical contact, they could feel each other’s soul fluctuations and magnetic life fields.

This sort of feeling of touching together their lives was incomparably beautiful.

And in that moment, Lin Ming also clearly sensed the life fluctuations of Sheng Mei’s child.

These fluctuations fit perfectly with his heart, connected to his blood…

Without a doubt, this was his child.

Taking a deep breath, Lin Ming drew his palm back. His slowly looked up at Sheng Mei, and could see his image clearly reflected in her pupils.

“Do you not plan on… undoing the seal?”

Lin Ming suddenly asked. Sheng Mei lightly said, “Once this child is born, the Soul Emperor will know of it. Although I managed to push out the spirit mark that he left in my body, there is still a part of his energy hiding within me. I have no means to flush this energy out… and as long as this energy exists, the Soul Emperor can control me.”

As Sheng Mei spoke to here, a dispirited sorrow flashed in her eyes.

She had the strength of a True Divinity, yet she wasn’t even capable of protecting her own child.

“You can give me the child.”

Lin Ming’s few words caused Sheng Mei’s heart to shrink.

Give Lin Ming her child?

Lin Ming was the child’s father. If she gave the child to Lin Ming, then he would naturally take good care of it.

But to give away the only hope left in her life, Sheng Mei felt an ache in her heart, as if she were too reluctant to part.

If she gave her child to Lin Ming, then even though the Soul Emperor would know, only she would have to face the Soul Emperor’s anger in the future.

Sheng Mei was well aware that she was only a chess piece to the Soul Emperor. Although she faintly understood what endgame he was playing towards, she didn’t know what steps he would take to get there. As a chess piece, if she couldn’t rid herself of her destiny then what awaited her was an incomparably miserable fate.

But…

She didn’t choose.

She knew that only by passing Lin Ming her child would it have a slim chance of survival.

Without a doubt, Lin Ming was the only one in this universe who had hopes of resisting the Soul Emperor, even though these hopes were incredibly dim.

Sheng Mei grit her teeth. With shaking hands she traced her own belly, gently whispering, as if she were speaking through a dream…

“My child, mommy will no longer seal you, mommy will let you be born…”

Her hands flickered as if she were playing a zither. Her ten fingers tapped rhythmically as runes shined atop her belly, shimmering like stars.

A seal was slowly undone.

Then another.

As seals were undone one after another, a faint glow began to emerge from Sheng Mei’s belly.

In the dark mystic realm cavern, this glow was like a group of fireflies gathered together.

Covered in this glow, traces of tears appeared at the edges of Sheng Mei’s eyes.

With it, an aura of life gently overflowed, like a new spring rain, like soft and tender buds growing in the moist dirt.

As if beginning to wake up from a slumber that lasted for thousands of years, this aura brought with it a pitiful feeling that touched the heart and soul.

This was a new life, a new start, a new hope...

This was Sheng Mei’s child and also Lin Ming’s child…

In this moment, Sheng Mei could clearly feel that this small life in her belly was incomparably overjoyed at having been unsealed after thousands of years.

This small life stretched out, and accidently kicked out a foot.

Feeling the gentle kick at her belly, that faint touch, Sheng Mei’s heart shivered. In the next moment, tears flowed.

“It… it moved…”

Sheng Mei covered her mouth, her voice somewhat vague. This was the feeling of motherhood, the joy of being able to sense the growth of one’s child, to watch as someone who was born from their body slowly grew up. It was something that couldn’t be described with words alone.

“My child is about to be born…”

Sheng Mei closed her eyes, her eyelashes quietly shivering. At this time, she felt as if nothing else mattered.

She only wanted to stay here and wait for the birth of her child.

Her child seemed to be… a girl.

Would her daughter look like her?

Chapter 2167 – Little Life

After undoing the seal, Sheng Mei’s energy had been completely poured into her child.

This underground mystic realm cavern contained an incomparably pure heaven and earth origin energy and power of demon gods. Sheng Mei sat in meditation every day, absorbing the surrounding heaven and earth energy. But, she didn’t absorb this energy for herself, but for her child to help her grow.

Maybe because the seal had been in place for too long, but after the seal was undone, the small life began to rapidly grow within her. The origin energy that Sheng Mei drew in was absorbed by this small life without a single drop remaining.

This speed of growth could be described as terrifying.

Sheng Mei and Lin Ming stayed in this cavern for over half a year.

Sheng Mei’s belly already started to protrude a little. As she felt the growth of her child every day, a smile would carelessly appear on her face.

Although this cavern that could only be described as deathly silent was dark, Sheng Mei had undone the seal on her child here and also had Lin Ming accompanying her. Because of that, the environment around her had become warm and touching. This sort of life brimmed with a faint happiness…

But, what left Sheng Mei sighing at times was that during this half year she rarely spoke with Lin Ming. Most of her time was spent in meditation, and as for Lin Ming, he spent the majority of the time studying the demon relief below the cliff and also studying the ancient bronze coffin held in the mouth of the demon relief.

The two of them would occasionally meet eyes, but oftentimes they would mostly exchange small talk and greetings. Even if they spoke, it would mostly be speculations about this mystic realm and discussions on Laws.

Besides that, Lin Ming and Sheng Mei basically didn’t speak to each other. Perhaps because of those special events that occurred 7000 years ago, the two of them might have had a beginning that was flooded with misunderstanding and hatred. Because of that, the two of them might not be able to clearly see each other’s heart, and even if they did, they still maintained a distance, one that was neither too friendly nor too aloof.

This might be a form of self-preservation, it might be a way to protect each other’s self-respect and esteem, it might be because of a fear of an uncertain future, or it might even be in fear that in the future, the two of them would head in opposite directions…

In order to avoid a greater tragedy in the future, to avoid them wounding each other even more, neither was willing to take the first step forwards.

Time passed. Sheng Mei carefully maintained this distance. She was like a noble and sensitive cat that prowled the night.

It was just that sometimes at night, she would speak to the child in her belly, pouring out all the emotions and thoughts that she had sealed away in her heart…

…..

Like this, two years passed.

Lin Ming and Sheng Mei’s lives continued without much change. Occasionally, they would touch each other’s soul fluctuations and life fields. Whether it was Lin Ming or Sheng Mei, this type of contact between the magnetic fields of their lives was a pleasant experience.

On this day, Sheng Mei’s eyes flashed open from meditation. At this moment she felt an incomparably clear life fluctuation emerge from her belly.

Then, a soft and obviously childish voice chirped out, “Mommy… Mommy… I want to see you a little bit sooner…”

Although this voice was weak, it caused Sheng Mei’s heart to quiver!

In the dreamland of her heart demons, she had heard her child speak. She never imagined that in reality, just as her child was about to be born, that her child would actually speak, and her tone was actually extremely similar to that child in her dreamland!

Everything that happened in that heart demon dreamland was clearly fake, but as she recalled her experiences there, Sheng Mei was left seeped in anxiousness.

She already vowed that even if she were to be crushed to pieces and her soul destroyed, she would never allow that scene in her dreams to occur in reality!

“My child, mommy is here, hurry and grow a little faster and you can see mommy soon.”

Sheng Mei said with a faintly excited expression as she stroked her belly.

And at this time, Lin Ming who was studying the demon relief below the cliff also heard the conversation between Sheng Mei and the child.

His breathing sped up. His figure flashed and he arrived beside Sheng Mei.

“She… she spoke?”

Lin Ming’s expression was filled with joy. His child had been able to speak even within her mother. This sort of perception and awareness was absolutely not something that a mortal child would have.

Once his child was born, she would absolutely be a monstrous genius when it came to cultivation.

Before Sheng Mei could nod, the little life in her belly asked, with an uncertain tone, “You are… Daddy?”

Although this small life couldn’t see the outside, she could see use her heart to perceive the world beyond.

“That’s right!” Hearing this small life call him daddy, Lin Ming felt feelings surge in his heart. There was satisfaction, pride, happiness… he wanted to hold this child in his arms and take good care of her.

But what a pity, she still hadn’t been born…

“My child, you must grow up well. Once you are born, daddy will teach you martial arts so that you can beat up all the bad guys.”

Lin Ming spoke from his heart, his expression filled with tender love.

However, the small life in Sheng Mei’s belly warily said, “Daddy, do you like me?”

“Of course!” Lin Ming replied without hesitation. Was that even a question?

“But...” The childish voice hesitated a little, “Then how come you’ve never touched me and rarely come to see me? It’s always been mommy speaking to me, but you’ve never spoken to me? Daddy feels like a stranger…”

This soft infant’s voice sounded in Lin Ming’s ear, knocking him silly as if it struck him like a heavy hammer.

He actually… was left speechless.

That was right. Two years ago, he had touched Sheng Mei’s belly, and that was to feel the life fluctuations of the child and determine that this small life was his own flesh and blood.

But after that, he never touched the child again, because touching the child was in truth the same as touching Sheng Mei…

As for speaking with his own child, Lin Ming never imagined that this would occur. He never thought that this small life would develop such a degree of consciousness and he never spoke to the child because that would be speaking to Sheng Mei’s belly. In Lin Ming’s point of view, this seemed a bit idiotic…

Thus, for these past two years it was Sheng Mei speaking to the child in her belly on her own. Lin Ming’s exchanges with this small life were nearly zero…

So, it wasn’t wrong for this little life to call him a stranger at all.

“Mommy, I don’t think Daddy likes us…”

The little life seemed to be more and more sure of its feelings. Its soft voice echoed in Lin Ming and Sheng Mei’s ears.

Lin Ming was left even more speechless. He froze up. He originally wanted to reach out a hand to touch his child, but when it was halfway out, he took it back, extremely embarrassed.

And on the other side, Sheng Mei’s thoughts were also complex. She gently traced her belly. She originally wanted to say ‘How could your daddy not like us?’, but as these words reached the tip of her tongue they fell away once more. This was because she didn’t have the belief to say such words.

She looked up at Lin Ming, not sure what expression to make…

“Daddy really doesn’t like us. I’ve already been hated before I’ve been born. Aiya, I think I should follow Mommy instead.”

The soft childish voice seemed to sigh like an adult. And faintly, one could sense the cunning playfulness of a child in the voice.

But at this time, whether or not these words were the true thoughts of this strange and playful little child were unimportant.

That soft and childish voice had already touched the softest parts of Lin Ming’s heart, making it feel as if his heart had been gripped by needles.

He quietly bent over and held onto Sheng Mei as well as the child in her belly.

He said in a warm tone, “Daddy likes you. No matter what happens to you in the future, no matter what dangers you face, daddy will stand in front of you and look after you and protect you…”

Like this, Sheng Mei was held by Lin Ming. She stiffened for a bit, her thoughts in tumult as she scrambled for something to say.

“Then you will also protect Mommy?” The small life earnestly asked.

“Of course!”

Lin Ming’s voice wasn’t loud, but it was solid and true.

Sheng Mei shivered. She looked at Lin Ming and at her belly, her eyes unknowingly turning wet…

She didn’t know what would happen in the future, but as long as she faced it bravely, then what did it matter?

At this time, Lin Ming quietly spoke in Sheng Mei’s ears. “After we leave the Demon God’s Tomb, come with me…”

This simple and light commitment didn’t have any illustrious words nor was it filled with the heated vows of love between men and women, but these few simple words caused Sheng Mei’s heart to shake and her misty eyes to start tearing up…

“He… will find us…”

Sheng Mei sadly said. She had already decided to bravely face the future, but she had never thought of accompanying Lin Ming. To the Soul Emperor, she was like a beacon at night. Wherever she went, he would be able to easily find her.

She didn’t want to drag Lin Ming into her mess. Just a simple promise from him was more than enough.

“I know…” Lin Ming gently traced Sheng Mei’s cheek. “I once had nothing in this world, but I grew step by step until I reached where I am now. I once broke through the chains of the Heavenly Dao to change my life and destiny. I once fell to the lowest valley, but I crawled back up. I once faced the overbearing might of the saints to find a moment of respite for my race. I have already gone through so many ‘onces’ before, so why should I fear the future?”

As Lin Ming spoke, he slowly pulled Sheng Mei to his chest.

Chapter 2168 – Demon Bone

Ever since the little fellow developed her own consciousness and was able to speak, her faint and immature voice would occasionally echo out in the cavern.

Perhaps because she was sealed away for too long, the child was particularly rambunctious and naughty. At the start, because her soul force was weak, she would make a ruckus but go to sleep soon afterwards.

But later, as the birth of the child approached, she became increasingly curious and intelligent, even pestering Sheng Mei and Lin Ming to tell her about how they met.

From when Sheng Mei and Lin Ming first met in the Asura Road’s final trial, to their reunion in Soul World’s Akashic Dream Universe, retelling this part of their story wasn’t a problem. But when the child specifically asked how Sheng Mei and Lin Ming got together and how she became pregnant, this question actually left Sheng Mei at a loss for words.

Sheng Mei simply didn’t know how to describe her experiences with Lin Ming at the Sky Spill Continent 7000 years ago.

And every time Sheng Mei would try to vaguely describe events, the little child would actually ask Lin Ming instead.

Regarding this, Lin Ming was left speechless. He didn’t understand how his child could speak before she was born but also have so many weird and eccentric thoughts. Could this child have possibly inherited a part of Sheng Mei’s memories, or even his own?

Days passed. The little fellow finally had a name – Lin Meng, with her childhood nickname being Jiu’er.

The name was chosen by Sheng Mei. The ‘Meng’ from Lin Meng was an ancient word for dream and the word ‘Jiu’ was an ancient word for nine.

She had dreamt of her child in her heart demon dreamland and also dreamt of Lin Ming’s 7000 past years of life.

In a sense, the reason she resolved her mind to undo the seal and have her child be born was because of her heart demon dreamland.

Since the child was to be born because of a dream, it was also named after a dream.

As for the childhood nickname of Jiu’er, that was because Sheng Mei had experienced nine reincarnations, and those nine lives she lived were live nine different dreams.

With this little fellow sneakily adjusting the mood all the time, the relationship between Lin Ming and Sheng Mei became much closer.

Slowly, three years passed in this cavern beneath the killing lake.

Sheng Mei’s belly protruded; soon, the child would be born.

But on this day, as Sheng Mei sat in meditation, she saw a red flash of light from below the cliff. This flash of light gushed out like a thick fountain of blood, bringing with it an intense infernal energy.

Sheng Mei was startled. She immediately branched out her sense, “Lin Ming, what is it?”

In these past years she knew that Lin Ming had been studying the demon relief and the ancient bronze coffin below the cliff all this time. As for what he was actually studying, she didn’t ask him.

If it were before, then when it came to this extremely mysterious mystic realm that might be involved with the ancient Demon God from 100 billion years ago, she would naturally be curious about it and would want to find out any possible secrets.

But because of the growing child in her belly now, Sheng Mei kept a respectful distance from the ancient totems that were filled with a dark and evil energy.

However, the sudden explosion today left Sheng Mei’s heart gripped. She was afraid that something had happened to Lin Ming.

Her body flickered and she arrived near the cliff edge. She could see that demon relief diabolically grinning; it seemed that was where the rich infernal energy had come from.

The demon relief’s mouth was open and the ancient bronze coffin in its mouth had also opened!

Sheng Mei focused her eyes and discovered that within the ancient bronze coffin, there was an even smaller coffin.

If so, then this large coffin that was opened was only the ‘outer coffin’, and the smaller coffin inside was where the corpse was truly buried.

Seeing the inside of this large coffin, Sheng Mei frowned.

The inside was filled with viscous dark blood. The small coffin seemed soaked in bloody water and seemed incredibly evil, full of wicked corruptions.

As if there were some peerlessly supreme demon sealed within the coffin. A single glance at the coffin caused an ominous feeling to rise up in one’s heart.

“Lin Ming…”

Sheng Mei said with a bit of worry. During these years she simply hadn’t paid any attention to this ancient bronze coffin and she had no idea what Lin Ming had discovered.

“Mama, what is that in front of us? It’s so evil…”

Jiu’er’s voice sounded out. Sheng Mei waved her hands and an energy enchantment appeared in front of her, isolating out all the infernal energy released by the demon relief.

Now, Sheng Mei had restored a great deal of her strength. As for the spiritual damage she received by overdrawing her soul force, that had also been cured by Lin Ming using the Magic Cube.

Lin Ming didn’t hide the Magic Cube’s existence from Sheng Mei. In any case, she had already seen it.

However, although Sheng Mei had a faint guess as to what the Magic Cube was, she actually never took the initiative to ask Lin Ming about it.

With the protection of the force field enchantment blocking out the infernal energy, Jiu’er felt much better. She quickly repositioned herself and soon fell asleep.

Sheng Mei looked at Lin Ming, “Did you activate the coffin?”

Lin Ming nodded. “Yes. In these past years I have been studying this demon relief all this time as well as what is in this ancient coffin. I feel that… there is no lucky chance in this cavern, and instead it is a deeply evil and ominous place!”

The Demon God’s Tomb was not filled with unrivalled lucky chances at every corner. There were many places that were completely and purely death zones. While lucky chances were often accompanied with risks, there were many times when risks weren’t accompanied with lucky chances. Once someone entered these evil and ominous places then they would just die in vain.

For instance, the killing lake. Even though so many formidable abyssals had entered, the only ones left were Lin Ming and Sheng Mei.

“Is there any danger in opening it?” Sheng Mei asked. She was worried about the child in her belly.

Lin Ming shook his head, “If I’m not mistaken then whatever is in this coffin is lifeless; there won’t be any great dangers.”

Even though he said this, he still brought out the Magic Cube and flew in front of Sheng Mei.

The Magic Cube slowly spun atop Sheng Mei’s head, covering her in layers of black light.

With the Magic Cube protecting Sheng Mei and Jiu’er, Lin Ming felt much more at ease. He placed his hands atop the small coffin and slowly pushed.

This ancient small coffin clearly wasn’t sealed. There were obvious gaps in the small coffin, and the thick blood in the large coffin flowed into the smaller coffin through these gaps.

Sheng Mei held her heart; she didn’t know just what was in the coffin.

As Lin Ming slowly pushed open the lid, what was revealed inside was also a thick pool of viscous blood.

The entire small coffin overflowed with blood. This blood seemed to have been sealed away for countless billions of years. It was completely dark, so thick that it seemed coagulated into a nearly solid substance!

Even one’s divine sense couldn’t penetrate this blood, as if there was a mysterious and evil world hidden beneath it.

As the coffin opened, the blood emitted a dark and dire aura, as if countless demon souls and wills were boiling within and clawing outwards, howling in pain the entire time.

Looking at this scene, Lin Ming’s complexion was dignified.

Then, he reached out a hand as if he wanted to pierce it through the thick pool of blood.

“Lin Ming! What are you doing!”

Sheng Mei was frightened and she called out to Lin Ming to stop him. If he were to stick his hand into this billion year old blood pool, who knew what would happen? Perhaps this blood might be incredibly poisonous and corrosive, or there might even be some amazingly potent curse contained within.

Lin Ming glanced back at Sheng Mei, trying to put her at ease. Then, he decisively reached in his hand. The surface of Lin Ming’s arm was covered with a force field formed by grandmist energy and it pushed away the thick blood.

His hand gently stirred in the blood pool. After an incense stick of time, Lin Ming felt through the blood pool and then slowly drew out his hand.

As he took his hand out, he also pulled out something long with it.

This thing was pitch black all over and 13 feet long; it was twice the height of Lin Ming.

It resembled a hideous centipede. From beginning to end, this long thing was divided into sections and each section had three gruesome bone spikes jutting out. Each spike was half a foot long and appeared incredibly ferocious.

Lin Ming placed it on the ground. This thing was thicker than Sheng Mei’s thigh and shined with a metallic sheen, even as it glowed with a cold brilliance.

“This is…” Sheng Mei felt her heart race as she saw this thing. This was truly an evil and ominous object. It contained a bloody infernal energy within that was so thick it had turned into substantive essence.

“Is this a weapon refined by an ancient peerless demon?”

Because of the metallic sheen, the icy cold light, and the thick bloody infernal energy, one couldn’t help but form such a guess.

However, Lin Ming thought for a moment and shook his head. He said, “This is not a weapon but a part of a skeleton. To be more accurate… it is the spine!”

Chapter 2169 – The Scheme of 100 Billion Years

“Spine?”

Lin Ming’s words left Sheng Mei stunned. This spine was simply too hideously fierce. Moreover, its texture didn’t seem like bone at all but like some kind of metal, and the icy cold feeling it gave off was like that of a peerless weapon.

Lin Ming grasped the 13 foot spine and slowly flew up. As he flew above the cliff, the spine dangled below. If the spine itself was so long then if the master of the spine was still living, they might have been 30 feet tall at least.

Moreover, this spine emitted such an evil and ominous aura that a frightening thought suddenly appeared in Sheng Mei’s heart. “This shouldn’t be… the spine left behind from the Demon God that died 100 billion years ago!?”

As Sheng Mei uttered these thoughts, her eyes as she looked at this spine changed. To the abyssal race, the ancient Demon God of 100 billion years past was a spiritual god that ruled over them all. The Demon God’s spine… just what sort of concept was that?

Lin Ming carefully rubbed one of the spine’s sharp bone spikes, feeling the energy fluctuations and vast strength of blood vitality that it emitted. He shook his head and said, “I don’t know. I can only confirm that this was left behind by some extraordinary ancient demon.”

Speaking to here, Lin Ming suddenly said, “Don’t you find it strange that this underground mystic realm, this bronze coffin, and even the blood in the coffin is also a bit strange?”

Lin Ming’s words left Sheng Mei startled. “You are saying…”

Lin Ming pondered for a moment. He slowly laid down the spine and said, “I’ve always felt that this Demon God’s Tomb was somewhat ghostly. Many places are filled with horrifying dangers. I’ve gone to many mystic realms before, but the most perilous mystic realms I’ve experienced aren’t even a tenth as dangerous as the Demon God’s Tomb. True Divinities have a chance to perish here, and for Empyreans it’s even easier.

“I think that for any race, developing an Empyrean isn’t easy at all. As for True Divinites, they are even rarer. In a war between races a True Divinity can display a strength that can be enough to affect the entire war situation.

“Even if it’s the incomparably powerful abyssal race, they likely have over a hundred True Divinities. This quantity is over ten times that of the 33 Heavens. However, even they cannot afford to lose so many like this!”

Upon entering the Demon God’s Tomb, then if one didn’t consider Lin Ming and Sheng Mei, then the number of True Divinity level abyssals that entered from the Deep Alliance and Flood Alliance were 23 in total. And five of the ones Lin Ming knew had already died!

Outside this cavern, for the next hundred years in the Demon God’s Tomb, it was inevitable that there would be more True Divinity level abyssals that perished. Of the 23 original True Divinity level abyssals, ultimately over half of them would die.

Many True Divinities would be lost, and many of these True Divinities still had a great deal of potential left remaining. As for Empyreans, the number that died would seem a bit exaggerated.

Although it could be said that the Demon God’s Tomb might only open every several hundred million years, such a pace of death would still cause great damage to the overall strength of the Dark Abyss.

The brutal and tragic method of competition would hasten the birth of powerhouses. But, no matter how brutal a competition, there should still be a limit. If low level abyssals died then it wouldn’t be a problem, but higher level abyssals were created from massive piles of resources.

Listening to Lin Ming’s question, Sheng Mei faintly frowned. She thought about it for a moment and then said, “In the Dark Abyss, it has always been the strong eating the weak. The most suitable description is that we follow the most basic and most barbaric of the laws of the jungle. In the Demon God’s Tomb, although many strong higher abyssals die, those remaining still obtain incredible benefits. The reason the Dark Abyss has so many True Divinities is in great part due to the Demon God’s Tomb.

“Moreover, the truth is that many abyssals in the Demon God’s Tomb die to the hands of enemy forces. For instance, the conflict between the Flood Alliance and Deep Alliance has caused more and more abyssals to die. With resources and lucky chances before them, it is far too difficult to restrain the wishes and desires of these abyssals who have the law of the jungle engraved in their hearts.”

Sheng Mei’s explanation left Lin Ming shaking his head. “I’ve always felt that this Demon God’s Tomb is too evil.

“As the land of greatest lucky chances in the Dark Abyss, in the last hundred billion years the abyssals should have found some way to explore the Demon God’s Tomb while reducing casualties. However, the fact is that the casualties in the Demon God’s Tomb have always remained at a terrifyingly high level. You have likely discovered already that when an abyssal dies in the Demon God’s Tomb, they will quickly turn to bones and the strength of the blood vitality in their corpse will be absorbed by the world…”

As Lin Ming spoke to here, Sheng Mei felt a chill cross her heart. She also noticed this.

The world of the Demon God’s Tomb had a bizarre characteristic of absorbing the strength of blood vitality from those that died. Originally Sheng Mei thought this was normal. After all, every time the Demon God’s Tomb opened, a massive number of abyssals would come in and absorb the power of demon gods.

The energy in this universe followed the laws of conservation. If the power of demon gods was sucked away then it naturally had to be refilled with new energy. Sheng Mei thought that the energy from the abyssals that died in the Demon God’s Tomb wasn’t wasted at all. Rather, their corpses were turned into pure energy to supplement this world, where it would evolve into the power of demon gods billions of years later.

But hearing Lin Ming’s words, a light lit up in Sheng Mei’s eyes. She looked at the ancient bronze coffin below the cliff. The ancient coffin was still filled with thick and viscous blood, looking evil to the extreme.

And though this blood seemed evil, Sheng Mei was well aware just what sort of terrifying blood vitality was contained within. Certain abyssal alchemists could use this blood as material to refine the purest of blood pills that would be greatly beneficial to one’s cultivation!

“You’re saying that… the blood in that ancient bronze coffin comes from the blood vitality that is absorbed by the Demon God’s Tomb? The blood vitality of the corpses here seeps into the ground and slowly gathers here!?”

Realizing Lin Ming’s speculations, Sheng Mei gasped in surprise.

A spine was soaked in an ancient coffin filled with the blood of abyssals, and around this coffin was a demon relief with all sorts of complex and diverse demon array diagrams carved into the walls.

And all of this had been constructed deep below ground in the Demon God’s Tomb. Over the last 100 billion years, countless abyssals had died in the Demon God’s Tomb, and these abyssals all had a cultivation at least at the Empyrean level. Moreover, they were all outstanding elites of their generation. With so many proud children of heaven dying here and having their blood vitality sucked out by the array formation and gathered here, it was all used to nourish a single spine…

Moreover, who could confirm whether or not there was only such a single evil array formation beneath the Demon God’s Tomb?

Perhaps there were a dozen or even dozens of such similar array formations scattered throughout the Demon God’s Tomb. However, the only difference was that the bones they nourished might not be the spine, but rather other bones like the skull, ribs, femur, arm bones…

Thinking of this, Sheng Mei felt a chill creep up her back.

This sort of great array formation was like an ancient ritual, the most evil and diabolical of rites…

“Are you saying that there is some ancient demon in the Dark Abyss that is using the Demon God’s Tomb to nourish its own skeleton to eventually resurrect itself?”

To absorb the blood vitality and energy of future generations to nourish their own skeleton, reforge their flesh and blood body and finally resurrect themselves into the world, this was Sheng Mei’s first thought!

If this were true, then the shock brought by this guess was simply far too great!

To be able to change and invoke the rules of the Demon God’s Tomb for their own use, then perhaps this demon must be… the creator of the Demon God’s Tomb – the Demon God!

Could the Demon God have created the Demon God’s Tomb not just to help his race overcome the Shattering, but also to resurrect himself in the future? He buried himself here in eventual hopes for his future return?

Sheng Mei found this all unbelievable.

Lin Ming said, “I don’t know whether it is the Demon God or not. All I know that if there is such mystic realms like this cave beneath the Demon God’s Tomb, then there must be a scheme behind it. Moreover, once its purpose is achieved, it will surely bring out terrifying changes to the world…”

“Then this spine…”

Sheng Mei’s complexion was cloudy and unsure. Although Lin Ming’s conjectures were reasonable, something still felt off.

It wasn’t just Sheng Mei who thought this, but also Lin Ming.

That was…

If these speculations were indeed true and this was a terrifying scheme planned out over 100 billion years ago, then how could they have taken out this bone from the ancient bronze coffin?

Shouldn’t such a great array have a protective array formation surrounding it? At the very least, this ancient bronze coffin should be sealed so that others couldn’t open it.

After all, this was something that occurred 100 billion years ago. There were sure to be abyssals that managed to stumble their way down to these cavernous mystic realms during such a long time period. If these bones were taken away, wouldn’t that disturb this mysterious being’s plans for resurrection?

Chapter 2171 – Emperor Bone Sea

The world of the Demon God’s Tomb was stable; this was a world that had withstood the great Shattering.

The space here was difficult for even a True Divinity to break. As for the earth and the rock, although a master like Sheng Mei had the ability to shatter it, it was impossible for her to do so as easily as Lin Ming just did. If Lin Ming were to pour his energy into the evil bone then the might displayed could be imagined.

“If so, then even if you couldn’t perceive anything from this evil bone and even if you didn’t manage to swallow any of its energy, at the very least it could be used as a weapon?”

A light lit up in Sheng Mei’s mind. This demon spine was 13 feet long and it was as thick as Sheng Mei’s thigh. In truth, with such length and width, in some ways it was similar to an overlord spear!

Such a giant spear was far too large for Lin Ming’s true self to use. But, if Lin Ming’s demon avatar were to use it then it would be just right.

Before, Lin Ming’s demon avatar used the Black Dragon Spear that was wrapped in bone fragments. This spear seemed incredibly mighty and sturdy, but once it came under impact the bone fragments would actually burst apart, causing its combat efficiency to also drop.

As for this evil bone, it was impossible for something like that to occur. And not just that, but the spine itself possessed cartilage and was even connected with meridian channels, allowing it a certain degree of flexibility.

This spine spear could be used by Lin Ming’s demon avatar. As for the Black Dragon Spear, that would be handed to Lin Ming’s true self.

“Mm… it seems that I can only do this for now.”

Lin Ming turned his hand, sealed the spine with layers of seals before placing it in his inner world.

“Let’s adjust for a few months. Then, we can start looking for an exit…”

“Mm.”

………

In the Demon God’s Tomb, desolate loneliness flooded the land. Only time passed monotonously and without change, an unstoppable force that continued to beat on.

Two years had passed since Lin Ming discovered the evil bone.

In a vast and boundless black desert, the air was polluted with the light scent of blood. A dried corpse lay above the boiling hot sand, its blood vitality already sucked dry with only withered skin and bones left remaining.

Even so, there were some predators that were extremely interested in this withered corpse. If one tore open the corpse they could see fist-sized large black corpse insects digging their way through, and bone gnashing sounds emitting outwards that caused one’s scalp to tingle.

But at this time, not too far away from the corpse, a sand dune rose up. The sand dune grew larger and larger and sand began pouring down from both sides of it. After several breaths of time, the entire sand dune exploded and an iron tower-like abyssal leapt out from the black sands!

And on the shoulder of this abyssal sat a peerless woman.

This woman was slender and thin and she wore a black dress. She jumped down from the abyssal’s shoulder, her clothes fluttering in the wind as she gently landed on the black sands.

And at this time, the black insects hiding in the corpse froze in vigilance. They stared at the two unexpected arrivals, motionless.

These two people were Lin Ming and Sheng Mei; they had just come from the underground mystic realm.

Originally Lin Ming said that they only needed to adjust themselves for a few months. However, Sheng Mei couldn’t bear to allow Jiu’er, who had just been born, to follow Lin Ming in his battles so soon. She wanted to enjoy a quiet and comfortable period of time with Jiu’er.

Thus, they stayed in the cavern for a year and three months.

During this year and three months, the child grew ridiculously quickly. As for her foundational lessons, she learned everything at first glance.

However, Jiu’er’s talent in body transformation wasn’t too amazing. Thus Lin Ming and Sheng Mei decided to have Jiu’er follow the dual cultivation road of energy and divine; this was the same road that Divine Dream walked down.

Now, Jiu’er had already finished Pulse Condensation. What followed next was to open her soul sea in her dantian and formally step onto the road of dual energy and divine cultivation.

A year and three months later, Lin Ming and Sheng Mei started to search for a way out of the underground mystic realm. They used a full nine months before they were able to leave.

Perhaps this underground cavern had an exit or perhaps it didn’t, but in short, when Lin Ming and Sheng Mei wanted to leave, they couldn’t find an exit path no matter how hard they searched.

Finally, they chose a relatively weak place in the underground enchantment, and then used the evil bone to forcefully tear open a section in the curse seals and dig out a channel.

Then, they used the evil bone to dig through the ground and continued upwards.

Even with the assistance of the evil bone, Lin Ming and Sheng Mei had to spend a considerable amount of time and effort before they finally dug through the rock layers and emerged aboveground.

The underground rock layers of the Demon God’s Tomb was even firmer than the rock above. In addition with the massive underground pressure, if an ordinary True Divinity or Empyrean was buried within then they could give up on ever coming back out.

After Lin Ming and Sheng Mei dig their way out they also clearly saw the surrounding environment. This was a black desert in the Demon God’s Tomb. It was broad and boundless and countless bones were buried here.

“There’s a corpse…”

Sheng Mei’s gaze fell upon a withered corpse not too far away. From what she knew, this corpse couldn’t have died too long ago.

Sheng Mei slowly approached. At this time, the several insects hiding within the corpse suddenly jumped out, shooting towards Sheng Mei like arrows!

Sheng Mei’s expression didn’t change. She simply flicked her fingers.

Pa! Pa! Pa!

Like red lotuses blooming the void, these corpse insects blew up in bloody flowers before fading away in wisps of mist.

“These are corpse insects condensed from the power of demon gods. With them around, once an abyssal below the True Divinity realm dies, they will be cleanly eaten up without even their bones remaining.”

Lin Ming stepped forwards and looked at this dead abyssal. The abyssal’s abdomen had completely withered away. As for its chest, it still rose high because of the presence of scales, but these scales had been bitten through by the corpse insects and looked like the honeycombs of a beehive.

“He is an Empyrean level abyssal of the Flood Alliance; I remember him.”

Sheng Mei said after staring at the withered face of the corpse for some time. A martial artist had an extremely potent memory. Even with a single glance, many useless and needless images would be saved inside their mind and could be immediately recalled if necessary.

“He’s likely only been dead for several days, but I have no idea how he died.”

Lin Ming rubbed his chin, not having much interest in such things. During this venture into the Demon God’s Tomb, even five True Divinities had already perished, so what was an Empyrean?

But at this time, Sheng Mei’s complexion changed. “Something’s not right. Too many have died!”

“Mm? What is it?”

“When the disciples of Deep King Road entered the Demon God’s Tomb, they would leave behind a simple soul mark brand on a jade slip which me and Deep Child have. This is to make it easier to determine their location and relative situation. But now, I just probed the jade slip and discovered that out of the 20 some Deep King Road disciples that came, most of them have… died!”

Sheng Mei’s words caused Lin Ming’s heart to sink.

“Most of them have died?”

“Yes. All of the Empyreans have died without exception…” Sheng Mei said with a heavy expression. When the Demon God’s Tomb opened in the past, the mortality rate had always been high. Even so, in several hundred years, having 80-90% of the participants die was as the most extreme end of the spectrum, and those that survived possessed amazing talent. And with the great destiny that would add itself upon their bodies, their future achievements would be astonishing. In such a situation, a high mortality rate was actually bearable.

But now, not even ten years had passed in the Demon God’s Tomb and of the abyssals that Sheng Mei was aware of, nearly all of them had died. If another hundred years were to pass, just how many would manage to survive?

Lin Ming frowned. A faintly foreboding feeling stirred in his heart. He feared that there was some terrifying danger lurking in the current Demon God’s Tomb.

He seemed to recall something. He asked Sheng Mei, “According to the jade slip of the Demon God’s Tomb, the final abyssal ritual should occur in the Emperor Bone Sea. When does that begin?” Lin Ming traced his spatial ring. Within it were two ceremonial rites books. In addition with Sheng Mei, they possessed all the ceremonial rites books.

The ceremonial rites books were treasures that even True Divinity level abyssals would salivate with envy over. This was because those in possession of one would have a chance to undergo the abyssal ritual and become a totem level abyssal.

This was also what high level abyssals like Lin Ming and Sheng Mei cared about the most.

But now… having more ceremonial rites books in hand didn’t bring any joy to Lin Ming.

This was because… he could smell some dark conspiracy in the Demon God’s Tomb.

Was the Demon God’s Tomb really a lucky chance? Or could it be a complete trap to begin with?

Sheng Mei said, “I don’t know when the Emperor Bone Sea will manifest. It could be several years from now, dozens of years from now, or even over a hundred years from now - ”

Before Sheng Mei finished speaking, she stiffened. Just now, she felt a shaking from the ceremonial rites book in her spatial ring.

“Mm? How could this be..?”

Sheng Mei seemed to realize something. She flew up, instantly flying several tens of thousands of feet high.

Lin Ming followed close behind her.

As they flew into the higher atmosphere, their clothes flapped in the strong desert winds as they looked into the horizon.

In the distance, they could see a sea that seemed connected to the skies. It was ethereal like fog, rolling with vast and endless waves of smoke, seeming as if it would spread all the way to the ends of the universe…

“That… is that… the Emperor Bone Sea where the abyssal ritual takes place?”

Lin Ming muttered, shocked, as he stared at the incomparably vast sea. The Emperor Bone Sea had appeared before even 10 years had passed?